((( created, edited and synced by DR.Samir )))
((( happy watching )))
((( enjoy translaters )))
okay. Here we go
focus. Speed. I am speed
one winner.
Forty two losers
I eat losers for breakfast
did I used to say that?
Yes sir... you did
yeah sure. You say
that all the time
major! What are you doing in here!
Well, I didn't want
you to be lonely
well, thank you but
I'm kind of preparing for a race
I need a little quiet
all right.
You got it buddy
hey every buddy, listen up. My best friend
Lightning McQueen need quiet. Perfect quiet.
Okay, where was I
racing. Real racing
that ain't racin
that wasn't even a Sunday Drive
that was one lap
racing is 500 of those
everybody fighting to
move up lap after lap
inside outside inches
apart never touching
now that's racing
well, I can't argue
with a Doc Hudson
how true. How true
hey lightning. Are you ready? Oh yeah
lightning is ready
this one's for you doc
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
cars 3
come on stickers
that is bret, coming through
go mcqueen
lightning mcqueen
Hey cal, your blinkers are on.
What? No, it's. Hey
your blinkers are on
good comeback cal
and into the pit goes lightning McQueen
Bobby Swift and Cal weathers
these three are fun to
watch. Aren't they Darrell?
You know Bob I can't tell they
have more fun on or off the track
get the car washed too Cal.
No you're getting a car wash macqueen
get them back now
lightning, how do you keep your
focus racing against Bobby and Cal
I mean I
think the key is we respect each other
these guys are real class ass
congratulations captain
they're gonna pay
Great win today Cal.
Thank You Shannon
it was great moves hey hey
ha ha knock it off
speed 196m/h. Your speed
come on. Keep it going buddy
are my sponsors happy today
stop wining we're running
out of bumper green to sell
I am the flame
big tax how's my
favorite competitor
just say the word, I'll put call off the donico team
and replace him with you
you know I can hear it right.
I'm right here
bye cal, see you next week
we're not
oh come on now, I am joking
roll it buddy
and meet buddy too
another great physician
of 80s. McQueen and Swift nose-to-nose
how's the view back there Boby
well, you would better not bleep
or, I'll blow right past you
the flap is out it's the final
stretch McQueen in the lead
okay lets
see what you get
oh, it's Jackson storm for the win
a huge upset.
Even lightning or Bobby never saw him coming
it's one thing to start
fast but we haven't seen anyone cross
the line with that kind of speed and power
its the young Lightning McQueen first
arrived on the scene
hey Bobby, who is that? That's....
Jackson storm
yeah he's one of the rookies
thank you, I appreciate it.
Thank you very much. Thank you
hey, Jackson storm right .great race today.
Wow, thank you mr. McQueen
you have no idea what a pleasure
it is for me to finally beat you
oh thanks wait hang on
did you say meet or beat.
I think you heard me
what... maqueen over here .storm,
can we get some pictures?
Yeah yeah, come on. Let's get a picture
you know what. You can
get a ton of pictures
because the champ here has been a
role model of mine for years now
and I mean a lot of years
right, I love this guy.
I think I touched a nerve
welcome back chick`s pics and Chick Hicks
I'm your host former and forever
Piston Cup champion chick hecks
this just in
rookie Jackson storm slaps the
proverbial door on lightning McQueen
oh, I couldn't have enjoyed it
more if I'd beaten McQueen myself
oh, wait. I have
now enough about me. Here
to tell you how it happened
is professional number
cruncher miss Natalie certain
it is pleasure to be here chick and actually
I prefer the term statistical analyst
right, so who is this mysterious newcomer
Jackson storm and why is he so darn fast
it's no mystery if you
study the data mr. Hicks.
Jackson's storm is part of the
next generation of high-tech racers
unlike the veterans of yesterday
oh what, old-timers like this guy ha ha
right
storm achieves his top speeds
by exploiting the numbers
I refer of course
to racing data: Tire pressure, downforce
weight distribution, aerodynamics
and NextGen's like storm
are taking advantage
the racing world is changing
and for the better if it means my old
pal lightning is down for the count
am I right certain
well, if I'm certain
of anything chick
it's that this season
is about to get even more interesting
I'll tell you what down
Jackson storm has
certainly made an impact
we've got six more
next generation rookies in the field
with six veterans hired to clear
the way
goog mornin champ.
How's our living legend today
still very much a live, thank you.
Now, I would appreciate if
I can't believe I get to race the Lightning
McQueen in his farewell season
what are you talking about
what..the flag...
good luck out there champ
you are gonna need it
one reason storm and the
next gens are more efficient
their ability to hold the optimum
racing line every single lap
with number 3
for the rockey sansation
storms in a class of
his own and a big reason for that
training on the newest
cutting-edge simulators
these machines create a virtual
racing experience so real
racers
never even have to go outside
storms ability to hold that line
is like nothing we had ever see
four rows..are you kidding me
two percent lower drag
coefficient
I wanna finish
5% increase in downforce
lucky number seven
1.2 % high on top speed
Mr. cup winner Chick Hicks here with
the racer taking the circuit by storm
Jackson storm. Another easy win overall
catch ow
or should I say the boos
because he's always in the back. Am I right?
No, no, no, chick
McQueen is a crafty veteran champ
he's the elder statesman
of the sport you know
takes everything I
got to beat him
oh, you got kidding me
what changes are you gonna make
to get McQueen back on top
look... we try new trainee
method.. is he prepare to retire
guys let's not overreact it's
just a slump
we'll get him next week
okay that's enough
no comment
not even about cow
weathers retiring
wait what
cow weathers he's
hanging up his lightyears
no, no comment on that either
hey, Cal
hey, retirement
what's going on
you know, I asked my uncle once how I'd
know when it was time to stop
you know what he said
the youngsters will tell you
we had some good times together
I'm gonna miss that the most I think
yeah
more changes ahead check
every week we've seen veteran racers either
retire like Cow weathers tonight
or fired to make room for these younger
faster racers and it's not over yet
hello racers fans
welcome to the los anglos 500
the final race of the piston cup season.
I can do this
I raced for you guys
almost 10 years
sorry brick
my mind's made up
I'm giving your
number to someone new
at two wings last year
old sports
hey Bobby
do you know what's happening with brick...
you.. wait! You're not Bobby
my name is Danny bro
hey champ, where would all your friends go
the final check of his tires as storm
settles into the pole position
what we see in this season
was a great race
that's it Buddy
40 laps to go and race leader Jackson
storm is making his way on the pit road
with McQueen on his tail
a good stop
here could mean the difference between
victory and defeat
come on, come on, that's a
would be there. Come on
I want to get back there before he does
quito.... hurry up
what a bitch stop of macqueen
man, he just got the lead
can he hold on it
hey maqueen, are you alright
listen, don't you worry pal.
You had agood run
enjoy your retirement
storm takes back the lead
unbelievable! McQueen is fading
McQueen is fading
fading fast.
No..no... no.....no
no.
Welcome back to piston cup talks
around-the-clock where we
do nothing but talk racing
let's get to it
starting of course
with Lightning McQueen
the season start
just two weeks away
there's still no
official announcement
but with number
95 coming off his worst year on record
don't shoot the messenger here folks
I think it's safe to assume that lightning
McQueen's racing days are over
meanwhile Jackson's storm is looking
even faster than
the number six
and the number 12 cars
are still fighting it out to the lead
but wait, here he comes
it's the fabulous Hudson
Hornet knocking at their door
what's he got up his sleeve
today
and there it is with one incredible move
he has passed them
the Hornet takes this decisively
he's left the pen behind
its group chic bohemian
it's unbelievable
oh no, this is trouble
the Hudson Hornet has
lost control
what should have been a scene of jubilation
has turned tragic here today folks
we await news on the
Hudson Hornets condition
after such a devastating crash
we can only hope that this race today
wasn't his last
but if I they got put
together I went back
expecting a big welcome,
you know what they said?
You are history, moved right on to
the next rookie standing in line
there was a lot left in me.
I never got a chance
to show
crash! The Hudson Hornet
is out for season
hey, stickers
hey, Sal
how are you feeling?
Yeah great
really really great
you have been thinking about doc again
yeah
you know they told him
when he was done.
He didn't decide.
I don't want what happened to doc
to happen to me
but that hasn't happened
no, but I can't go out on the track
and do the same old thing. It won't work
then change it up. Try something new.
I don't know Sally
don't fear failure
be afraid of not having the chance
you have the chance. Doc didn't
and you can either take it or you
can do what you've been doing
sitting in here for month
and by the way I love what
you've done with the place
I mean the monster movie lighting
and the musky air freshener
and don't let anyone tell you
you're not working that primer
because wow, I have never found
you more attractive
and now that I've been in here
for a couple of minutes the stench
I'm getting kind of used to it
okay Sal, I get it. I get it.
I miss you lightning. We all do
try something new, huh
thank you to work miss Sally
did you set him straight with your
lawyerly powers of persuasion
is he ready to start training?
Well, stinky stickers
yes mater, I am.
I decide when I'm done.
I was hoping
you'd say that
okay, but I got an idea
and I'm gonna need to talk
to rusty and dusty, all right
oh, I'll get them on the horn
yeah get them on the horn
oops, bono got a speed
my gum, I lost
hey, I will you through.
I flowed it
hey, watch your steps
with a circular driveway
you boys need
to get your rusty tails down here
I created a drink in your
yeah, the rutsy
medicated bumper bomb
it goes down faster than
elevator for the win bag of them
rusty and dusty, hey guys
hey newest, good to see you lightning
thanks guys
you all here
sorry buddy,
did you just want this call to be private
no major. This is perfect
listen, thanks everyone for...
for sticking by me
it took me a while to figure it out, but
I know now it's time for
me to make some changes
changes! What kind of changes
it's futile do is ease change man
- you're right Fillmore.
- Really
which is why I have an
announcement to make
I've thought long and hard about it
done a lot of soul-searching and
considered all of the options
and I finally decided
you do want to keep racing
are you kidding! Of course
I want to keep racing
man for a second..., wait a minute...
i knew that all the time
guys, I'm talking about making this my
best season yet
we were hoping you'd say that
the thing is if I'm gonna
be faster than storm
I need to train like him
we hear you buddy
lightning, we want
you on the road
first thing in the morning
so you can come out and see the
brand new Rusty's racing center
wait, what! Rusteze racing center
yeah, it's got all the fancy bells and
whistles that the kids are
training on these days
we'll send Mack boy
all the directions
now get moving, all right
okay
yes
you too come, we offer two
back of the tire
hey, McQueen we can race him primer man
come on, let's go
parfum Moon, you have done it again
it's like the cestin Chapel on wheels
I am coming for you storm
welcome back, you look different
obviously
you look ready
wait, come. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Coming through
dont get those rookies in the trunk
all right, bye
go get them tiger
I'll see you guys in Florida
see you McQueen
dont get coming
good luck in college
hey Sal,
thanks
any time
good luck
love you
love you more.
Rusteze, here we come
it`s time to head
((( created, edited and synced by DR.Samir )))
((( happy watching )))
((( enjoy translaters )))
rusteze racing center
McQueen! McQueen!
Have you seen the
latest record storm has been set
have you thought about a retirement
that is enough, no
questions, excuse me
back off! Back off!
No, no, no, thank you. Bye bye
can you believe the.....
looks good, doesn't it?
Hey guys
what do you think
what do I think
it's unbelievable
yeah, you know it's kind
of a cozy humble little place
guys how did you ever do this?
You want to tell him or
should I Tell him,
you start .go ahead. Go ahead.
We sold rusteze
what?
What, do you think a couple of jabronis
like us could do this...
you sold rusteze
its all good news
we just realize that you needed
something that we couldn't give you
if I what the time was right for us too
I mean
we are as young and handsome as we look
oh, that's true. Besides
this sterling fellow
he's got every high-tech
thing you'll ever need
everything we wanted to
give you but couldn't
whoa, whoa, sterling! Who is sterling?
Lightning McQueen
you made some serious
time partner
your new sponsor
he's the
mudflap king of the eastern seaboard
welcome to the Rusteze Racing Center
you have no idea how much I've
been looking forward to this
thanks mr......
please, no mister. Just sterling.
I have been a fan of yours
forever and to be your sponsor
how great is that
I can't thank rusty and dusty here enough
tough negotiators by the way
oh-ho, you flatter us. But don't stop
anyway, I just wanted to say a quick hello
take as much time as you need
doors are always open guys
see!
Well, I sure I'm gonna
miss racing for you guys
you know, you gave us a lot
of great memories lightening
memories we'll
remember
wow that's good
hey lightning,
whatever you do. Don't drive
like my brother
don't drive like my brother
so, you like it.
Oh, hey mr sterling
my career on a wall.
Nicely you included doc
well, of course. He
was your mentor
losing him left a giant
hole in the sport
yeah
jars of dirt
sacred dirt
each of those jars contains dirt from
all the old tracks the doc raced on
Florida International
Thunder Hollow
just down the road and our very
own Fireball Beach right outside
hey, is that...
bit of asphalt from Glen Ellyn
my first win
you really are a fan
I am and a fan of your future
you ready for it
definitely
first let's get you into
a more contemporary look.
Wow
it's electronic suit with it
we'll be able to track your
speed and your vital signs
does it have a phone.
Toki crazy
race cars don't have bugs.
Wow..... not bad ha
this is really impressive
this Center has quickly become the most
coveted destination for young racers
training to make
our team someday
and it's where you'll train
until you leave for Florida
treadmills, wind tunnels, virtual reality
still working on that
and the best fitness regimen
anyone could possibly imagine
wait! Wait!
Is that a simulator
oh yes.
Lightning McQueen I'd
like to introduce you
to the multi-million
dollar flagship
of interactive races in Malaysia
the XDL 24 GTS RC
the X D L
Jaxon storm wishes he had this model
it is just like been on a
real track to put your hours in
okay, let's hit the truck most
come on, show me what you got.
Wow fast!
Who is the racer
no, no, no, no. She's not a race
she's a trainer. Cruz Ramirez
the best trainer in the business
ready to meet it, read it and defeat it
alright, now bring
up those rpms
I like the attitude here
we call her a maestro
of motivation
you're driving a little
tense again Ronald
no, no, I'm cool. I'm cool
do your exercise
I am a fluffy cloud .I am a
fluffy cloud. I am a fluffy.....
here you go
you're a clown
shut up curtain
here come
the bugs current you ready
hey, I kept my eyes
open this time
gotta see that truck. Oh, No.
Homesick again people
you guys gotta work through this stuff
so when your big chance
comes along you could take
hey, cruise. Oh, hey mr. Sterling
I'd like to introduce you
to Lightning McQueen
I hear you're the
maestro
mr. Sterling, did you say
Lightning McQueen was here?
Because I don't see him anywhere
uh, but he's right here
do you not see him
nope still don't see him
it's right in front of you
it is Lightning McQueen
he is obviously an
imposter
he looks old and broken-down.
Hey
with flabby tires
I do not
use that! Woah
oh yeah, I see I can use that
energy from motivation right
it's all about motivation mr.
McQueen
you can use anything negative as
fuel to push through to the positive
ah, pretty
positive ever since I was a rookie.
I am so excited that I get to train you
I grew up watching you on TV
ha, is that right
these young guys
are great and all
but I like a challenge
ha ha, not that much over.
In fact, I call you
my senior project
we need to loosen
those ancient joints
first, the wheels and bone
and rest and bone and rest.
Join me. Rest
and rest
is all these resting necessary
I am working with you and
slowly and peach for you much
peach for your much
now, wheel
to the fry
what is there, its your lines
now backwards
what is there
when we will go to the simulator
good morning mr. Macqueen .looking good
why
this will get oiler to places
it hasn't been in a long time
is that a drip pan
just in case
how old you think I am?
Visualize yourself driving
fast on a steep hill
I'll be back in the field
visualize...! wait! Wait!
Cruze
I feel what
I just like go on the simulator
how's it hanging
drip pan!
Okay, day three. Treadmill
offset maximum
speed to conserve your energy
what I want you to do, is
visualize beating this guy
storm! Uh-huh that's right
get him .get him mr. McQueen.
Get him
this is only going like five
miles an hour
we'll work up to the higher speed
right after you take your nap
nap!
Do I need a nap!
I am not taking a nap
how is your nap mr. McQueen?
It was kind of
refreshing actually
oh,.....okay what do you .....hey
you have been driving
on tires a long time
and you never stopped to get to know them
I'm sorry, what?
Tires are individuals
you should give each a name
name!
I will not be doing that
minor names. Maria, marika, ronaldo
and Debby Richardson
what?
Long story
may I have my tires back so I
can go on the simulator please
name them!
Lefty, righty, backy
, backy junior. Okay
does this make you mad?
Yes it does
use that!
Emerge and kneel
emerge and kneel
now, you got some tire damage
Thank You Cruz. I'm done
mr McQueen,
where are you going
to the futue!
Okay, here we go. Here we go. How
do I do this? Come on baby
mr McQueen
cruise, thank you for the old
man training as crazy as it was
but I'm warmed up enough and now I need you
to launch this thing
mr. McQueen wait until you can handle
it please
there are no shortcuts
okay, we'll just see about that
all right, my star racer
is on the simulator
why! Yes I am.
Well, let's see you
take it out for a spin
right away mr. Sterling
owner of the company
okay, have fun
this is what I'm
talking about
whoa! Didn't know about those
wait, what you didn't
say is it talking
the flag is out
but I don't see the
flag.... what do I do
go! Go! Go!
Oh..., that is sensetive
you have hit the wall
it shouldn`t be this hard, should it?
You have hit the wall
you are fighting the simulator
just race like you always do
you have hit the wall
there can't be this many walls
in a ring on the track
you have been passed by jackson storm
wait, storm is in here
the motivation
storm races at 2:07
pick it up mr. McQueen!
I am trying
you have hit the wall
mr. McQueen from now and from there
we will work you up to this
I am fine Cruz. I can do it, okay
you have jumped a barrier
you have hit two vechiles
You have to see an ambulance
you are on fire
danger! Danger! You
are going wrong way
look out! Turn it off! Turn it off!
Get these things off from me
you have crashed! You have crashed!
Are you alright?
You have crashed
I have crashed
your all washed up McQueen
I'm sorry, what!
I said floors all
washed up and clean
oh, right.
Thank you very much
good luck
hey, lightning. Come on in. I got
something to show you
you ready
for what?
You are about to become the
biggest brand in racing
we are talking about saturation on
all continents for every demographic
movie deals, incommercials
, product endorsements
mud flaps
of course, you will
be rich beyond belief
do you think
you're famous now?
How you'd be mad about the simulator
I mean this is all great mr.
Sterling I guess but.
I don't know .I never really
thought of myself as a brand
oh, no. Do I? I'm a fan maybe
your most avid
I think of this as your
legacy
it sounds like something that
happens after you're done racing
mr. Sterling. What is this about?
Look lightning!
I'm not gonna race you what
what!...what do you mean not racing
hold on! Hold on!
I'm not going to Florida.
Lightning!
You have no idea how
excited I was to get you here
because I knew I knew you'd be
back
this gonna be the comeback
story of the year but
your speed and performance
just aren't where they need to be
I'm sorry
we're talking about speed on a simulator.
Listen how crazy that sounds
look, I'm trying to help you
as your sponsor yes but also
as your friend
your racing days are coming
to an end
every time you lose, you damage
yourself
damage the brand you mean.
Oh, lightening. Come on
you've done the work now
move on to the next phase
and reap the reward
the racing is the
reward not the stuff.
I don't want to cash in. I want to feel
the rush of moving 200 miles an hour
inches from the other guys
pushing myself faster
than I thought I could go
that's the reward mr. Sterling.
Oh, lightening. Come on.
Look, I can do this. I can I promise.
I'll train like I did with Doc
I'll get my tires dirty on every
turn track from here in the Florida
I can start right there on fireball
Beach where all the old greats used to race
get your tires dirty
that's how you're gonna
get faster than storm
yes exactly
I mean sacred dirt, right
mr. Sterlin if you care about
my legacy, the one that doc started
you'll let me do this. I
promise you I will win.
I don't know
what you're asking it's to risky
come on, you like it .I can tell
it's got that little comeback story
of the year feel to it, doesn't it?
One race
if you don't win at
Florida, you'll retire
look... if I don't win also
I will hold the mud flaps you got
but if I do win, I decide
when I'm done
deal
deal.
Thank You mr. Sterling.
You won't be sorry
just one thing and this is only because
I don't like taking chances
you're taking someone with you
you talked him into it
way to go mr. Macqueen
Cruz! You could talk to snowmobile
into an air conditioner
you're going with me
with that thing
yeah, you still need my help
you're brittle like a fossil.
I don't need a trainer out here Cruz
you're old
what if you have fallen 0n
this Beach and can't get up
well, life's a beach and
then you drive
macqueen, thank you
this is beautiful
I can see why mr. Sterling said you
wanted to train out here
as soon as this thing's
booted up, we'll get
you on the treadmill and
I'll track your speed
what! No! The whole idea
is getting my tires dirty.
Real Racing not driving on that
thing when I've got the sand
and the whole earth
oh, okay.
Leweege let's do this
welcome a racer
to fireball beach
historical for
today's great test of speed
our finish line will be the
abandoned appear in the distance
all right, quicker than quick
faster than fast, I am speed
that is great self-motivation
did you come up with
that? Yeah I did
on your mark, get set! Go!
Here you go, felt good
hey, what was my speed
I don't know
I can only track you on the treadmill
no treadmills.
Oh, what about Hamilton
Hamilton here
who's Hamilton
my electronic personal
assistant you know like on your phone
you do have a phone, don't you?
Race cars don't have phones
cruze
Hamilton! Track mr. McQueen speed
and report it
tracking
I'll stay as close as I can
your suit will transmit
your speeds to Hamilton
fine whatever
quicker than quick, faster than fast
I am speed, come on lewegy. On your mark
get set and go
46 mile per hour
53 miles.. out of range
out of range. Out of range
it stuck.
I did not go
on sands you gotta ease into your
start or your tires can grab okay okay
you do work with race cars don't you
yeah but never outside
all right let's go again
go
54 miles per hour
here you go
75 miles per hour
out of range. Out of range
out of range
sorry
got stuck
go again
and go
sorry
go.
Go.
The beach ate me
all right Cruz, pick a
line on the compacted sand
got after-action you're
gonna spin out
let's do this thing
on your mark
you try to go
134 miles
out of range. Out of range
out of range
now, what!
I didn't wanna hit a crab
you gotta be kidding me
what! It was cute
now, your are gonna pick on
slow to let your tires grab
yes! And pick a straight line
on hard Sansy. Don't spin out
and all the Crabbies have gone night-night
mr. McQueen
all right, let's go again
150 miles per hour
175 miles per hour
196 miles per hour
right, finally you made it
congratulations!, how did I do?
You topped out at 198
198 that's it
still slower than storm.
I wasted my whole day
I wouldn't say that
it did feel great to
be out here doing real racing
listen, real racing
we are on a beach
all you do is go straight. How am
I gonna get faster if I don't.
Thunder hollow.
Thunder hollow
there is a dirt track there
that's what I need
to race against actual racers
not too public
if the press find you, they would be like
Many many bugs on you
guys, I really need this
hey, just leave it to me boss
I am a master of disguise
thunder hollow
you sir are officially incognito
hey boys, the father is new
the Great lightening mcQueen
I can feel it guys
tonight is the night I find my speech
racers..
Get over to the start lines
All right, more straight lines
just a good old-fashion
hey now, you that out-of-towner
yes that's me
Chester Whipple filter
and I'm Francis
beltline
cruiz, what are you
doing? I'm your trainer
I am gonna track your
speed from the infield.
Whipple filter
fine, just stay all the way
excuse me sir?
Where are the other racers
oh, they'll be alone. We always
let our guest start right up front
welcome young
to the thunder hollow Speedway
for tonight's edition of
crazy eight
did he say crazy 8?
It is time to meet tonight Challenger
Protect and swerve
cruz, this isn't
what I thought it was
come on, follow me
we'll slip out
rule number one:
Gate closes you rides
wait, no no.
I am not a racer
rule number two: Last
cars standing wins
and rule number three: No cursing
it's family night
excuse me sir
wait, no. I am just a trainer
the undefeated greatest champion
the demo of demolition
miss fritter
look here boys
we got us a couple of rookies
I will call you Marty Bridget
and you lamin nae
hey, neither one of them has a single dead
oh, h am gonna fix them
all right, every body
let`s go racing.
I am about to commit a moving demolition
cruz
what are you doing?
You gotta keep moving
I should be out here
move cruz! Move!
What I do
I get scared
turn right to go left
that doesn`t make any sense
hey fatty Oh, hey pal
look mom, I can drive
Get out of my way
hey, I am driving here
I am flying
no, I am not flying.
I got it
cruz
ah, buddy move it
turn right to go left
come on
buckle up everybody
it`s fritter time
fritter! Fritter! Fritter!
Fritter!
We love you miss fritter!
Oh, god run!
Cruz
miss fritter is down
nobody touches him. He is mine
you go get going whipple filter
come on, mcqueen
you can go, come on
Miss Ritter's can get up right folks
she is not pleased
you about to feel the wrath of the lower
Bell Bell County unified school desperate
ladies and gentlemen we have a winner
francis beltline
is that me, that`s me
I won I won
cruz cruz No no no no
watch out
whipple filter
it`s lightning mcqueen
got my tires dirty at
thunder hollow
the fans here in Thunder Hollow
still buzzing over
tonight's unexpected
appearance of Lightning McQueen
he has always been my favorite
my garage is covered from head
to toe with 95 posters
so.
Trophies are kind of nice
don't you think.
I mean I know you got like a
billion of them so you would know.
I still
can't believe I won
it's pretty shiny, I have
never seen one up close
looks like they spent a lot of money on it
I mean I think it's real nut up
stop! Just stop! Okay, Cruz
you don't even know
you don't even have one clue.
I was just trying to....
do you know
what happens if I lose this race
every mile of this trip was to get
me faster than Jackson storm
faster.
I start off getting
nowhere for a week on a simulator
I lose a whole day with
you on fireball beach
and then I waste
tonight and a crosshairs for miss fritter
I'm stuck in the same speed I
was a month ago
I can't get any faster because I'm too
busy taking care of my trainer
this is my last chance Cruz
last final finito. If I
lose, I never get to do this again
if you were a racer you'd
know what I'm talking about but you're not
so you don't.
Mack! Pull over!
Now!
Okay okay pulling over
pulling overr
ask me if I dreamed of being a trainer
mr. Macqueen go ahead
ask me if I got up in the dark to
run laps before school every day
ask me if I saved every penny to buy a
ticket to the races when they came to town
ask me if I did that so
that I could be a trainer someday ask me
no.
I wanted to become a racer forever
because of you.
I used to watch you onTV
flying in the air
you seemed so
fearless
dream small cruz
that's what my
family used to say
dream small or not at all
they were just trying to protect me
but I was the fastest kid in town and I
was gonna prove them wrong
what happened
when I got to my first race.
I figured it out what
what
that I didn't belong
the other racers
look nothing like me
they were bigger
and stronger and so confident
and when they started their engines
that was it.
I knew I'd never be a racer.
I just left
it was my one shot
and I didn't take it
yeah so uh
I'm gonna head back to
the training center
I think we both know
it's for the best
but can I ask you something
what was it like for you
when you showed up to your first race
how did you know you could do it.
I don't know, I just never
thought I couldn't
it was shiny with that felt like
good luck mr. McQueen
cruz
cruz, wait
Champion for the ages
, Chick Hicks here
coming to you live from
Chick Hicks studios
where I'm joined once again by
next-gen racing expert, Natalie certain
thanks chick, Piston Cup
champion Jackson storm
set a new record today when he pulled
off the fastest lap ever recorded
an unprecedented 213
miles an hour
so what do you think certain
stormy boy gonna start the
season with another win
highly likely chick
based on his recent run times and
forecasted track temperatures on race day
storms chances of winning are
95.2 %
that low huh
oh and in case you missed it
talk of the track tonight is
lightning mcqueen finding
yet another way to
embarrass himself
at a demolition
derby whoa
wow
almost makes me feel sorry
for the guy not really
here's what his new sponsor had to say
everyone relax, the 95 is gonna race
lightnings just
taking a somewhat
unconventional approach
to this race
it's one of the things his fans love
huh yeah right
talk about humiliating
show I won't even bother to
show up in Florida
that could be for the best chick
even if he does race. McQueen's
probability of winning is 1.2 percent.
Wow
numbers never lie I'm
willing to predict tonight
that lightning McQueen's
racing career will be over within the week
it might even be over now
I mean I knew his career
was stuck in the.....
berty find a came from the rusty bump bump
wait for me in the dark
make it in mark bump bump
and that's the way
done it's not a fun bump bump
lifting my funk making
sculptures out of junk
what's it
there we go, somebody's
interrupting genius
well, hey there buddy
mater!
You know I was just thinking of
you and here you are looking right at me
you see me okay
wait a second, let me see here.
Is that better
looking you straight in the eye there pal
hey sorry about calling so late
not for me it's not
I'm always burning
that midnight oil
so get me caught
up on everything
well, actually I am kind hope
I might hear what's going on back home
well, not much but if you don't count
sergeant Fillmore trying to run the tire
shop but tell the weed you not don't worry
sergeant's gonna track down every
last tired it fell more done gived away
other than that everything's good
how is Sally
oh she's fine keep him busy to comb
she misses you
we shoot we all do when you're on the road
yeah
you know, I've been kind of
thinking about that you know what
what we should do when I'm
not on the road anymore
what do you mean not on the road
you know
mater I can't do this
forever
I'm just not getting
anywhere with the trainee
if anything I've gotten
slower not faster
shit buddy it'll work out
just tell me what your problem is
now stay right here with you till we fix
it that's just it mater I don't know I.
I feel like I'm all out of ideas
all right, let me think
oh, you know what I do
what?
I don't know I got nothing
I guess I ain't dark when it comes to that.
I would give anything to talk
to him right now
if there was nobody smarter
no knock
well except for maybe
whoever taught him
wait, what?
I mean everybody was
taught by somebody right
take my cousin Dora
he taught me
how to sing and whistled at the same time
he was very musical that way
smoky
mater you're brilliant
uh well
it's all about shape of
your teeth
I gotta go to Thomasville.
Oh well good
you know me buddy
I'm always happy to help
think of better dad to
most low, you know talk
hey Cruz
you won't talk me out of this mr Macqueen
I'm going back
I resign as your trainer
all right
I accept your resignation, bye
uh okay
but since you cleared your calendar
why would you come with us
I'm looking for someone named smokey
hoping he can help me
maybe he can help you too
nah! Come on, I fixed it
no thanks anyways
but but I'm done
okay but maybe this will
change your mind, hit it
first I'm gonna loosen
up these ancient joints
no please don't
I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry that I yield
it wasn't your fault
that I almost got killed
but now
you're leaving then you won't get
all right I will go
just stop
how do you know Smoky is gonna be here
I don't
do you know if he's even alive?
Nope. Okay
so tell me this?
How do you know if it's smoky
wait, Mac pull over
thomasville speedway
home of 51 fabulous hudson hornet
good to see you doc
hey isn't that your
old crew chief
hey Cruz, do you want to check out the
whole track of the greatest racer ever
aren't we supposed to
be looking for smokey
oh that's right he is dead
we don't know that
are you sure you have time for this
for this
I do
piston cup
smokey`s garage.
Wow, this track could talk
cruiz, what do you say
let's take a lap.
Wow
yes, you nailed it
way easy without the school bus of death
trying to kill us
yeah, no kidding.
I am starting to think
I might never meet you
smokey!
He is alive
I know why you're
you're thirsty
I'll tell you what
these folks are gonna get a kick out of
me the HUDs boy
who's hud? Oh, Doc Hudson right
hey
act civilized, we got company
Would you look at that
what?
Look at the biggest racing legends ever
jr. Midnight Moon, River Scott who is
she, stormer Nash and she had 38 wins
well as I live and breathe if it
ain't Lightning McQueen
miss Nash
it's a pleasure to meet you
you had a tough year haven't you?
Oh uh should you be running practice laps
in Florida by now
yeah sure
you're here to steal our secret
looking for you lost mojo.
Wow, you don't mince words
around here do you
truth is always quicker, kid
look, she is an angel
But she used to have serious eyes for her
oh really
even if I did it wouldn't have mattered
huh didn't like fast women and that left
me out
the new one just fast
she was fearless
the second I saw my first race I just
knew I had to get in there
of course the fellows in charge
didn't like the idea
of a lady racer showing them up
so they wouldn't let me
have a number
what did you do
I stole one, what
I still short to take no for an answer
right River, if we waited for an invitation
we might have never raced
and once we got on the track
we didn't want to leave and
that's how doc felt too
you should have seen him when he first came
to town
shiny blue paint
not just a Hudson Hornet
he was already calling himself
the fabulous Hudson Hornet
did we ever ride him on that
not for long
hud was the fastest race of this side
of the Mississippi, until he wasn't
what
everything changed when
the rookie showed up
he took all at no time to work his way
through the best racers in both Carolini
fast river, fast loo
even junior
but there was still the rookie to deal with
he tried slamming
him into the wall
but hud never touched anything
unless he wanted to
that rookie never saw anything
like that before
docked it oh
are you kidding
couldn`t wipe the smile off his face
for a week after that.
I wish I could have seen him like that
like what
so happy
you didn't come all
this way for a quarter of oil, did you?
I need your help smokey
yeah, what kind of help
that's just it, I I'm not sure
all I know is if I lose in Florida
it`s over for me
what happened to doc will happen to me
what did happen to him
no, racing was the best part of his life
and when it ended he
we both know he was never the same
after that
is that what you think
come on
I want to show you something
you got the first part right
the crash broke HUD's body and the
no more racing broke his heart
he cut himself off disappeared
to Radiator Springs
son-of-a-gone
didn't talk to me for 50 years
but in one day
the letters started coming
and every last one of them
was about you
yeah, I'd love racing
but coaching you.
I had never seen the old grump so happy.
I owe it all to the doc
racing wasn't the best part of HUD's life
you were
ready to go out for little carbon air boy
yes I am
give it too much travel
you in the tulips
hey, lightning you might
want to take notes on it
you got a lot of stuff, kid
hud saw something in you
that you don't even see in yourself
are you ready to go find it
yes sir
all right, all right
lesson one: You're old accept it
I told him that
he is probably losing his hearing
he said you're old, I heard him
you'll never be as fast as storm but
you can be smarter than him
okay what do I
you said you were in a demolition derby
yeah it was terrible
are you sure?
Because there's not a scratch on you
funny what a racer can do when he's
not overthinking things
Shannon spokes here at
Florida International
jackson storm clocked
214 miles per hour today
you want to beat the storm
you need someone to stand in for
like a sparring partner
I'm not so sure
I not a racer
just a trainer
go ahead and cut it
yeah, with no muffler
you even sound like storm
oh you're going down McQueen
get that arthritis rail
keister onto the tracks, so I can
put you into the old folks
home against your will
how is that
it gonna work, work for me
, I'm good .yeah what ever she says it
you didn't show up in Florida
for qualifying
so you'll be starting dead last
I'll give you three
left to catch
go through the entire field
in three laps
you wanna beat storm or
not? Yes of course I do
well, then go
come on, kid
all right, looks like
we got some work to do
reflexes are the first to go
why are we in a field
sneak through that window
what is that mean? I don't know!
Go.
Not cool man, not cool
let`s roll it back
do you even want to be out here
only two days left, kid
we gotta work harder
wait aminute, who is that?
I put McQueen in there
to give you some real competition.
HUD was a master of letting
the other cars do the work for him
he used to say, playing to him is like you were
two June bugs on a summer night
he stole that form me
drafting, I've never had to do that
yeah that's when you were fast
now you're slow and old and
rickety and....
okay, okay, I get it
the new you has to look for
opportunities you never knew were there
sneak through the window
what?
When a window opens
take it
yes!
I made it
let`s go, let`s move
reflexes!
Alright quito turn up the heat
okay
alright, look who finally showed up
this where we cut our racing team
in the woods
let's just say the boom
was always shinemoons
if the moon didn`t shine we
didn't have to... oh, nevermind
we ran moonshine dummy
oh!
By the way, no lights
instinct only
macqueen still not here, didn't he pull
this when he was a rookie
this is my grandfather
told me
all right, we got time for one last race.
Hurry this along awesome
we got to get you to Florida
go
maybe it's best that he doesn't show up
you know after how last season how did
let me put it this way I'm not losing any sleep
wondering where Lightning McQueen is!
Come on! Come on!
Here you go!
Macqueen is fading! Macqueen is fading!
Fading! Fast fast!
Did you see that?
That was incredible
sorry. I didn't mean to...
hey, awesome it's time to hit the road
yeah, I wanna to thank everyone for
the training
we better get going to Florida
welcome to Racing's greatest day
we're beachside at the
Florida International Speedway
to kick off a new season
of Piston Cup racing
it's the Florida 500
43 cars in a quarter million fans
await today's intense contest of strategy
skill but most of all speed. This crowd is here for
one great day of racing
I'm bob cutlass joined as always by my
broadcasting partner darrell cartrip
and stat sensation natalie certain
I've never seen the numbers lineup for storm
like they do today Bob
storm should be ninety six point
eight percent unstoppable
well, don't overlook Lightning McQueen
whipple filter
we've heard stories of the unusual way
McQueen trained to get here
now the question is
did it work?
Speed. I am..... speed.
Hey boss, they call the racers to the track
Jeff board? How does
today's talent stack up?
Oh I think we're in for a treat
today these racers
hey McQueen, win one first old
guys ...we will do Jeff
hey guys, stickers
hey Sal, are you okay? Yeah
absolutely
listen, you're gonna do great today and
and no matter what happens
I'm gonna move on to the next
rookie and forget I ever knew you
I'm glad you're here.
Wow, nice costume come
here let's get a picture
it's so great to meet my number
one fan
what ajerk!
She's not a fan storm
oh, hey there champ.
I heard you're selling mud flap after today
is that true?
Hey you put me down
for the first case okay
lightning macqueen!
Hey lightning!
Hey mr. Sterling!
To the future. Hey champ
yeah, to the future.
Hey...... just focus on what
you're here to do kid
thanks smokey.
Now, go make HUD proud. You got it
lightning McQueen is making steady progress
in the early parts of this race
it won't be enough to catch storm
considered he started head last
I don't think he's doing
half bad out there
not too shabby
keep this up you'll finish in the top ten
top ten is not going to cut it smokey
I got to go all the way
so dig in
remember your training
find storm and chase him down.
Oh tell him he has three
laps to catch me
Cruz says you've got
three laps to catch her
okay. Tell her thanks
Cruz, what are you doing here?
Oh mr. Sterling I was
I would like you to head back
to the training center right away,
oh! But why? I need you to get Kurt up to
speed for the race next weekend
wait, not Kurt he's the bug guy, right
the other one Ronald yes
I want to stay and watch
that's not gonna happen cruze
now go
but mr. McQueen still has a chance
just go do your job
yes sir
and take off that spoiler and those racing
tires you look ridiculous
you are a trainer, remember
not a racer! Not a race!
If you were racer, you know
what I'm talking about but you're not
so you don't
no no, she's not a race
she's a trainer.
I wanted to become a racer forever
because of you! You!
It was my one shot and I didn't take it
it was my one shot I didn't take it
break in two! Break in turn two!
Hold on! Hold on!
Kid, are you okay?
Smokey, I need cruiz
never mind that now
no, I'm here back here
now get her back
yellow flags still out there
sir Hamilton here
call from Chester wipple filter
Chester whipple! Mr. McQueen!
!well the green lights on pit road is opening
and everybody's coming in
get ready guys Leweege
we know: Tire, fillmore, you
okay, I'm here what's going on?
No, not me... what!
What is she doing back there
come on guys, get her set up quickly
okay, wait! What's happening
hey, Remone got your paints
you know I do
wait! Guys! What are you doing?
I don`t understand it.
McQueen's just sit
there. Something's got to be wrong
mr. McQueen! Today's today cruze
you're getting your shot
what! I started this race
and you're gonna finish it
what! She will damage the
brand. She's just a trainer
no, she's a racer
just took me a while to see you
that can`t be legal .the rules only said
the number has to be out there
doesn't say who has to
no you can`t do that
hey, did I tell you
how much I love your mud flaps
get out of my way
bump it up, the facial flaps
the churche flaps
come on guys,
we gotta get her out there, let`s go
check fuel! Checked!
Remon!
Best I could do in the
time frame boss
yeah, that'll work
why are you doing this! You said it
yourself. This might be your last chance
which makes it my last chance to give
you your first chance Cruz
this time I want you to take it
she's got a beat that pace car out
no, no, no, you can't do that.
Now or Never
what do you say
25 miles per hour fits me
I know that
lightning McQueen's team has headed
a different car supporting the 95.
I don't believe what I'm seeing
you're watching this right
what the girl in the costume
you're kidding me
he put her in the race
the green flag is out
and good luck to racers
cruz, what are you doing?
Come on, pick it up
you got to go faster okay
call her Francis belt line and tell her the
the school bus of death is after her
what! No!
Trust me
Francis belt line, the school bus of
death is after you
oh..., right
okay, that was different
cruz, you are looking too tight now
come on, loosen it up!
Tell her she is afluffy cloud
what! No!
Smokey tell her
cruz, you are a fluffy cloud
oh, right... too tight.
I am a fluffy floud!
You just pick the turns
cruz, get your head in the race
no, no, no, wait, wait, wait!
Tell her she's on a beach and all the little
crappie have gone night-night
no ain't saying that
you tell her
all right cruz the beach
I need you to think of the beach
mr. McQueen! Yeah yeah it`s me
remember th beach
oh, pick a line!
Stick to it! I got it
all right, not too bad
this is nothing like the simulator
you got every toy in need
remember Thomasville.
Thomasville! Yeah,
sneak through the window
now that, I understand
sneak through the window.
I am just learning that the racer replacing
McQueen is Cruz Ramirez
this is her very first race
actually Darrell, it says here she
does have one win under her belt
at a place called Thunder Hollow
Thunder Hollow! Thunder Hollow!
I got it
watch out that, you gotta go high
go low! Go low!
Nice job, you are smoking these guys
now, watch the tire Marvel's launcher three
keep your tires clean, okay
bump, coming up on the inside
careful you don't go airborne
now, yes. Now!
Watch out by the wall it's a all
slick there .watch it! Watch it!
You have hit a wall. You have hit a wall
haha, just being aggressive
hey, come on... watch your rpm,
okay.
Get off the gas, on the brake on, the brake
two thousand
oh, we're back here,
sorry
alright pick them off, one at a time
go go go
that's it
nice and straight
go! Go! Go!
Bob, are you watching.
I just want to let you know
Ramirez is moving up toward you
why should I care
because now she's in the top ten
hey, now you are coming up on the leaders
Ramirez is of the fourth
in fourth
here you go!
Ramirez is in the third
what are you doing storm?
Hey, costume girl
you're at first I thought you were downhere
because your GPS was broken
don't listen to him Cruz
you look good
it's important to look the part that
you can't have everyone thinking that
you don't deserve to be here
just trying to get in your head
they don't need to know
what you and I already do
that you can play dress-up all you
want but you'll never be one of us
cruz, did you see what happened there
yeah, he's in he's in my head
no no
listen to me! You got
into his head don't you understand
he would never have done
that if you didn't scare him
what! He see something in you
that you don't even see in yourself
you made me believe it
now, you gotta believe it too
you are a racer!
Use that!
How far back is she now?
Look behind you!
What! Get in it storm! I am just back
here travelling at your butt
nothing to be concerned about
about two june bugs on a summer night
hey, hamilton!
Hamilton here!
How are my speed?
208 mile per hour, 207 miles per hour
stop that! You are taking me off the line!
Ah slap, come on cruz
my gps say that I have slow travelling my way
no no no
you are not willing to do that!
You are angry!
I am not angry!
You know, you can use that anger to push through
I said I'm not angry.
I don`t think so
cruz, get out of there!
You don't belong on this track
yes, I don`t.
I don`t believe it!
It's cruze Ramirez for the win
I didn`t expect this
cruz rameriz
way to go, cruze
man, heck of a win!
Yeah, heck of a win!
Hey cruze, you were flying!
Thanks
you really had it roll today, don`t you?
Thank you
hey cruz, your blinkers are on.
It is? You got me! Very funny
roll it cruze
go ahead? Get them some smoke
you'll get used to that
come on, move it! Move!
Cruze, I knew you
had something and now look at you
a winner. I could use you
as a racer on our team .we....
sorry mr. Sterling, I would
never race for you. I quit
well then race for me
Tex, miss Cruz I would be tickled pink
to have you race for Team Dinoco
as you know we have a long history
of great racers
except for the cow
Oh guys, I am still right here
team Dinoco cruze! Hire her
I don't care
lightning now that you're retired, I
need your first thing Monday morning
for a photo shoot
yeah all right mr. Sterling
oh, hang on now
what! Why is my name up there!
You've started the race
that's how it works
wait! What!
We will, no!
If lightning macqueen wins, he decides
when he's done racing that was the deal
hi I'm miss gorden... that was the deal
you are not a nice guy
look seriouslly, I gotta say,
you do make a quality mud flap in an affordable price
hey sterling, why don't you and I take
a drive and talk... billionaire to billionaire
kids got a lot of stuff
hey, doc
well she had a great teacher and now you
get to decide when you're done racing
so what's it gonna be stinky stickers oh
I'm gonna keep racing but before
I had something I want to do
welcome all to historic
for today's great exhibition of speed
thanks guys
nice paint, kid
hey hey, coming through
get it on 51!
Great number
it was McQueen's idea
he felt hud what he wanted you to have it
I love it oh it's perfect it's very
old-school
did someone just say old school!
Fabulous mcqueen
for doc hudson
you are trying something new
I like it.
Wow subtle! I figured if I'm gonna be
your crew chief I'd better do it in style
what's mr. Sterling gonna say
I'm actually more worried about what Tex is
gonna say considering the pot rusteze
thanks tex! I made that spelling fella
a texas-sized offer
so ready to start training! I don't know
you ready to lose again.
Oh, I hope you got your fluffy cloud
I hope you got your drip pan! I got my drip
pan and I'm taking my nap
bring it on old man
leWeegee! Go!
Ll ll created, edited and synced by DR.Samir ll ll
ll ll vote good if you like it ll ll
Craving big poker? Feast your eyes on Venom.
$5 million GTD. AmericasCardroom.com