Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
MISSOURI
EARTH
(singing along with "Brandy" on the car stereo)
- Come on!
- Slow down.
What do you say, my River Lily?
Come on!
Where are you taking me?
Come on, come on, come on.
Look. Look.
Oh, it's beautiful!
I was afraid it wouldn't
take to this soil.
But it rooted quickly.
And soon it'll be everywhere.
All across the universe.
Well I don't know what
you're talking about...
...but I like the
way you say it.
My heart is yours...
Meredith Quill.
I can't believe I fell
in love with a spaceman.
34 YEARS LATER
THE SOVEREIGN
PLANET
Showtime, a-holes!
It's gonna be here any minute.
Which will be its loss.
I thought your thing
was a sword.
We've been hired to stop an
inter-dimensional beast...
...from feeding on those batteries,
and I'm gonna stop it with a sword?
It's just, swords were your thing and
guns were mine
but I guess we're both doing guns now.
I just didn't know that.
Drax, why aren't you wearing
one of Rocket's aero-rigs?
It hurts.
Hurts?
I have sensitive nipples.
My nipples hurt!
Oh goodness me!
What about him?
What's he doing?
I'm finishing this so we can listen
to tunes while we work.
How is that a priority?
Blame Quill.
He's the one who loves music so much.
No, I actually agree with Drax on this.
That's hardly important right now.
Oh, Okay.
Sure, Quill.
No, seriously, I side with Drax.
No, I understand that.
You're being very serious right now.
I can clearly see you winking.
Dammit.
I'm using my left eye?
I am Groot.
They were not looking
at you funny.
That's intense.
GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY VOL. 2
Groot!
Groot, get out of the way!
You're going to get hurt!
Hi!
No, no!
Spit it out, spit it out!
Come on!
Disgusting!
The beast's hide is too thick
to be pierced from the outside.
I must cut through it from the inside.
Huh?
No, no, Drax!
Wait a minute!
Drax!
What is he doing?
He said the skin is too thick to be
pierced from the outside, so he...
- That doesn't make any sense!
- I tried telling him that!
Skin's the same level of thickness
from the inside as from the outside!
I realize that.
There is a cut on its neck.
Rocket, get it to look up.
Hey, giant sea monkey!
I'm here!
Watch it, Quill!
Yes!
I have single handedly...
...vanquished the beast!
What?
What are they called again?
Anulax batteries.
Harbulary batteries.
That's nothing like
what I just said.
But they're worth thousands
of units a piece, which is...
why the Sovereign hired
us to protect them.
Careful what you say around these
folks, they're easily offended.
The cost of transgression is death.
We thank you Guardians for putting
your lives on the line.
We could not risk the lives of
our own Sovereign citizens.
Every citizen is born exactly
as designed by the community.
Impeccable, both physically
and mentally.
We control the DNA of our progeny...
...germinating them in birthing pods.
I guess I prefer to make people
the old fashioned way.
Well...
Perhaps someday you could
give me a history lesson...
...in the archaic ways
of our ancestors.
For academic purposes.
I would be honored.
Yes.
In the name of research...
I think that could be...
...pretty uh, repulsive. I'm...
I'm not into that kind of casual...
Please...
Your people promised something
in exchange for our services.
Bring it...
...and we shall gladly
be on our way.
Family reunion. Yay!
I understand she
is your sister.
She's worth no more to me than
the bounty due for her on Xandar.
Our soldiers apprehended her
attempting to steal the batteries.
Do with her as you please.
We thank you, High Priestess Ayesha.
What is your heritage, Mr. Quill?
My mother was from Earth.
And your father?
He ain't from Missouri.
That's all I know.
I see it within you.
An unorthodox genealogy.
A hybrid that seems particularly...
...wreckless.
You know, they told me you people
were conceited douchebags.
But that isn't true at all.
Ah, shit. I'm using my wrong
eye again, aren't I?
I'm sorry, that was... that was
meant to be behind your back.
Count yourself blessed
they didn't kill you.
You're telling me.
- You want to buy some batteries?
- Ha ha ha!
All right, let's get baldly to Xandar
and collect that bounty.
Awesome Mix Vol. 2
That stuff about my father.
Who does she thing she is?
I know you're sensitive about that.
I'm not sensitive about it.
I just don't know who he is.
Sorry if it seemed like I was
flirting with the High Priestess.
I wasn't.
I don't care if you were.
Well I feel like you do care.
That's why I'm apologizing.
So, sorry.
Gamora is not the one for you, Quill.
Damn shadow.
There are two types of
beings in the universe.
Those who dance and
those who do not.
Mmm-hmm.
I first met my beloved
at a war rally.
Oh god.
Everyone in the village
flailed about dancing.
Except one woman.
My Ovette.
I knew immediately she
was the one for me.
The most melodic song in the
world could be playing.
She wouldn't even tap her foot.
Wouldn't move a muscle.
One might assume she was dead.
That does sound pretty hot.
It would make my nether-regions engorged.
Okay I get it, yes.
I'm a dancer, Gamora is not.
You just need to find a woman
who is pathetic, like you.
I'm hungry.
Hand me some of that Yaro root.
No.
It's not ripe yet...
...and I hate you.
You hate me?
You left me there while you
stole that stone for yourself.
And yet here you
stand, a hero.
I will be free of these shackles
soon and I will kill you.
I swear.
No.
You're gonna live out the rest of
your days in a prison on Xandar,
wishing you could.
This is weird.
We've got a Sovereign fleet
approaching from the rear.
Why would they do that?
Perhaps because Rocket stole
some of their batteries.
Dude!
Right.
He didn't steal some of those.
I don't know why they're after us.
What a mystery this is.
What were you thinking?
Dude, they were really
easy to steal!
- That's your defense?
- Come on!
You saw how that High Priestess
talked down to us.
Now I'm teaching her a lesson!
Oh, I didn't realize your
motivation was altruism.
It's really a shame the Sovereign
have mistaken your intentions...
...and are trying to kill us.
- Exactly!
I was being sarcastic!
Oh no!
You're supposed to use the sarcastic tone!
Now I look foolish!
Can we put the bickering on hold...
...'til after we've survived
this massive space battle?
- More incoming!
- Good!
I want to kill some guys!
You're not killing anyone.
All those ships are remotely piloted.
Dammit!
What is the delay, Admiral?
High Priestess, the batteries,
they are exceptionally combustible...
...and could destroy the entire fleet.
Our concern is their slight
against our people.
We hired them and
they steal from us.
It's heresy of the highest order.
All command modules...
...fire with the intent to kill.
What's the nearest
habital planet?
It's called Berhert.
- How many jumps?
- Only one.
But the access point is
47 clicks away.
And you have to go through
that quantum asteroid field.
Quill, to make it through that...
...you'd have to be the
greatest pilot in the universe.
Luck for us...
- I...
- I am.
What are you doing?
I've been flying this rig
since I was 10 years old.
I was cybernetically engineered
to pilot a spacecraft.
You were cybernetically engineered
to be a douchebag!
Stop it!
Quill, later on tonight, you're
gonna be laying down in your bed...
...and there's gonna be something
squishy in your pillowcase.
And you're gonna be like,
What's this?
And it's gonna be because
I put a turd in there.
You put your turd in my bed,
I shave you.
Oh, it won't be my turd.
- It'll be Drax's.
- Ha ha ha ha!
I have famously huge turds.
We're about to die, and
this is what we're discussing?
Son of a...!
Dude! Seriously!
Hey, let me...
Idiots!
Ah! That's what you get when Quill flies.
We still have a Sovereign craft behind us.
Our weapons are down.
Twenty clicks to the jump.
Hold on.
It's not ripe.
SPACESUITS FOR EMERGENCY
OR FOR FUN.
Come on, Zylak.
You can do this.
- Yes!
- Yes, yes!
15 clicks to the jump.
(cheers)
10 clicks!
Die, spaceship!
You suck, Zylak.
Typical.
It's 5 clicks!
Son of a...!
They went around the field!
Someone destroyed all our ships!
What?
Who?
One click!
- What is that?
- Who cares?
That's the jump point!
Go, go!
It's a guy.
Oh my god.
He's still out there?
Groot, put your seatbelt on!
Prepare for a really bad landing!
BERHERT
Ha ha ha ha!
That was awesome!
Ha ha ha! Yes!
Look at this!
Where's the other half of our ship?
My ship.
Either one of you could've gotten
us through that field...
...had you flown with what's between
your ears instead of what's between your legs!
If what's between my legs
had a hand on it...
...I guarantee I could've
landed this ship with it.
Peter. We almost died because
of your arrogance.
No, like, because he stole...
...Anulax batteries.
They're called Harbulary batteries.
No, they're not!
You know why I did it,
Star-Munch? Hmm?
I'm not gonna answer
to Star-Munch.
- I did it because I wanted to!
- Dick.
What are we even talking
about this for?
We just had a little man save
us by blowing up 50 ships!
How little?
I, I don't know, like this?
A little one-inch man saved us?
Well, if he got closer, I'm
sure he'd be much larger.
That's how eyesight works,
you stupid raccoon.
Don't call me a raccoon!
I'm sorry.
I took it too far.
I meant trash panda.
Is that better?
I don't know.
It's worse. It's so much worse.
You son of a...!
Hey!
- I've about had it with you!
- No! Back off!
Someone followed you
through the jump point.
Set me free.
You'll need my help.
I'm not a fool, Nebula.
You are a fool to deprive
yourself a hand in combat.
You'll attack me the moment
I let you go.
No I won't.
You would think an evil super-villain
would learn how to properly lie.
I bet it's the one-inch man..
After all these years,
I've found you.
And who the hell are you?
I figured my rugged good looks
would make that obvious.
My name is Ego.
And I'm your dad, Peter.
CONTRAXIA
You know what they say.
You're out of luck
until you've gone duck.
Yondu!
Come on down!
...this woman, I ended up marrying her.
I said, Aleta, I love you...
...but you're losing your mind!
And she's always been this way.
I could never trust her, you know.
Stakar.
It's been some time.
Seems like this establishment
is the wrong kind of disreputable.
Stakar.
There's 100 Ravager factions.
You just lost the business of 99
of them by serving one.
Please, sir.
Please!
Get away from me.
You can go to hell then!
I don't give a damn what
you think of me!
So, what are you following us for?
You're gonna listen to
what I gotta say!
I don't gotta listen to nothing!
You betrayed the code!
Ravager's don't deal in kids!
I told you before!
I didn't know what was going on!
You didn't know 'cause you didn't
want to know 'cause it made you rich.
I demand a seat at the table.
I wear these flames, same as you.
You may dress like us...
...but you'll never hear the Horns
of Freedom when you die, Yondu.
And the Colors of Orgord...
...will never lash over your grave.
If you think...
I take pleasure in exiling you...
...you're wrong.
You broke all all our hearts.
Pathetic.
First, Quill betrays us...
...and Yondu just lets
him go scott-free.
We followed him...
...because he was the one who wasn't
afraid to do what needed to be done.
Seems he's going soft.
If he's so soft,
why are you whispering for?
You know I'm right, Kraglin.
You best be very careful what
you say about our captain.
Who is that?
Yondu Udonta.
I have a proposition for you.
I hired Yondu to pick you up...
...when your mother passed away.
But, instead of returning you...
...Yondu kept you.
I have no clue as to why.
Well, I'll tell you why.
'Cause I was a skinny little kid who
could squeeze into places adults couldn't.
It made it easier for thieving.
Well. I've been trying to
track you down ever since.
I thought Yondu was your father.
What? We've been together
this whole time...
...and you thought Yondu was
my actual blood relative?
You look exactly alike.
One's blue!
No, he's not my father!
Yondu is the guy
who abducted me.
Kicked the crap out of me
so I could learn to fight.
And kept me in terror by
threatening to eat me.
- Eat you?
- Yeah.
Ah, that son of a bitch!
How did you locate us now?
Well, even where I reside, out
past the edge what's known...
...we've heard tell about the
man they call Star-Lord.
What say we head out there right now?
Your associates are welcome.
Even that triangle-face monkey, there.
I promise you...
...it's not like any other
place you've ever seen.
And there...
I can explain your very
special heritage.
Finally get to be the...
...father I've always wanted to be.
Excuse me.
I've gotta take a whiz.
I'm not buying it.
Let's go take a walk.
I am Mantis.
What are you doing?
Smiling.
I hear it is the thing to do
to make people like you.
Not if you do it like that.
Oh.
I was raised alone on Ego's planet.
I do not understand the
intricacies of social interaction.
Can I pet your puppy?
It's adorable.
Yes.
Ha ha ha ha!
That is called a practical joke!
I liked it very much!
I just made it up.
Give me a break!
After all this time, you're gonna
show up and just all of a sudden...
...you want to be my dad?
- I hear you.
You know, by the way,
this could be a trap.
Ok? The Kree ~Perus, the Ravagers...
...they all want us dead.
- I know, but...
But, what?
What was that story you told
me about Zardu Hasselfrau?
Who?
He owned a magic boat.
David Hasselhoff?
Right.
Not in a magic boat.
A talking car.
Why did he talk, again?
To help him fight crime,
and to be supportive.
As a child, you would carry
his picture in your pocket...
and you would tell all
the other children...
...that he was your father,
but that he was out of town.
Shooting Knight Rider or touring
with his band in Germany.
I told you that when I was drunk.
Why are you bringing it up now?
I love that story.
I hate that story.
It's so sad!
As a kid, I used to see all the other
kids all playing catch with their dad.
And I wanted that, more than
anything in the world.
That's my point, Peter.
What if this man
is your Hasselhoff?
Listen. If he ends
up being evil...
...we'll just kill him.
You're leaving me with that fox?
He's not a fox.
Shoot her if she does
anything suspicious.
- Or if you feel like it.
- Okay.
Hey. It'll be just a
couple of days.
We'll be back before Rocket's
finished fixing the ship.
What if Sovereign come?
There's no way for them to
know we're here. Let's go.
I'm uncertain about parting ways.
God, you're like an old woman.
Because I'm wise?
Why do you have so much luggage?
I don't want Groot
playing with my things.
I hope daddy isn't as big of a
dick as you, orphan boy.
What is your goal here?
To get everbody to hate you?
Because it's working.
Hey. Can I ask you a
personal question?
Oh! Noone has ever asked
me a personal question.
Your antennae, what are they for?
Their purpose?
Yes, Quill and I have a bet.
Ugh. You're not supposed to say that.
I say...
that if you're about to go through
a doorway that's too low...
...the antennae will feel this and
keep you from being decapitated.
Right.
And if it's anything other than...
...you specifically not being
decapitated by a doorway, I win.
They are not for feeling doorways.
I think...
...they have something to do
with my empathic abilities.
What are those?
If I touch someone, I can
feel their feelings.
- You read minds?
- No.
Telepaths know thoughts.
Empaths feel feelings.
Emotions.
May I?
Oh, all right.
You feel love.
Yeah, I guess feel a general
unselfish love for just about everybody...
No!
Romantic, sexual love.
No. No I don't.
- For her!
- No! That is not...
Okay.
She just told everyone
your deepest, darkest secret!
Dude, come on, I think you're
overreacting a little bit.
You must be so embarrassed!
Aha ha ha ha!
Do me!
Do me! Do me!
I have never felt such humor.
So unbelievably not cool.
Quill.
Touch me, and the only thing you're
gonna feel is a broken jaw.
I can also alter emotions,
to some extent.
Yeah, like what?
If I touch someone who is sad...
...I can ease them into
contentment for a short while.
I can make a stubborn person compliant.
But I mostly use it to
help my master sleep.
He lies awake at night
thinking about his progeny.
Do one of those on me.
Sleep.
I love this song.
There!
Ain't so tough now,
without all your toys.
Are ya?
Move!
Crap.
Hey there, rat!
How's it going, you blue idiot?
Not so bad.
We got ourselves a pretty
good little gig here.
This golden gal with quite a
high opinion of herself...
...has offered us a large sum to
deliver you and your pals over to her...
...'cause she wants to kill y'all.
Your Friend...
There's too many of them.
He needs my help.
If you care about him...
...you need to get
me out of these bonds.
They are going to kill him!
I'll tell you, it was
pretty easy to find you.
I put a tracer on
your ship back there...
...during the war with Xandar.
Give me your word you
won't hurt Groot...
...and I'll tell you
where the batteries are.
Lucky for you, my
word don't mean squat.
Otherwise, I'd actually hand you over.
Otherwise... what?
We'll take them batteries.
They're worth, what, a
quarter mil on the open market?
That Priestess offered
us a million.
A quarter is only one third of that!
A quarter ain't a third.
A quarter is 25.
No.
We can't even buy a pair
of boots with 25 units.
Enough!
The point is, we ain't stupid enough to
help kill the Guardians of the Galaxy!
The whole dang Nova Corps'd be on us.
That ain't right!
I just gotta say it this
one time, captain.
No matter how many times
Quill betrays you...
...you protect him like none
of the rest of us much matter.
I'm the one what sticks up for you!
Take it easy, Kraglin.
Damn straight, lads.
He's gone soft.
I suppose it's time for
a change in leadership.
Put your ~gob guns down!
Whoa! Whoa!
There must be some kind of
peaceful resolution to this, fellas.
Or even a violent one, where
I'm standing over there.
Well, hello boys.
It's not ripe.
EGO'S PLANET
Welcome, everyone, to my world.
Wow. You have your own planet?
Come on. It's no larger
than your Earth's moon.
Humility.
I like it.
I, too, am extraordinarily humble.
You own a planet and can destroy
two dozen spaceships without a suit.
What are you exactly?
I'm what's called a Celestial, sweetheart.
A Celestial, like a God?
Oh, a small "g", son.
At least on the days I'm
feeling as humble as Drax.
I don't know where I came from, exactly.
The first thing I remember is...
...flickering. Adrift in
the cosmos, utterly...
...and entirely alone.
Over millions of years...
...I learned to control
the molecules around me.
I grew smarter and stronger.
And I continued building from there.
Layer by layer...
...the very planet you walk on now.
Whoa.
But I wanted more.
I desired...
...meaning.
There must be some life out
there in the universe...
...besides just me, I thought.
And so, I set myself to task
for finding it.
I created...
...what I imagined biological
life to be like...
...down to the most minute detail.
Did you make a penis?
Dude!
What is wrong with you?
If he is a planet, how could he
make a baby with your mother?
He would smush her!
I... ugh! I don't need to hear
how my parents...
Why?
My father would tell the story of
impregnating my mother every winter solstice.
That's disgusting.
It was beautiful.
You Earthers have hang-ups.
Yes, Drax.
I got a penis.
Ha! Thank you.
- And it's not half bad.
- Huh!
I also have pain receptors
and a digestive system...
...and all the accompanying junk.
I wanted to experience what it
truly meant to be human.
As I set out amongst the stars...
...'til I found...
...what I sought.
Life.
I was not alone in the
universe after all.
When did you meet my mother?
Not long after.
It was, with Meredith, that I
first experienced love.
I called her my River Lily.
And from that love, Peter...
You.
I've searched for you for so long.
And when I heard of
a man from Earth...
...who held an Infinity Stone
in his hand without dying...
...I knew you must be the
son of the woman I loved.
If you loved her, why
did you leave her?
You should ~?
Sorry about this!
Captain!
Help me!
Please help!
Captain!
You're the one what killed those men...
...by leading them
down the wrong path.
Because you're weak.
And stupid!
It's time for the Ravengers...
...to rise once again to glory
with a new captain...
Taserface!
Aha ha ha ha!
I'm sorry.
Your name is...
...it's Taserface?
That's right.
Do you shoot tasers
out of your face?
It's metaphorical!
Yeah!
For what?
For...
It is a name what strikes fear...
...into the hearts of
anyone what hears it!
Okay.
Okay...
Whatever you say.
You shut up.
You're next.
Udonta, I've been
waiting a long time to...
What?
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
I just keep imagining
you waking up in the morning, sir...
...looking in the mirror and,
in all seriousness, saying to yourelf...
You know what would be a really
kick-ass name? Taserface!
Ah ha ha!
That's how I hear you in my head!
I can't take it anymore!
What was your second choice?
Scrotum Hat?
New plan.
We're killing you first.
Well. Dying is certainly better than
having to live an entire life...
...as a moronic shitbag who thinks
Taserface is a cool name.
That's enough killing for today.
She's the daughter of Thanos.
I thought you were the biggest
sadist in the galaxy.
That was when daddy was
paying my bills.
The Priestess wants to
kill the fox herself.
And he has bounties on his head
in at least 12 Kree provinces.
I assure you...
I am not as easy a mark as an
old man without his magic stick...
...or a talking woodland beast.
I want ten percent of the take.
And a couple more things.
We got a whole box of hands...
...if that one don't work out.
- It is fine.
You, uh, think them Kree is
gonna execute the captain?
The Kree consider themselves
merciful. It will be painless.
Well, uh, here it is.
It's the best ship we got.
The location of Ego's planet
in the nav.
We'll wire you the ten percent
once we's paid.
What're you gonna do
with your share?
As a child, my father would have Gamora
and me battle one another in training.
Every time my sister prevailed...
...my father would replace a
piece of me with machinery...
...claiming he wanted me
to be her equal.
But she won.
Again and again and again,
never once refraining.
So, after I murder my sister...
...I will buy a warship will every
conceivable instrument of death.
I will hunt my father like a
dog and I will tear him apart slowly...
...piece by piece...
until he knows some semblance
of the profound and unceasing pain...
...I know every single day.
Yeah...
...I was talking about
a pretty necklace.
Or a nice hat, you know.
Something to make the other
girls go, Ooooh, that's nice.
Anyways, happy trails.
My mother told everyone my
father was from the stars.
She had brain cancer, so
everyone thought she was delusional.
Peter.
Listen, I'd love to believe
all of this, I really would.
But you left...
The most wonderful woman ever...
...to die alone.
I didn't want to leave
your mother, Peter.
If I don't return regularly
to my planet...
...and the light within it...
...this form will wither and perish.
Then why didn't you come back?
Why did you send Yondu?
A criminal, of all people, to
come and to fetch me.
I loved your mother, Peter!
I couldn't stand to step
foot on an Earth...
...where she wasn't living!
You can't imagine what that's like!
I know exactly what that feels like!
I had to watch her die!
Over the millions and millions
of years of my existence...
...I've made many mistakes, Peter.
But you're not one of them.
Please give me the chance to be
the father she would want me to be.
There's so much that I need to
teach you about this planet...
...and the light within.
They are a part of you, Peter.
What do you mean?
Give me your hand, son.
Here.
Hold them like that.
Now, close your eyes
and concentrate.
Take your brain to the
center of this planet.
Yes!
Whoa!
- Yes!
- What was it?
It's okay, just relax.
Concentrate.
You can do it.
Bring it back.
Yes!
Yes, now, shape it.
Feel that energy.
Yes.
You're home.
Peter.
How'd you get to this
weird, dumb planet?
Ego found me in my larvae state.
Orphan on my homeworld.
He raised me by hand and
kept me as his own.
So, you're a pet.
I suppose.
People usually want cute pets.
Why would Ego want such
a hideous one?
I am hideous?
You are horrifying to look at, yes.
- But that's a good thing.
- Oh?
When you're ugly and
someone loves you...
...you know they love
you for who you are.
Beautiful people never
know who to trust.
Well, then I am certainly
grateful to be ugly.
Those pools, they remind
me of a time...
...when I took my daughter to the
Forgotten Lakes of my homeworld.
She was like you.
Disgusting?
Innocent.
Drax?
There's something I
must tell you.
What's going on?
This gross bug lady
is my new friend.
I'm learning many things,
like I'm a pet and ugly.
You're not ugly.
Drax.
What are you talking about?
Mantis.
Can you show us where
we'll be staying?
Why are there no other
beings on this planet?
The planet is Ego.
A dog would not invite a
flea to live on his back.
And you're not a flea?
I'm a flea with a purpose.
I help him sleep.
What were you about to say
to Drax before I walked out?
Nothing.
Your quarters are this way.
We deliver you to
the Kree in the morning.
Neither one of you will last
much longer after that.
Okay, Taserface.
Hey, tell the other guys, we said...
Hi, Taserface!
Oh! Hey, what about this little plant?
Can I smash it with a rock?
No, Gef.
It's too adorable to kill.
Take it to the tailor.
No offense, but your employees
are a bunch of jerks.
I was a Kree battle slave for
20 years when Stakar freed me.
He offered me a place with the Ravagers.
He said, all I needed to do
was adhere to the code.
But I was young...
...and greedy and stupid.
Like you stealing those batteries.
That was mostly Drax.
Me & Stakar, and the other captains...
...we won't so different from
you and your friends.
The only family I ever had.
When I broke the code...
...they exiled me.
This is what I deserve.
Slow down, drama queen.
You might deserve
this, but I don't.
We gotta get out of here.
Where's Quill?
Ah, he went off with his old man.
- Ego?
- Yeah.
It's a day for dumb-ass names.
You smiled. There for a second
I got a warm feeling.
But then it was ruined by
those disgusting-ass teeth.
You're like, a professional
asshole, or what?
Pretty much a pro.
Why didn't you deliver Quill
to Ego like you promised?
He was skinny.
He fit into places we couldn't.
Good for thieving.
Uh huh.
I got an idea on how
to get out of here.
But we're gonna need
your little friend.
Mascot! Mascot!
Mascot!
You fellas all want
~sausage drunk?
Look how cute it is
when it's all riled up.
It's god-dang precious.
Psst! Hey, twig!
Come here.
Come on.
Aw man.
What'd they do to you?
Hey, you want to
help us get out of here?
There's something I need you
to get and bring back to me.
In the captain's quarters,
there's a prototype fin.
The thing I wore in my head.
There's a drawer next to the bunk.
It's in that. It's red.
You got it?
- Ugh.
- That's my underwear.
Yeah, I was pretty sure he didn't
know what you were talking about.
You have to explain
it more careful.
It's a prototype fin.
That's an Orloni.
It's a fin, Groot.
You try it this time.
All right.
That's Vorker's eye.
He takes it out when he sleeps.
Go, look again.
But leave the eye here.
Why?
He's gonna wake up tomorrow...
and he's not gonna know...
...where his eye is!
Ha ha ha ha!
That's a desk.
We told you it was this big.
Tell me you guys have
a refrigerator somewhere...
...with a bunch of
severed human toes.
Okay, then let's just agree
to never discuss this.
The drawer you want to open
has this symbol on it.
Okay?
What? No!
He thinks you want him
to wear it as a hat.
That's not what I said!
- I am Groot!
- He's relieved you don't want him to.
- I am Groot.
- He hates hats.
I am Groot.
On anyone, not just himself.
One minute, you think someone
has a weird shaped head...
...the next minute, just because,
you realize part of that head is the hat.
That's why you don't like hats?
This is an important
conversation right now?
What you have there?
I didn't mean to do a mutiny.
They killed all my friends.
Get the third quadrant
ready for release.
One more thing.
You got any clones of
Quill's old music on the ship?
He's got it!
Yondu's got the fin!
Go!
Down there!
You maniac!
The whole ship's gonna blow.
Not the whole ship.
Who is this?
I am sending you the
coordinates for Yondu's ship.
- Release the quadrant!
- Aye, captain!
I only ask one thing.
That your High Priestess...
...tell him the name of
the man what sealed his fate.
Taserface!
Where to, captain?
Ego.
No, boy!
It ain't healthy, mammalian body
to hop more than 50 jumps at a time.
I know that.
We're about to do 700!
So, I guess this could all
be mine someday.
Rocket?
Rocket, are you there?
What are you doing, Peter?
Dance with me.
I'm not going to dance with you.
This is Sam Cooke...
...one of the greatest
Earth singers of all time.
Drax says you're not a dancer.
If you ever tell anyone about this...
...I will kill you.
When are we going to do something
about this unspoken thing between us?
What unspoken thing?
This...
...Cheers, Sam and Diane...
...guy and a girl on a
TV show who dig each other...
...but never say it because the
TV ratings would go down...
...sort of thing.
There's no unspoken thing here.
Well, it's a catch-22, because if
you said it then it would be spoken...
...and you'd be a liar.
So, by not saying it...
...you are telling the truth
and admitting that there is.
No, that's not what I...
What we should be discussing
right now is, something about this place.
It doesn't feel right.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who
wanted me to come here.
That girl, Mantis...
...she's afraid of something.
Why are you trying to take
this away from me?
I'm not trying...
He's my father.
He's blood.
Well you have blood on Earth,
you never wanted to return there.
Again, you made me come here.
And Earth, Earth is the place
where my mother died in front of me.
No, it's because that place is
real, and this is a fantasy.
This is real!
I'm only half human, remember?
That's the half I'm worried about.
Oh, so... I get it.
You're jealous...
...because I'm part god and
you like when I'm the weak one.
You were insufferable to begin with.
I haven't been able
to reach Rocket.
I'm going to go outside and
try to get a signal.
You know what?
This is not Cheers after all.
This is whatever the show is where
one person is willing to...
...open themselves up to to new
possibilities, and the other person...
...is a jerk who
doesn't trust anybody!
It's a show that doesn't exist!
That's why it would get zero ratings.
I don't know what Cheers is.
I finally found my family.
Don't you understand that?
I thought you alread had.
Psychopath!
Are you kidding me!
I win.
I win, I bested you in combat.
No.
I saved your life.
Well you were stupid
enough to let me live.
You let me live!
I don't need you to
always try and defeat me!
I'm not the one who just flew across the
universe just because I wanted to win.
Do not tell me what I want.
I don't need to tell
you what you want!
It's obvious!
You were the one who wanted to win.
And I just wanted a sister!
You were all I had.
But you were the one
who needed to win.
Thanos pulled my eye
from my head...
...and my brain from my skull...
...and my arm from my body...
...because of you.
AWESOME MIX VOL. 2
You all right, son?
I saw your girl stomp off
a little earlier in quite a huff.
Yeah.
It's fortuitous,...
...you listening to this song.
You know, uh, "Brandy?"
By Looking Glass?
A favorite of your mom's.
Yes. Yeah, it was.
One of Earth's greatest
musical compositions.
Perhaps its very greatest.
Yeah, yes!
You know, Peter, you and I, we're...
we're the sailer in that song.
He came on a summer's day.
Bringing gifts from far away.
Like the child I put
in your mother.
Or the freedom you brought Gamora.
Brandy, you're a fine girl.
What a good wife you would be.
My life, my love,
my lady, is the sea.
The sea calls the sailor back.
And he loves the girl, but
that's not his place.
The sea calls upon him as
history calls upon great men.
And sometimes we are deprived
the pleasures of mortals.
Well, you may not be
mortal, but me...
No, Peter.
Death will remain a
stranger to both of us...
...as long as the light
burns in this planet.
- I'm immortal?
- Mm-hm.
Really?
Yes!
As long as this light exists.
And I can use the light to
build cool things, like...
...how you made this whole planet?
Well, it may take you a few
million years of practice...
...before you get
really good at it.
But, yes!
What?
This is...! Well, get ready for
an 800-foot statue of Pac-Man...
...with Skeletor and Heather Locklear.
Whatever you want.
I'm gonna make some weird shit.
You know, Peter, it is
a tremendous responsibility.
Only we can remake the universe.
Only we can take the
bridle of the cosmos...
...and lead it to
where it needs to go.
How?
Come with me.
Drax. Drax.
Drax! Drax!
We need to talk.
I'm sorry.
But I like a woman with
some meat on her bones.
What?
I tried to let you down easily by
telling you I found you disgusting.
No, that's not why...
What are you doing?
I'm imagining being with you.
Drax, that's not...
I don't like you like that.
I don't even know the
type of thing you are.
Hey!
There's no need to get personal.
Listen!
Ego's gotten exactly what he wanted.
I should have told you earlier.
I is stupid.
You are in danger.
What is that?
Now, you need to readjust
the way you process life.
Everything around us,
including the girl...
...everything is temporary.
We are forever.
Doesn't eternity get boring?
Not if you have a purpose, Peter.
Which is why you're here.
I told you how all those years ago...
...I had an unceasing
impulse to find life.
But what I did not tell you
is how I finally did find it.
It was all so...
...disappointing.
And that is when I came...
...to a profound realization.
My innate desire to
seek out other life...
...was not so that I
could walk among that life.
Peter.
I have found meaning.
I see it.
Eternity.
Oh my god.
We need to get off this planet.
Oh man.
Anyway, before I was so
rudely interrupted.
At that time, I was
a Federal Express man.
What the hell you doing, boy?
I could tell by how
you talked about him...
...this Ego is bad news.
We are here to save Quill.
For what? Huh?
For honor? For love?
No.
I don't care about those things.
I want to save Quill so I
can prove I'm better than him!
I can lord this
over him forever.
What are you laughing
at me for?
Oh, you can fool yourself and
everyone else, but you can't fool me.
I know who you are.
You do not know anything
about me, loser.
I know everything about you.
I know you play like your the
meanest and the hardest...
...but actually you're the
most scared of all.
Shut up!
I know you steal batteries
you don't need...
...and you push away anyone
who's willing to put up with you...
Because just a little bit of love...
...reminds you how big and empty
that hole inside you actually is.
I said, shut up!
I know them scientists what made
you never gave a rat's ass about you.
I'm serious, dude.
Just like my own damn parents,
who sold me,...
...their own little
baby, into slavery.
I know who you are, boy.
Because you're me.
What kind of a pair are we
The kinds that's about to
go fight a planet, I recon.
All right!
Okay.
Wait.
Fight a what?
Who are you people?
What is this place?
Gamora, let her go!
The bodies in the
caverns, who are they?
You are scared.
I call it, the Expansion.
It is my purpose.
Now, it is yours, as well.
It's beautiful.
Over thousands of years...
...I implanted thousands
of extension of myself...
...on thousands of worlds.
I need to fulfill life's
one true purpose...
...to grow and spread...
...covering all that exists...
...until everything is...
...me.
What did she do to me?
She already told me everything.
I only had one problem.
A single Celestial doesn't have
enough power for such an enterprise.
But two Celestials...
...well, now, that just might do.
The bodies...
...are his children.
Out of all my labors...
...the most beguiling
was attempting to...
...graft my DNA with
that of another species.
I hoped the result of such
a coupling would be...
...enough to power the Expansion.
I had Yondu deliver
some of them to me.
It broke the Ravager code, but
I compensated him generously, and...
...to ease his conscience,
I said I'd never hurt them.
And that was true,
they never felt a thing.
But, one after the
other, they failed me.
Not one of them
carried the Celestial genes.
Until you, Peter.
Out of all my spawn...
...only you carry the
connection to the light.
We need to find Peter now
and get off this damn planet.
Ego will have brought
him to his side by now.
- He has a way.
- Then we just go.
- No!
- He's our friend.
- All any of you do...
...is yell at each other.
You're not friends.
You're right.
We're family.
We leave noone behind.
Except maybe you.
Thank you.
For the first time
in my existence...
...I am truly not alone!
What is it, son?
My friends.
Oh, no, you see,
that's the mortal in you, Peter.
Yes.
We are beyond such things.
- Now...
- But my mother...
You said you loved my mother.
And that I did.
My River Lily who knew all the words
to every song that came over the radio.
I returned to Earth to
see her three times.
And I knew if returned a 4th...
...I'd never leave.
The Expansion...
...the reason for my very
existence would be over, so...
...I did what I had to do.
But it broke my heart
to put that tumor in her head.
What?
Now, now, I know...
...that sounds bad.
Who in the hell
do you think you are?
You killed my mother!
I tried...
...so hard...
...to find the form...
...that best suited you...
...and this is
the thanks I get?
You really need to grow up.
I wanted to do this together.
But I suppose you'll have to learn by
spending the next thousand years...
...as a battery.
Finally! Rocket?
Keep that transmitter
nearby so I can find you.
We're in an old piece of construction
Wip and Yondu once used...
...to slice open the bank of A'askavaria.
Ego's unhinged.
I know.
Get ready.
Cut him loose, Kraglin.
No.
My life, my love,
my lady, is the sea.
Peter.
This is the sea.
Hey there, jackass!
- What is that?
- Whoa, it's ~?
Out of the way,
dumber, smaller Groot!
I told you something
didn't feel right.
"I told you so?"
Just what I need to hear right now.
Well, I came back, didn't I?
Because of the unspoken thing.
There is no unspoken thing.
What are you doing?
You could have killed us all.
Uh, "Thank you, Rocket?"
We had it under control.
We did not.
That is only an extension of...
...his true self.
He will be back soon.
What's Smurfette doing here?
Whatever I need to do
to get a damn ride home.
She tried to murder me!
I saved you, you stupid fox!
He's not a fox.
- I am Groot.
- I'm not a rabboon either.
I am Groot.
Raccoon.
Whatever.
How do we kill a Celestial?
There's a center to him.
His brain, his soul, whatever it is,
in some sort of protective shell.
It's in the caverns...
...below the surface.
Yondu?
Thrusters are out.
I guess I should be
glad I was a skinny kid.
Otherwise you would've
delivered me to this maniac.
You still recon that's the
reason I kept you around, idiot?
That's what you
told me, you old doofus.
Well once I figured out what
happened to them other kids...
...I wasn't just
gonna hand you over.
You said you were
gonna eat me.
That was being funny.
Not to me!
You people have issues.
Well of course I have issues.
That's my freaking father!
Thrusters are back up.
- We should be going up!
- We can't.
Ego wants to eradicate the
universe as we know it.
We have to kill him.
Rocket!
Got it!
So, we're saving the galaxy again?
I guess.
Awesome!
We're really gonna be
able to jack up our price...
...if we're two-time galaxy savers.
I seriously can't believe
that's where your mind goes.
It was just a random thought,
man. I thought we were friends?
Of course, I care about
the planets and the buildings...
...and all the animals
on the planets.
And the people.
Meh.
The crabby puppy's so cute.
He makes me want to die!
Soup! Soup!
Pilots...
...release envoy units.
Our sensors detect a battery
below the surface of the planet.
Dive!
Um. Cap'n?
Cap'n?
Tell me, why'd Ego
want you here?
He needs my genetic
connection to the light...
...to help destroy the universe.
He tried to teach me how
to control the power.
So, could you?
A little.
I made a ball.
A ball?
I thought as hard as I could.
That's all that I could come up with.
You thought?
You think when I let
this arrow fly...
...I use my head?
Woah.
There.
That's Ego's core.
That ore is thick, Rocket.
I got it covered.
We must hurry.
It will not take Ego
long to find us.
Keep it steady.
We drill into the
center, we kill him!
Captain?
What is it, Kraglin?
Hey, remember that Ayesha chick?
Yeah, why?
- Uhh...
- Oh hell!
Why aren't you firing the laser?
They blew up the generator.
I think I packed
a small detonator.
A detonator is worthless
without explosives.
Well, we've got these.
Is that thing strong enough to kill Ego?
If it is, it'll
cause a chain reaction...
...throughout his
entire nervous system.
Meaning what?
Meaning the entire planet will explode.
We'll have to get out of here fast.
I made the timer.
Go!
He's coming!
Didn't you say you
could make him sleep?
When he wants.
He's too powerful.
I can't!
You have to believe in yourself.
Because I believe in you.
Sleep!
I never thought she'd
be able to do it...
...with as weak and
skinny as she appears to be.
I don't know how
long I can hold him.
The metal's too thick.
For the bomb to work,...
...we actually need
to place it on Ego's core.
And our fat butts ain't
gonna fit through those tiny holes.
Well...
That's a terrible idea.
Which is the only kind
of idea we have left.
Unbelievable.
Rocket, do this.
Rocket, do that.
What a day.
All right, first you flick
this switch, then this switch.
That activates it.
Then you push this button.
Which will give you 5 minutes
to get out of there.
Now, whatever you do...
...don't push this button.
'Cause that will set off the bomb
immediately and we'll all be dead.
Now, repeat back what I just said.
- I am Groot.
- Uh-huh.
- That's right.
- I am Groot.
- No!
No, that's the button that
will kill everyone!
Try again.
- I am Groot.
- Um-hmm.
- Uh-huh.
- I am Groot.
- No!
That's exactly what you just
said, how is that even possible?
Which button is the button
you're supposed to push?
Point to it.
No!
Hey, you're making him nervous!
Shut up and
give me some tape!
Does anybody have
any tape out there?
I wanna put some tape
over the death button.
I don't have any tape.
Let me check.
Yo, Yondu...
...do you have any... ouch!
Do you have any tape?
Gamora?
You have the tape?
Tape!
Ah, nevermind.
Drax?
Do you have any tape?
Yeah, Scotch tape would work.
Then why did you ask me if Scotch tape
would work if you don't have any?
Nobody has any tape!
Not a single person has tape?
Nope.
Did you ask Nebula?
Yes!
Are you sure?
I asked Yondu and she was
sitting right next to him.
I knew you're lying!
You have priceless batteries and
an atomic bomb in your bag.
If anybody's gonna
have tape, it's you!
That's exactly my point!
I have to do everything!
You are wasting
a lot of time here!
We're all gonna die.
Ah, rear thrusters are out again!
We're done for
without that generator!
Guardians.
Perhaps it will
provide you solace...
...that your deaths
are not without purpose.
They will serve as a warning...
...for all of those
tempted to betray us.
Don't screw with the Sovereign.
This is gonna hurt.
Promises, promises.
No!
No! No! No!
We're gonna blow!
Peter!
No!
- Ha ha!
- What?
You look like Mary Poppins.
Is he cool?
Hell yeah, he's cool.
I'm Mary Poppins, y'all!
Mantis!
Look out!
She's just unconscious.
How long 'til the
bomb goes off?
In the unlikely event
that Groot doesn't kill us all...
...about 6 minutes.
Kraglin, we need the
quadrant for an extraction.
T-minus 5 minutes.
Aye, captain.
Somebody's gotta be on
top when Kraglin arrives.
Drax, take Mantis.
Ow! My nipples!
Ahhh!
Gamora!
Peter!
Get over it.
Come now, Peter.
I know this isn't what you want.
What kind of father would I be
to let you make this choice?
Yeah!
Soon, Peter,
we will be all there is.
So stop pissing me off!
We have to get up
to the extraction point.
Go!
I told you...
...I don't want
to do this alone.
You can not deny...
...the purpose the
universe has bestowed upon you.
Everyone, I need you
to stay back, it's not safe...
What is that?
It doesn't need to
be like this, Peter.
Why are you destroying
our chance?
Stop pretending you
aren't what you are.
One in billions.
Trillions. Even more.
What greater meaning
can a life possibly have to offer?
I don't use my head
to fly the arrows, boy!
I use my heart.
You shouldn't have killed my
mom and squished my Walkman.
Groot! Groot, if you can
hear me, hurry up!
I'm not sure how long
Quill can keep him distracted!
Groot, hurry!
Yondu, we're about to blow!
Get to the ship!
Not without Quill!
You need to take care of the twig!
Not without you.
I ain't got nothing right
my whole damn life, rat.
You need to give me this.
A spacesuit and an aero-rig.
I only have one of each.
I...
I am Groot!
What's that?
He says, Welcome to the frickin'
Guardians of the Galaxy.
Only he didn't use frickin'.
Bye, twig.
We're gonna have to have a real
discussion about your language.
Where's Peter?
Rocket, where is he?
Rocket?
Rocket, look at me!
Where is he?
No, I'm not
leaving without him.
I'm sorry.
I can only afford to
lose one friend today.
Kraglin, go!
Wait.
Let's hold back.
Rocket, where's Quill?
Rocket!
Where's Quill?
No, we need to stop it.
We need to stop it.
Stop, listen!
Listen to me.
You are a god.
If you kill me...
...you'll be just
like everybody else.
What's wrong with that?
No!
He may have been your father,
boy, but he wasn't your daddy.
I'm sorry I didn't
do none of it right.
Damn lucky you my boy.
What?
Yondu, what are you doing?
You can't.
Yondu!
No.
No!
Oh no!
I told Gamora...
...how when I was a kid, I used to
pretend David Hasselhoff was my dad.
He is a singer and actor
from Earth, really famous guy.
Earlier, it struck me...
...Yondu didn't have a talking car
but he did have a flying arrow.
He didn't have the beautiful
voice of an angel...
...but he did have
the whistle of one.
Both Yondu and David Hasselhoff
went on kick-ass adventures...
...and hooked up with hot women...
...and fought robots.
I guess David Hasselhoff did kind
of end up being my dad after all.
Only, it was you, Yondu.
I had a pretty cool dad.
What I'm trying to say here is...
...sometimes the thing you're
searching for your whole life...
...it's right there
by your side all along.
You don't even know it.
I am Groot.
He did call you twig.
Nebula.
I was a child like you.
I was concerned with staying
alive until the next day, every day.
And I never considered what
Thanos was doing to you.
I'm trying to make it right.
There are little girls
like you across the universe...
...who are in danger.
You can stay with
us and help them.
I will help them
by killing Thanos.
I don't know if
that's possible.
You will always be my sister.
Pete!
The captain found this
for you in a junker shop,...
...said you'd come
back to the fold someday.
What is it?
It's called a Zune.
It's what everybody's listening
to on Earth nowadays.
It's got 300 songs on it.
300 songs?
Wait.
Rocket grabbed the
pieces and re-assembled it.
But I think Yondu would
want you to have it.
Thanks.
Cap'n.
They came.
What is it?
I sent word to Yondu's old Ravager buddies.
Told them what he did.
It's a Ravager funeral.
Yea! Yes!
He didn't let as down after all, Captain.
No, he did not.
He did not.
Fare thee well, old friend.
Yondu Udonta, I will
see you in the stars.
He didn't chase them away.
No.
Even though he yelled at 'em.
And was always mean.
And he stole batteries
he didn't need.
Well of course not.
What?
It's just...
...some unspoken thing.
It's beautiful.
Yes.
And so are you.
On the inside.
THE GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY
WILL RETURN.
subtitles transcribed by Scram.Cypher
synchronized by Andrian Reid
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org