I remember,
I remember everything.
Captain Webb, are you [??].
Good morning.. good morning
Yes, sir.
When we are finished with you,
you will no longer be David Webb.
I'll be whoever you need me to be, sir.
You can't say [??].
- [ ?? ]
01:01:.18- [ ?? ]
Eventually you're gonna
have to face the fact
you chose right here
to become Jason Bourne.
TSAMANTAS, GREECE
On the Greek-Albanian border.
Vasily, you're up first.
10 on the Serbian!
20 on the Serb!
10 on the Russian!
REYKJAVIK, ICELAND
Christian Dassault made a reservation.
Use SQL to  corrupt their databases...
CIA: CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
LANGLEY, Virginia
NEWSPAPER:
Loss of confidence in the CIA.
Hello, Nate?
Regarding your device,
issued to an agent [???]
assigned to their first project in 1993.
Marked  on our Inventory as destroyed.
It's knocking on our front door.
Downloading "BLACK OPERATIONS"
folder to: USB Drive.
- What's the status?
- Whoever it is, is just sitting there, idle.
Move.
- SYSTEM BREACH
- They found a back-door.
- We need a reverse shell [???]
- I'm not clocking at the source.
Okay, we have a major breach
of our classified main-frame.
Drop everything you're doing
and get on it, right now.
- We're sending you the shell.
- Got it.
- Oompa loompa camp [ ???]
- Cut the power to the building.
- Get into that power grid, now.
- Yes, sir.
Kickass Torrents (KAT.cr)
currently off-line. /s
WARNING:
EXTERNAL TRACE DETECTED.
- I've got the power to the building.
- Stand by.
- Shut it down.
- Copy that. Shutting it down.
You still online?
McLEAN, Virginia
- Dewey.
(CIA Director Robert Dewey)
We've just been hacked.
- How badly?
- Could be worse than Snowden.
- Is there any attribution?
- We're working on it.
Police say it must be someone with
a deep knowledge of our systems.
This could affect Rio Olympics [???]
and Iron Hand.
I want a briefing.
In my conference room.
In one hour.
DEEP DREAM CORPORATION.
SILICON VALLLEY, California
- According to the reports
- Yes.
- Did you get confirmation?
- Yeah, it was a hack.
- So are we exposed?
- We don't know yet. We're checking.
George, are we ready for launch?
Helen, you know the Dir of National Intelligence.
( Director NI Edwin Russell )
I believe [ ??? ], sir.
Have you got a name for us?
Our hacker was a former Agency operative.
Believed to be working with
Christian Dassault,  and ...
previously linked to ... Jason Bourne.
Bourne?
- Jesus Christ.
- Ain't he dead yet [ ???].
Black ops funds, from TreadStone,
all the way to IronHand.
IronHand?
That's not even operational yet,
for Christ's sakes.
Where is Nicky Parsons right now?
On the move.
She left [ ??? ] traveling with a group of
Feels like a meeting to me.
How are you going to handle it?
We cut the head off this thing.
Sir. I'd like to be point
on this operation.
- You're not indoctrinated for this material.
- I'm already into it.
I embedded malware into Parsons' download.
When those files are opened, I can trace them.
I'd be in.
I'll deliver Parsons, the files,
And if he's out there,
I'll give you Bourne, too.
I appreciate you enthusiasm.
but,
- Do not push your personal agenda, to the DEI again.
- Understood.
Alright, I think you can help me.
I'm going to give you full
operational control on this.
And I'll assure that you have
acces to any relevant teams
and resources. And I want to
know every move you make.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much sir.
ROME, ITALY
- Yeah.
- I need your help now.
I'm not finished here.
Jason Bourne is in play.
- Where?
- Athens, closer to Carmen [ ???], Rome.
Cuncer?
ATHENS, GREECE
SYNTAGMA SQUARE KIOSK
1 hour.
We got a hit from a CC TV feed ,
Parsons boarded a bus half-hour ago.
west across Athens.
I got two local teams en route.
- Any sign of Bourne?
- Not so far.
He's involved in this somehow,
I can feel it.
- 16:14.960- [ ?? ].
- 16:15.01 [ ??? ].
Copy that.
Where are we?
Carson's assett has just
arrived at Syntayma Square.
There's a demonstration in front
of the Natalia[??] building.
I think she will use it as cover.
Before [ ???] at the square,
We come in for Parsons, pair up at Parliament,
and any possible run-in with Bourne.
Copy that, sir.
Sir, the asset has landed.
- Alpha Team arriving now.
- Copy that.
- I have the Alpha Team feed.
- Pull them up.
Athens police is reporting tactical
teams moving on the demonstrators.
- Isolate all social media posts from the Square.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Rewind Alpha One's feed.
- Yes, ma'am. Twenty seconds.
- What's wrong?
- I hacked the Agency.
- 19:11.75 [???].
I hacked all the black ops files,
including the Armani. [ ???]
Who you doing this for?
Stop.
Two seconds more. Long hair.
Enhance.
Find her.
- I told you, Dassault is going to get you killed.
- We don't have a choice, Jason.
They started again, a new program,
Iron Hand. It's even worse than before.
- What's that got to do with me?
- Because it matters.  It matters.
To me, it doesn't.
All that matters is staying alive.
You get off the grid, survive.
I don't believe that,
and neither do you.
Look at yourself.
Look at what you're doing.
You can't live like
this for much longer.
Jason, I came here
because I found something.
I found you father's
[???] Treadstone files.
He was an analyst.
He wasn't in operations.
- He wasn't near any of that stuff.
- I'm telling you what I saw.
It looks like he was involved directly.
- And there's more. More about you.
- What do you mean?
Before you joined the program,
they were watching you.
Watching me?
You tortured yourself
for a long time now, Jason.
And you don't know the truth
about what they did to you.
You need to read those files.
Move
Number One has eyes on two targets.
One female, one male.
- Identify the male.
- Copy that.
You gotta get out of here before
they [???] this part of the city.
Head north.
Meet me at the statue of Athena.
- I'll take them away from you.
- Hey, stop!
That's him.
Now.
[ ???] Bourne. .
- Cleared to engage the target.
- Copy.
Sir, Alpha Team's comms are down.
We've lost Support Team No. 3 [ ???]
- 22:55.880 [ ??? ].
- 22:58.790 [ ??? ]
Sir, rioting is starting to break out and
Athens' declaring State of Emergency.
We got her.
Second team put her in a box.
Suspect last reported seen on a police
motorcycle. He's heading north.
- Where the hell is the asset?
- Two minutes out, sir.
- Carson is at the statue of Athena.
- Copy that.
- [???] Team is down.
- Sir, the asset is arriving on scene.
Philip the gosh down, give
me direct comm to the Asset.
- 26:57.720 [???].
- I need eyes overhead.
- Remit the satellite's feed.
They're actually [??].
Twelve satellites available.
- 27:20.320 [ ???].
- Yes, sir.
The [??? ] feed is online.
- 27:38.40 [ ???] barrier.
- The target is [???] will be forced to turn left.
Another barricade at 200 meters.
Target turning left.
Bourne is heading for the alley.
Left at top of the hill.
Here, got out. Where is he going?
Found a way out. 200 meters
to your left. 19 Salomon.
Get to the roof.  Bourne
will pass by your line-of-sight.
I see soldiers coming.
- 29:12.000 [??? ].
- 29:12.2000 [??? ].
- Copy that.
Approaching the targets
at Harmonien and 50th.
- 29:47.040 [ ???].
Coming at you in 55 seconds.
Copy that.
- 30:18.960 [???] .
Targets with you within 15 seconds.
5 seconds.
- Contact.
Stay low!
One shot.
Hold on.
Where's Bourne?
Police at the top have spotted three bodies
on the roof that the asset attacked.
Team's on it's way.
Nicky.
Don't move.
The tactical team has entered the building.
- Asset, you need to get out of there.
- Negative
We don't even know
if Bourne is still alive.
So [???] is gone.
This is Director Dewey, 27 is gone.
Hold on, Nicky.
I'm going to get you to cover.
Don't, no ..
I'm coming..
Location was from this office, sir.
If he was working with Nikky Parsons,
he will have suggested Bourne.
And let me know if you
get a hit on that malware.
Sir, can I clarify one thing.
- 34:20.040  [??? ]
Plus he has to think Bourne.
- 34:22.280 [ ???]
His behavior or will-power?
And suggests a connectioin.
The last time Bourne came back he
exposed the Black Briar program.
He compromised accurate operations.
And the assets in Syria, under cover.
He was captured, and tortured. And
took near a damn year to get him out.
So you think that's why Bourne
wanted the files. To go public again?
I have no idea why he came back.
But whatever he's doing,
he wants to destroy us.
I can't let that happen.
So please give me a call,
soon as you hear anything.
Yes, sir.
- Treadstone  >>>  IronHand
- Richard Webb Involved. JB Under surveillance.
And now the founder and chairman
of DEEP DREAM .. Aaron Kalloor.
Ahh, you know why you're here.
We will be unveiling a new platform.
We think it is a bold new step, to
allow us to serve our community better.
We're turning in right now to
trascend national boundaries, and
I think we're at 1.5 Billion users.
You know we have an ecosystem of hundreds
of thousands of apps at this point.
And what this new platform
will do is integrate
User's data and preferences,
And use that information,
to enrich and tailor-make
Each unique user experience,
in a way that is frankly
Unprecedented.
Now, I can see some journalists' brains
twitching, ready to ask about privacy.
This is a concern of many
people, and so it should be.
This is something that matters
to us, and let me just say
I understand, nobody wants to feel
like they're being watched
So let just tell you, when you come to
DEEP DREAM, when you use our service.
No-one will be watching you.
- Enjoy your meal?
- Thank you.
Congratulations,
I hear you stock-holders were very
happy with the new platform.
And I heard you got hacked.
You were [ ???].
This changes everything.
There's too much risk.
- I'm out.
- Hey,
You are an extra-ordinarily gifted
and perceptive young man.
And you agreed to help us it's because
you understood the very grave threats,
Do you have idea the shit-storm on our
hands if this arrangement goes public?
I agreed to it, and you were more ..
Our enemies have become
much more sophisticated.
Gathering meta-data is
no longer adequate.
We need a back-door into
your new platform, in a way
- 40:28.680 [ ???].
- When that's not enough, you want something new.
You .. you don't get it, do you?
Privacy is,, is, freedom.
I believe that's something you
should think about defending.
You little prick, you didn't believe
in privacy or freedom when
When you started.
I've turned you into a billionaire.
I have paid you back many,
many, many times over.
And I was not comfortable
with any of this.  I'm out.
- I'm done selling out our customers.
- Yet you would sell out your country.
The truth is, we would't be having
this conversation if you didn't feel
Personally at risk.
You talk about a free internet, you tell
yourself you're saving the world,
All you're doing is making it a much more
dangerous place. And you sure as hell
Making this country much
more difficult to defend.
And you're sure as
hell accountable for that.
BERLIN, GERMANY
Oi, everything on the table.
Open it.
Sure.
Bourne's surfaced.
- In Berlin.
Get the Berlin team out.
- Where is she?
- She is dead.
She knew the risks. I owed her.
She made her choice.
You exploited her.
- Blue Team is mobile.
- Who do we have in the location?
- We can try to find Christian Dassault .
- Can we put a bit more?
Not on the app. I'm activating CC TV now.
So I've been thinking,
What if we go this wrong?
What if they still come for us?
What if it's something else?
You don't have any idea
of who you're dealing with.
We should work together more.
We both have the same thing right.
You expose the [???].
We both want to take down
the [??] that control society.
I'm not on your side.
CC TV is online.
- He's on a computer.
- Yes,
He puts those files online,
Operations will be compromised,
and people will die.
Yes, sir.
Is this what you've
done for your files?
These programs have
to be exposed. [???]
Be glad I know you well.
TREADSTONE PROGRAM
A proposal by Richard Web
We need that computer.
- Hasn't found the malware.
I can use it to delete the files.
REMOTE STATUS -  ACCESS CONFIRMED
LINK COMPLETE.
- Where's that team?
- Five minutes out, sir.
Listen to me Dave, I've done something.
Something,
It came with a cost.
One day, you'll understand why.
I got to get back to Washington.
I love you, son.
They're fighting, sir.
One more firewall.
Files deleted, sir.
Call it.
Bourne, my name is Heather Lee.
I'm not in charge here.
I wasn't here when you were missing.
I can see you're going through
the old Treadstone files.
Are you tracing you history?
I know you're looking for something.
Let me know if you find it.
Give me that phone.
Yes, sir.
Jason, this is Robert Dewey.
Do you remember me?
- Jason, your Dad was a patriot.
He could see the threats
facing Americans in [???].
Chose to serve his country across
Balance it, Eddie.
Giving up
But to see you on the Agency.
- 52:34 [???].
I'm here to stop it now.
TEAM ARRIVING.
You HAVE 2 MINUTES.
We lost him, sir.
Malcom Smith, contract-only,
based out of London
Ran all of Tradestone's surveillance in
the late 90's, when Bourne was recruited.
- Is he still active?
- He's private security now.
Contact the asset and tell him who we
want drowned and murderd in 6 hours.
I'd be ... in Stickson.
He'd sick, won't he?
The'res [???] for catching Bourne.
Instead of killing him.
Alright, let's hear it.
Bourne's been off the
grid for a long time.
He's been hiding in the shadows.
He's seen things.
He knows things that could help us.
Bring him back in, is the smart move.
And how are we going to do that?
I'll [???] and Bourne with the program.
He concluded Bourne is
still a patriot at heart.
Put me back into the program, and [???].
- And where do you suggest that?
- I'll watch Bourne [???].
Desperately, but our
intests passed, and ...
I can be sort a tech [???].
If I can get face to face with him.
I think I can bring him back in.
One time.  And if it fails ..
You don't have to ..
Well, it makes sense to me.
What do you think, Bob?
Let's give it a shot.
Alright, do it.
Bring Bourne in,
We'll tie it off.
- This ends now.
- Thank you, sir.
- Sir, I'm sorry.
- No, no, don't.
Better get some sleep, kid.
You don't want 24-hours
without looking.
Yes, sir.
It's taking too long, it still shouldn't
be this buggy this close to launch.
Would be so buggy if
James hadn't taken out [???].
- It's the parametes, it's going to have to go.
- Okay, then we'll have to change it back.
- Pull the car up?
- Absolutely.
I just don't think we
want the entire piece.
Mr. Kalloor,
Mr. Kalloor, I'm from
the Dept of Justice.
- I'm hereby serving you with the enclosed claim,
- Really, you have to do this in public?
And the Deep Dream Corporation,
for violation of the Sherman Act.
This claim requires you to preserve all
corporate and personal financial records.
Pending an osmosis to be
filed in Federal Court.
Good day.
- This is Dewey.
- Aaron, it's a message.
And maybe we should think about what
we're doing before it gets any worse.
So, you think if we give him
what he wants, it will end there.
I'm just saying that
maybe we should listen.
I want you to pull up all the records
of all the meetings Paul had with me.
All the records?
- Even the off-the-books discussions?
- Especially, those.
I'm going to Vegas,
I need an insurance policy.
- Yeah.
- Are you in London?- Yes.
Who're you sending now?
She serves a purpose.
- I work alone.
- Not this time.
Don't make this personal.
Bourne betrayed us.
It's always been personal.
[??? ] when you're ready.
-Yeah?
- I need an assurance.
That I have your support.
[???], what do you have?
Kalloor,
is planning something,
for Vegas.
LONDON, UNITED KINGDOM
- Yes?
- This is Jason Bourne.
- I need to talk.
- What about?
- I don't work for the Agency anymore.
- Aubrey Plaza [???], 15 minutes.
Bourne just called Smith.
They're meeting at Aubrey Plaza,
15 minutes.
- 1:01:47.720 [???].
As soon as we get eyes on Bourne,
I'll approach him.
Whatever you say, contain him.
I don't want the Brits falling
all over this asking questions.
Aye, sir.
Tracking device.
You'll hold on the south
side of the bridge.
I'll contact you if I need you.
Sure,
You're the boss, right?
- Subject is on the move.
- I can [???] now.
Alpha Team take [???].
Bravo Team, pull up to the subject from
behind. You keep your eyes open for Bourne.
Bravo Team, tailing subjects.
- Let's go. At 200 meters, set your mark.
- Copy that.
Comms check, second channel.
Do you copy?
- I have you. Where are you now?
- Heading towards the [???].
No sign of Bourne.
- Subject is turning east.
- Into an alley.
Alpha Team, that alley leads to a foot-trail,
which will lead him to you.
Copy that.
Bravo Team is down. The second update from now.
Copy that, Smith?
Yes.
Programs team, why aren't
you moving? What's going on?
Programs team, do you copy?
What's happening, where is Bravo?
The comms down for Bravo.
Akpha Team do you have
eyes on the subject?
Alpha Team, sitprep?
- Alpha Team report.
- What's happening Heather?
- Alpha Team isn't responding.
- Bravo?
What's going on?
You lost both teams [??] this
operation, Heather. That's Bourne.
Bring out the asset.
- Sir, I need more time.
- We have no time.
- Are you going to give that order or not?
- Sir, please.
If you're too naive to see the trees,
there's no bringing in Bourne.
He has to be put down.
And you obviously cannot do what has to
be done. I'm taking operational control.
- 1:06:03.00 [???].
- [???], you have green light on Bourne.
- Copy that. I'm on my way.
Asset are you on the move?
Asset, your tracking device
says you're stationary.
Are you moving?
Heaher stay off this channel,
let him do his job.
Left here. Get up to
Aubrey Plaza, fast.
In position.
Locked in.
- What's that alarm?
- What's that noise?
- Lots of fire alarms.
- That's Bourne.
- 1:08:04.94 [??? ].
- I can't see you, you can't protect me.
- I need you to stay where you are, Smith.
We still have [???] on the side of me.
I'm on him.
Can you see me?  In the crowd?
Stay where you are, Smith.
You know why he's here.
He wants the address.
We've lost the signal.
I got to get out of here.
- What the hell's going on?
- Bourne's got Smith.
Go after them.
I'll come along and come them off.
Smith, I know you're with Bourne.
Find a way to let us know where you are.
- Why are you taking me in here?
- 5th avenue, at the Plaza.
- Take it easy.
- Jason Webb ..
- 1:09:58.90 [???], Beirut.
He was my father,
he started Treadstone.
He hired you to put me under survellaince.
Why?, Why did he hire you?
Or so you think, [???].
- What do you want us to do?
- Work you way down to Canal.
I'll circle around and meet you there.
You followed my to Beirut.
The last time I saw my father.
Why would he have you follow me?
It doesn't make any sense, why?
Don't give him a goddamn thing.
Why?
- 1:10:41.74 [???].
I can hear that.
I went there to tell you that
Treadstone had approached me.
But if it was [???],
why didn't he say anything.
I've done something.
something ..
that came at a cost.
That was the day he was killed.
They said he was killed by terrorists.
He wasn't killed by terrorists, was he?
Think about your family's safety, Smith.
and keep your mouth shut.
The nest bullet is in your head.
Why was he killed?
Why?
Jesus, just because of you.
Your father,
he wasn't in operations.
He didn't really choose you,
but when he found out
He threatened to expose the program.
He didn't want you turned into a killer.
Who killed him?
- Who killed him?
- Don't do it.
Where is he?
He's almost there.
We're going to stop this now.
He went off the roof.
Tried to run. [???].
He recognized me.
I got to make sure it's finished. [???].
Step aside please, step aside.
- He's gone. - Oh, shit.
- I'm going after him.
I'll work my way down the Canal.
No. You're done in London.
- What're you talking about?
- There's another place [???].
Now he knows [???].
- 1:13:23.240 [???],
Opportunity for something else.
- This isn't about revenge.
- Yes, it is.
And it won't be done
till one of us is dead.
Get to the airport.
We have a problem with IronHand.
Copy that.
- Give me a sitrep. [ situation report ]
- We've got nothing.
Keep looking.
Drive.
It wasn't supposed to go like this, I wanted to talk.
- Where's Dewey going?
He's going to Vegas to speak with
Aaron Kalloor to sign the [???].
Convention. The Agency recruits there every year.
What's Iron Hand?
Dewey's new black ops program.
Full-sprectrum surveillance.
[???] everyone, all the time.
Dewey needs Kalloor's
co-operation for the online
Let me out.
I can help you get there.
Why would you do that?
You and I have different reasons,
but we both want  to [???].
Here, take this.
I'll see you in Vegas.
LAS VEGAS, NEVADA
We're getting close hit on a
fix on Shahadi's shooter [???]
- 1:15:51.34 [???].
We created bank accounts, travel
documents, emails, phone records.
- It'll look like a lone wolf.
- Any physical evidence?
[???] the gun, and rub
his fingerprints on it.
Russell doesn't need to know about this.
(Director NI Edwin Russell)
I understand sir.
Any news on Bourne. [???]
Nothing.
He was always going to come for me.
Well, if it happens we'll deal with it.
Toothpaste and little shampoos Police.
- 1:17:00.16  [???], Mr. Michaels.
Business.
- Welcome home, sir.
- Thank you,
Sir, we have a secure room for you,
right upstairs.
- Enjoy your stay.
- Thank you.
Hi, welcome to the REO Expo.
- I have arranged [???] check-in.
- Okay.
We have you in a lovely sky-suite,
No 2016.
- Enjoy your stay.
- Thank you.
- Find Lee, tell her I want to see her
before we go upstairs.- Yes, sir.
I'm going to need men posted
backstate as well as the auditorium.
DIRECTOR WANTS TO SEE YOU.
- You all set?
- Checking departure route now.
- You don't have much time.
- They won't know where it came from.
I'll have enough time.
After you take care of Kalloor,
I'll be standing left-hand beside,
You put a bullet in him, it's better,
auditorium too. [???]
Copy that.
Lee, the Director wants
a word with you, upstairs.
Of course.
LEFT POCKET FOR DEWEY
Heather, come here. I brought you in,
strong supporter,
That's why I didn't know what to do
with you.  I suppose I could just, ah,
Write it  off to your .. learning curve.
I appreciate that.
I least you can now see
that you didn't have [???].
Or Bourne, [???].
I'll deal with him, do you understand?
Of course.
I agree completely.
When you're on stage, [???].
- I'll be ready, sir.
- Okay, let's do this.
- Aaron.
- Robert.
You never met.
Yeah, we.. we went to Stanford together.
- How are you enjoying life at the Agency?
- Challenging, but fulfilling.
[???], still your interest over there?
My principles are just fine, thanks.
Gentlemen, we're ready for you.
Follow me, please.
- I'm going to enjoy this.
- So am I.
Oh, hi. How's everyone doing tonight?
Welcome.
Welcome to tonight's EXOCON Symposium.
We are so lucky to have four
fantastic guests this evening.
CIA Director, Robert Dewey
Dear friend of mine,
and old friend of EXOCON,
CEO social media giant DEEP
DREAM, Aaron Kalloor is here.
[???], Personal rights vs Public safety.
This is the great question of our time.
And the choices we make about
this will determine our future.
So let's just dive right in, okay?
Come on, you guys!
Sir, you have an incoming message.
- High priority.
Alright guys, I'm going
to have to take this.
- 1:26:45.34 [???].
It appears Director Dewey settled
down momentarily, and I mean
I'm told that it shouldn't
be too much longer,
But we have a ton of stuff to get into
tonight, so I'm going to start anyway.
Craig, can I say a few words?
- Excuse me?
- Can I get normal?
Oh, sure man. By all means.
Ladies and gentlemen, Aaron Kalloor.
Thank you, thanks a lot.
Before the Director comes
out to join us, I just
just wanted to share a
few words with you guys.
A long time ago, I,
I had this idea.
Copy that.
Facial recognition got a hit on [???]
He was [???] in Vegas like two hours ago.
- 1:28:02.39  [???]
Someone issued an Agency
security clearance on his passport.
... people from aroun the world
started using our service,
SOMETHING's WRONG
Come on stay, take care of
Kalloor, and the girl.
Copy.
What I want to say is, you know,
All this success has come at a cost,
There's a cancer at the heart
of DEEP DREAM,
A guilty secret,
and now, ah, now I have to share it
with all of you guys, so
Just have to take a [???]. Take
out Kalloor and the girl right now.
I, took money to ah, start my company
and made a bargain with
the guy in the dark suit.
And now, he's come back to take my soul.
Sir, we got to go.
Get the cars ready.
Get the cars ready, right now!
No. Take me to the suite.
Sir, we got to get you out of
here. Bourne is on the loose.
- You heard me.
Take me to the suite. - Yes, sir.
Take to the suite. Take him upstairs.
Get him upstairs. Right now, right now.
Up to the suite.
Vasquez, sitrep. [SITUATION REPORT].
Vasquez.  Vasquez, come in.
Hey!
Okay, we got him, sir.
We've ID'd the sniper.
- Shit!
- We're circulating his photo now.
- What about Bourne?
- Hang on.
Okay, Bourne is just leaving the west
stairs corridor heading for the lobby.
Copy that.  Stay on Bourne.
- Horton.
- We're still looking for Bourne.
They've ID'd the IAD asset.
Go back to the first floor, and wait for
further instructions.- Yes, sir, copy that.
Stop right there.
Put it down.
Move, move, move.
[???] to the northeast elevator, now.
Bourne is on his way up to you.
You took a long time to get here, Jason.
I know about Beirut.
I know what you did.
It all ends tonight.
It'll a lot easier if do it right away.
You didn't come here for revenge.
You came because it's time to come in.
Your father created the program. Didn't
have what it takes to make it work.
And you did.
You always did.
- That's why you volunteered. - I volunteered
because I thought terrorists killed Lou.
- I volunteered because of a lie.
- No. You volunteered becasue of who you are.
You volunteered because
you are Jason Bourne.
And, not, David Webb.
32 kills, Jason.
[???]
people all across this country,
Are safer because of what you did.
- 1:34:53.80  [???].
I tried to find another way.
And how's that working out for you?
You didn't any peace.
NOt till you admit to
yourself, who you really are.
It's sudden death here, Jason.
Stop doing it.
- So?
- I can't.
Not for you.
You were never here.
You don't have to walk.
This can stop now.
You have a choice.
[???] All units, suspect stole
a 2015 black dodge charger.
This is Air One, be advised,
suspects vehicles have crashed
On the southeast entrance of the Riviera.
We have unkown a suspect heading
to the storm-drain of the Riviera.
You're a traitor.
You've always been a traitor.
- 1:45:50.64 [???].
[???] work with the authorities,
to find out who's responsible.
- 1:47:35.92 [???] .
Thank you.
Sir.
I wanted to say I'm sorry, sir.
About Vegas.
I read that Dewey's tactics
were .. unwise.
Unwise.
We're still trying to come up with a
narrative to explain what happened.
That son-of-a-bitch put
a spotlight on our heads.
All of us.
- 1:48:44.79 yet [???].
I know her. [???]
There's still moves we can make.
Tell me.
Dewey's problem was that
he clung on to the past.
People are  [???]  the future.
These are my people.
I know what to do over.
and what do you want?
When you appoint someone head of your
Agency, you're going to need someone,
Working [???].
Someone ...
An hour, [???].
By you, [???]
- 1:49:28.05- [???].
What about Bourne?
You still think you can bring him in?
I have his trust.
After all we've been through.
I'll bring him in.
I'm certain of it.
What if you can't?
Then ..
He'll have to be put down.
That's an interesting proposal.
You can pull over here.
Of course if you decide
you don't need me,
That's not a problem.
There are many other agencies
that want what I know.
I brought you something.
It's a cast from you father's
star, on Memorial Wall.
I'm sorry for what happened to you.
I [???]. The people who did that, are gone.
And,
Things are changing in the Agency.
What is it you want?
I know you've always been a patriot.
And what happens to this
country, matters to you.
We need you to help us protect it.
Come back in.
And we'll work together.
Let me think about it.
How will I find you.
You still think you can bring him in?
I have his trust.
After all we've been through.
I'll bring him in.
I'm certain of it.
And if you can't?
Then,
He'll have to be put down.
I"M NOT SURPRISED, MOTHERFUCKERS!