Play one of the best new FPS shooters,
search Steam for PROJECT WARLOCK
- Hey, boy!
- What?
I found something. Come and see.
Jumanji.
A game on the board. Who is playing such games?
Makoto77
JUMANJI: WELCOME TO THE JUNGLE
Okay, guard up! Uppercut!
You're dead. Attack, attack, counterattack and down with it!
You got it?
Yes.
YOU LOSE
Freak house in 20 minutes.
Benjamin Franklin; And it was this sense of national exclusivity
which fueled the spread of the wild fire of the Westward expansion.
Spencer, honey.
Mom,what we say about knock to the door.
I'm late at work, go to your father after school?
- Yes probably.
- Do not forget the equipment.
And you should know that world is a terifying  place.
I love you more than my life. See you on Sunday.
okay.
- Goodbye, Mom.
- Eat something before you leave.
I can not, I'm going to meet Spencer.
- Spencer Gilman?
- Yes, Spencer Gilman.
He meditated and helped me get good grades.
I'm glad to hear that. So Spencer Gilpen.
- Do you have good grades?
- Yes mother, that's why I ask for help.
- I do not want you out of the team.
- I will not get out of the team.
It'll be okay.
Nice.
Yes.
Bethany Walker. I just woke up. Good morning.
- Hello.
- Hello, Fridge.
Why do you wear a rain cloak?
- What do you want to say?
- It does not rain.
It might rain.
What the hell are you?
Let's finish this! I feel very uncomfortable.
Here you go.
- Have you checked everything?
- Yes, I checked.
I gave it a start and an end.
And something comprised.
I would have done it if I had time.
Yeah, that's not a big deal.
I thought it fun to help you do your homework, but...
I do not know what you're doing on the weekend, maybe...
This weekend, yes...
- Good, Fridge!
- Hi.
Do you want me to take you with the car?
- I'm going with her.
- It's better for me.
I have my own program. I'll see you later, "Fridge."
Sorry.
Hello, face.
I do not care. He's not the best friend of his childhood.
What you say?
Nothing, sir.
- This guy's really weird.
- The poor man.
It was terrible what happened to them.
I was referring to the kids.
What are you doing here?
I was talking to my friend earlier.
- You have to be more careful, do you hear?
- Yes, Mr. Rick.
- I understand.
- This world swallows babies like you.
It's been two hours after I posted and did not comment.
Because he does not like it. Did you see her?
Yes, huge. I do not know what his problem is.
Thanks. And I do not always post, just enough to be relevant.
- But that's funny.
- Is this a strange person behind you?
- Hi.
Bethany, did you call during the test?
Yeah, but I finished my test.
Do you realize that others have not finished yet?
- And?
- Sorry.
Do you know there are other people in the world?
I got something done right now.
I'm not happy either.
I have a crisis, and Lucinda asserts me as a woman.
Maybe you should do it too.
- Shut the phone!
- Okay no problem.
- Bethany, close it now.
- Two more minutes and I'm done.
That means detention.
Okay, keep your hands up. Come on!
- Bethany, you're late.
- I am sorry!
I heard he was separated from the footballer.
Maybe that's your chance.
We'll practice catching and throwing. Take your partner and a ball.
Pry yourself!
Martha, you can not play alone.
Find a partner. Grãbeºte up!
I'm not ok.
Good.
You have to participate, just like everyone else.
- If not, why are you here?
- It's a compulsory hour.
- Martha ..
- It's useless.
The time of the sport would not go to Princeton,
And are not obsessed with throwing the ball and leaps, and touchdowns!
Okay, it's wrong, but...
It is a beneficial physical activity.
And it benefits others.
And if you try, you may like it.
Is that what we are doing here? We are having fun?
Here we are at school, we need to learn important things.
- Good.
- We do not have much time in our lives.
And I do not want to waste it by being a teacher of physical education.
- It sounds crappy.
- Yes.
That means detention.
- Mommy.
- Smack.
Spencer Gilpen.
Take a seat, Spencer.
Mrs. Mathers.
And with that feeling of national exceptions,
which fueled the spread of the wild fire of the Westward expansion.
Is he familiar, Mr. Gilpen?
Not.
It was the last line of Anthony's thesis on Westward expansion.
And coincidence, that's your last line
to the thesis on Westward's expansion last year.
Interesting.
- Yes?
- That's what I think.
What were the chances?
Very small.
Yes, you used the same metaphor.
The spread of wild fire in the Boston Tea Party thesis,
Battle at Gettysburg and Suffocation Movement.
- It's so hot in this room.
- Anthony.
I know you have to pass the class, but not that way.
- I will not tolerate cheating.
- Cheating?
- I did not cheat.
- It's my fault.
I did it to him.
Did you make him ask you to write his thesis?
Yes.
- I am sorry.
- Not.
I'll be kicked out of the team.
Yes, but you could expel me.
Not only do you live dangerously.
- Are I living dangerously?
- Yes.
It's the most dangerous thing I've ever done in my life.
And now look at me. Accept the consequences.
What a fun group.
Welcome to detention.
- Yes, Spencer?
- I just want to apologize.
- Thank you.
- Bentley director, I just called.
Bethany, you're here for a reason.
That's what you need to think about.
Who are you at this moment?
And who you want to be.
You have only one life, decide how you live.
Fortunately, there is no better place than detention to reflect.
Let's go.
We will turn this place into a new computer center.
But before doing so, it must be cleaned.
All of these old magazines will be recycled.
But they must be prepared before they are sent.
He must remove all the staples.
If you do not finish today, tomorrow is one day.
- But tomorrow is Saturday.
- Because I do not want to..
Yes, I do not think it will work.
It's correct.
I suggest you get started.
Choose your weapons.
Why is there a bowling ball here?
Really? No signal? Can it be more than that?
Are you helping us or are you too beautiful?
I'm too beautiful.
I followed the discussion with the Web Coach.
Not in a weird way.
We were in the same class with you.
I think you said intelligent things about the sports hour.
And about other topics.
Thanks.
Yes.
What is this?
- I do not know.
- Is that kind of old Nintendo?
I do not believe.
I do not recognize him.
A game for those who are looking to find
a way to leave the world.
Welcome to JUMANJI
Jumanji.
Staples.
- Jumanji, what does that mean?
- I do not know, I did not hear about him.
SELECT CHARACTER
- Which one to choose?
- I do not know, I do not think it matters.
Jefferson "Seaplane" McDonough. Pilot and bastard.
- That does not work.
- Okay, try another one.
Franklin "Mouse" Finbar.
Sounds funny.
He's a zoologist.
- Choose yourself too.
- Good.
Doctor Smolder Bravestone.
- Bethany, do you play?
- Good.
I'll choose Shelly Oberon.
Sexy genius.
- Well, staples, it's your turn.
- No, thank you.
Just a minute. It will be fun.
He does not like having fun.
Good.
May.
It's the most unconvincing thing I've ever done.
I doubt very much.
Welcome to Jumanji.
What happens?
I think it's a short circuit.
Disconnect the cable!
- What happens? What about your hands?
- What's wrong with you?
I do not know.
Dear good!
What the hell? Not!
Friends! It does not sound like my voice.
Where is my hair?
What the hell?
Lord!
Very bad.
- Who are you?
- Yeah, who are you?
Who is she?
Who are you?
Good. What the hell...
- God!
- Get out of me!
What's my voice?
- Get out of me.
- Where am I?
Get!
What happened...
with the rest of me? What do I have in the crap?
- What is this?
- God.
Fridge?
Yes, who are you?
I'm Spencer.
What the? You're fuckin '! What happens?
- I think we're in the game.
- Sorry?
- What are you talking about?
- Somehow...
I do not know how... We were absorbed into the game.
And we become the avatar we choose.
It's me, Spencer. But I look and talk to Dr. Smolder Bravestone.
You want to tell me you're Spencer?
Yes Yes. That's right. Fridge, I'm Spencer.
You are Finbar Mouse. Write on your vest.
And...
- Martha? You are Ruby Roundhouse.
- Yes.
Bethany, you're Professor Shelly Oberon.
Only Shelly's Sheldon abridged.
- What are you talking about?
- God, he's right.
- And are you Spencer? You?
- Yes. Believe me, my friends.
I'm Spencer.
Yeah, it's Spencer.
That means I...
Wait.
Not!
I'm a middle-aged fat man.
I have a tattoo. My mom told me that it kills me if I do.
I have one too.
Sometimes.
Stay here, where's my cell phone?
Why do I wear this jungle suit?
It's kinda little and a little tight.
Looks like a dwarf of the garden. Where's my cell phone?
- Who cares?
- We're in someone else's body.
It's not something your cell phone is.
Really? Is not the right time to call someone?
Or to give an SMS? Or change your status to "Prins in Game"?
I do not have Claritin to me either.
And I'm almost allergic to everything.
Do you have any allergies, Spencer?
I miss a part of my body.
It can not be possible.
Maybe we're all in a coma.
Together? Are we all in coma together?
It's the best explanation.
Lord!
Lord. Better run and save him.
I will not go in there. Come in.
I do not go anywhere, I have a backpack.
Everyone knows they do not get into the water with a backpack.
- What the?
- Bethany.
Are you okay?
It's very intense.
I can not leave this place.
- What happened to you?
- I just hated a rhino.
Then I fell from 1000 meters from the sky.
- Yeah, that's what it looks like.
- It was a hippopotamus.
They are short-distance rapists and have a force of 8100 newtons.
How do I know that?
- You're a zoologist.
- What the?
- I'm fat, right?
- I'm afraid yes.
Why do you agree with that? I mean, it fell...
- From the sky.
- Friends?
Bethany, get up!
Come on, come on, come on.
Doctor Bravestone. Welcome to Jumanji.
Do not sit there, climb up.
Come on, come on!
Doctor Bravestone.
Famous archaeologist and international explorer.
Known on 7 continents for heroic deeds.
- Belt?
- I can not tell you what I'm honored...
to meet you in the end.
I'm not ashamed to say that you are even more beautiful in reality.
- Thank you.
- Who are you?
Nigel Vilengsly, your servant, Ruby Roundhouse, the killer of men.
Welcome to Jumanji.
We're just waiting for your arrival.
Jumanji is in great danger.
We hold four of you to lift the curse.
- Curse?
- What a curse?
Scuzaþi me. Did you see my cellphone somehow?
Professor Sheldon Oberon. Welcome to Jumanji.
Nigel Vilengsly is your servant.
We're just waiting for your arrival.
- Those with him?
- I think it's a NPC.
- What the? Tell me about it.
- A naughty character.
It's part of the game. So whatever we ask him...
only a few responses are scheduled.
Okay, I'm clear.
Franklin Mouse Finbar. Welcome to Jumanji.
Moose, not Mouse.
No, sir. I'm pretty sure it's Mouse.
- Mouse?
- A nickname for your stature.
And adorable behavior. I knew you'd come.
Doctor Bravestone does not go anywhere without his dear assistants.
Assistants?
Since Dr. Bravestone has saved you from the Peruvian jungle
You have never abandoned him.
- That's right.
- Let's go back to the curse.
I wrote everything in the letter sent, Doctor Bravestone.
Maybe you should read it out loud.
I do not have a letter...
OK.
Doctor Bravestone, I am writing to you about the desperate situation in Jumanji.
We need your help right away.
Friends, what's going on?
- What my rifle is going on?
- I think it's a trailer.
Many games have trailers to support the background story.
My name is Nigel Vilengsly. Travel guide in Jumanji.
I was hired by your former partner,
now enemy, Professor Van Pelt. to conduct an expedition.
Professor Van Pelt searched for the altar of the jaguar.
The place where the gemstone of Jumanji lies.
You know how obsessive that gem is.
And after years of research, he discovered his location.
Yes, I finally found it.
Van Pelt told me he wanted to find her to write about her.
In his writings.
- It's real.
- What I did not know...
It's that he wanted to take the gem for him.
I found her!
The legend says the Jaguar watches over Jumanji.
And anyone who tries to blind him will be consumed by a dark force.
Van Pelt became the leader of all creatures in Jumanji.
Possessing them, controlling them.
And a terrible curse has occupied this land.
I asked him to put it back, but once in his hand
he will never let him go.
I waited until they fell asleep that night.
And I went to attack.
Bring me the gem!
And kill anyone who tries to stop you.
Here is.
With your valuable help and associates
You must use your special abilities
to return the gem to the eye of the jaguar
And to lift the curse.
I'm sure you want to start right away.
- Actually, I think...
- Good luck.
The fate of Jumanji lies in your hands.
- What the?
- And do not forget...
The purpose is to recite it in verses.
Return the stone and lift the curse.
If you want to leave the game, you have to save Jumanji.
And call his name.
Good luck. The fate of Jumanji lies in your hands.
- And do not forget...
- Always say the same things.
Return the Gem and lift the curse.
If you want to leave the game you have to save Jumanji.
And call his name.
OK. You do it.
In the real world, people love you, you can meet with anyone you want.
So you say when you scare yourself?
Do you sit and judge me all the time?
I split myself from Noah, I turned into a man and I can not find my cell phone!
I'm allowed to be sad.
Doctor Bravestone, here's a Jumanji map.
Go to the Bazaar to find the missing piece.
- Bazaar?
- Missing part of what?
- Goodbye.
- Can not we go to the statue?
And remember, if you want to leave the game...
You have to save Jumanji and call his name.
You want to put it in your backpack?
Not.
Come on, you're the only one who has a backpack, Fridge.
And what if? We have a map, so we have to look ..
Bazaar, I think.
So we try to return the jewel to the jaguar statue.
And then we go home. No problem.
Why can not we go? Let's stop the game without doing it.
We have to finish the game.
I think we should save Jumanji.
Damn, what a man!
Don't cry...
There are many diseases here.
It's hot.
That's what I'm good at. Play video games.
That's what I do.
There will be levels in such a game.
To finish the game, we must finish all levels.
They will become more and more difficult as we advance.
- We finish the level...
- Spencer, do you know where we're going?
- Somewhat.
- Somewhat?
It's good.
We are in good hands.
I think the missing part.
That's what we're looking for, the missing part of the map.
The problem is that there's nothing here.
What does that mean?
It's a map, as he said.
It's a map of Jumanji.
- Cartography.
- What is this?
Studying the maps. It's a skill of Professor Oberon.
Yes. That's right.
So you can not see, but I can.
The chosen characters have special abilities.
There must be a way to access our abilities.
What you did?
Power, fearlessness, speed, boomerang, education.
Intensity of burning.
What are you doing?
What happened?
You just burned.
Weaknesses: Nothing?
How did you make your list appear?
I pressed my left arm.
Yes, on your breasts. Come on, I'll show you.
Stay away from me.
At least try to see in front of us.
Strengths: Karate, T'ai Chi, Aikido, Dance Fight?
Dance fight?
Weakness: Venin.
Really?
What does Paleontology mean?
I think the fossil study.
It's the cargo.
Said karatesta sexy to the old fossil with no resistance.
I hate this game.
Weakness: the cake?
Yes, cake is my weakness. Together with speed and force.
Force is my weakness.
Hey, I can, quick question.
How is my weakness forced?
Somebody explain. And why do I need speed?
Why do I have to be fast when I'm being watched by a huge killer zebra?
And can I wear that shiny hat?
You're a valet.
- What this means?
- I think you're taking my gun
in your backpack and you give it to me when I need it.
Friends... Map...
- It's changed.
- I mean?
- What's that?
- Well...
There is not much information, but now one minute did not write this.
Write "Powerful Shot".
I do not like this. I'm done.
- What else?
- Good.
And right here it says "Deep".
- Hippopotamus comes from deep. The one..
- Yes, who did the thing.
Let's continue.
If "Deep" is the first level,
then "Powerful Shot" must be the second level.
In what direction?
Good.
If that's what it is.
And that's here...
I think right here.
What is that game?
Fugiþi!
Wait!
Come on!
Why do I run so slowly?
Dear good!
- It's shit!
- Let's break up!
Lord!
- Come on!
- These guys have big weapons!
- What? Is that what it is about?
- See your backpack.
- Or what?
- In your backpack you have my gun!
I have your weapons.
I do not feel anything. What is this?
Yes, boomerang, one of my abilities.
What are you gonna do about it?
I do not know, I think I'll kill them.
- You want to kill them?
- Do you have a better idea?
Warning.
Take a look.
Good job.
We have to get out of here before we exterminate.
It's not possible.
It worked!
Okay, we have to go.
I can not beat them at speed.
We have to go, climb behind me.
- I'd rather die.
- Come on, come on.
No, I'm gonna die.
Get down, Spencer!
I think you're joking.
Not...
- We have to jump.
- Are you okay?
I'd like to do something else now than that.
- Piss!
- What the hell!
- We have to jump.
- We do not even know the depth of water.
We have to jump.
Jump up!
I think I've had a heart attack. I have difficulty in breathing.
It was the most embarrassing moment of my life.
Do not do that anymore.
I swallowed plenty of water.
They shot me.
It's not possible...
Martha?
What happened to her?
She's dead?
Just sit for a moment.
What the heck is happening?
- Get out of me.
- Are you okay?
- I guess.
- Get out of me.
- Are you okay?
- You want to kill me?
What am I, human landing zone?
Just as I thought. Everyone has three lives.
These tattoos are small on the arms.
Mama da 'ce brand am!
Spencer.
What were you saying?
It's the number of our lives.
Bethany was eaten by hippopotamus and has only two lines.
Is right.
What happens when we exhaust the lines?
It usually means... that the game is over.
What do you want to say?
Are you saying we can even die here?
- I'm not sure.
- Are not you sure?
Are not you sure you are always playing?
I was not locked in here anymore. I'm not sure, but I think so, we can die.
That worries me most now.
Let's find the missing part then.
Good.
There seems to be another village behind this mountain.
Maybe it's the Bazaar.
- Let's go.
- One minute, I have to urinate first.
And I have, I've been on the whole day.
Can I come with you and show me how to do it?
I need your help.
Yeah, sure, I'll help you.
So how do you do it?
Easily open the zipper, pull it off and pull it.
Do not forget to target, it's very important.
God, I have a penis attached to the body.
- Martha, look at my penis.
- No, thank you.
Is it the first time you saw him?
Yes, I did not want to forget.
I just looked at how I got to her and I'm glad it's long like mine.
What are you doing? Are you looking?
- Sorry.
- Do not look here.
It's important never to look.
Okay, good boy, we're gonna make it slowly not just you.
- Now what?
- Launch, and do not forget to target.
What's the point? What did you miss?
Can not avoid the discussion?
It's much easier!
Commodity, right?
Yes, you can handle it more easily.
Mother I want to put on Instagram.
Bravestone?
He and the others.
They escaped?
I lost them in the jungle.
I should have known.
What do you mean, sir?
I want every creature and every soldier to hunt them.
Take what is mine.
Finds him.
Be careful with the ground.
The earth is slippery, I do not want to get your ankle stuck.
- Shut up.
- Good.
- Are you borrowing my coat?
- Yes of course.
- What are you doing?
- I feel bikini harbor in school.
I did it once and sent me to the director.
Of course.
Noah likes to see some skin, that's the key to our relationship.
I can not open my mouth around you, you do not know me, but you hate me.
I do not hate you.
- Do not you hate me?
- Not.
I thought you were like a popular girl, and they all treat you like a princess.
Maybe that makes you think a little bit about you.
It's correct.
But do you think the reason you judge me...
Is it because you're afraid the world does not like you, and you decided not to like it first?
Not.
May be...
Well then.
I'm just saying you're a chick. Keep it as such.
Thanks.
I guess.
- Come to me, Spencer.
- Why are you so upset about me?
Do you really ask me?
You kicked me out of the team and you got me here.
Are we no longer friends that we are stuck in Jumanji? I do not believe this.
We're no longer friends that I'm not cool enough to go out with you.
So you pretend you do not know me anymore.
Until you needed themes you could not do it yourself.
No wonder you do not know anything about the Westward expansion.
See?
I'm not stupid, Spencer.
I asked you to make me a simple favor.
I told you to do my homework, do not get out of the squad and kick it.
And I can not do what I know better, and it's just your fault.
I should get married.
- I want to see you try.
- What you said?
Good.
- See what's going on here.
- Boys.
Do you think that if you have 1.97m,
122 pounds of muscle, I fear you?
That you think?
May be.
All the annoying child I met in the 7th.
You never change.
Do not let your new body make you arrogant.
Fool.
Not!
Spencer!
- You killed him!
- You're crazy!
Calm down, he'll be back.
- Do not do me anymore.
- Do not push me anymore.
- Or what, Spencer?
- Or I'll push you back.
Did you burst me?
Fridge, no.
I will beat you.
Enough!
We can not waste our lives.
We like it or not, we need each other.
We need to do this together.
Can you repeat?
Do we have to do this together?
Do you control yourself? Or does it happen naturally?
It happens naturally.
What should we do here?
We look for the missing part of the map.
And we ask her?
No, we look around, we investigate, but most importantly, friends...
Let's be discreet.
Fresh, fresh bread!
Does anyone have money? I starve.
Take your fresh bread.
Friends, I think the game is trying to tell us to eat.
- We have to...
- Do not do that anymore.
God, what a good thing, I have not eaten bread since 9 years.
- Are you serious?
- How do you think I have this belly?
Give me too.
Wait... what is that?
It's my favorite cake.
Cake?
But you said it was bread.
I have not eaten much and I forgot my taste.
I do not even...
- Something wrong with me?
- Not.
- Shaking me?
- I'm weird?
- Not.
- Are I still black?
- Yes.
OK friend.
I'm fine, everything is fine.
I just found out that I like the cake, so I could not resist it.
It's all right...
What the hell?
As I said, you have to be discreet.
- You said it and eat.
- Fresh bread.
Go away!
Dr. Bravestone, fine you are here, Jumanji needs you.
Thanks. We're glad to be here.
Ask him about the missing part.
Okay, I'm Bethany.
I mean, Professor Sherly, and I have a map with a missing piece.
Dr. Bravestone, fine you are here, Jumanji needs you.
Really?
We have to find the missing part.
What you need is in the basket.
A wrong move and you die.
Trust each other and do not blink.
The missing part is not what you think it is.
Dear good.
- Good luck my hero, Jumanji...
- She needs you.
We know, you said that.
So, do you think there's a snake there, or something like that?
Yeah, it's more like your kind.
Why would that be my kind?
Because you're her hero. Get to work.
I do not want to do that!
Just do it!
Mamba black!
It was Mamba black.
A quarter of a milligram of venom is enough to kill an adult.
It numbs your mouth,
followed by fever and you lose control of your muscles.
How can I know all this?
- What should we do?
- Have you seen anything else there?
I did not see that I had no time.
Come on, trust each other, and never blink.
I think it's a holbat contest.
- What the?
- What are you talking about?
- Think about it! What does it mean not to blink?
- Friends, I think he's right.
If we see a rattle snake, we do not move too much.
I think someone should look directly at the snake and not blink.
And then Spencer stretches and takes whatever's in there.
- Why me?
- Because it's your mission.
Okay, then who will look at it and will not blink?
I'm good at doing that.
Then this is your moment.
Tell me when.
Now.
What should we do?
- We have to deactivate it.
- What the?
We have to pull his mouth out of the blind spot.
We need to be very careful with the venomous gland.
We need to break his teeth.
Everyone.
It was not until then a holbat contest.
Trust each other and never blink.
You trusted me and deactivated the serpent.
I did, I did.
Yeah, you did.
- Thank you.
- Yes of course.
Friends, that does not look like a piece of paper.
The missing part is an elephant?
There's something written on the wrapping paper.
When you see me, start climbing.
Start climbing?
When do we see an elephant?
I turned off the snake.
You have to find elephants for the next level in the game.
Hey!
Fugiþi!
Warning!
Jump up!
I have to warn you, I think I have a strong punch.
Very.
Very, very, very...
Uppercut.
Esche. We're hitting our heads.
Caput!
Esche. Lock.
Escape, blow.
Break into the wall!
Mommy crazy!
Let's do it.
What to do?
Put it in my backpack.
Esche. We head off.
Throw the ceiling!
Hi, Doctor.
It's been a long time.
I'm sure you have something that belongs to me.
We just want to go home.
Come on, follow me fast.
Put your hand on them!
Come on!
Down here, fast.
Follow me and do exactly what I'm telling you.
Let's go.
God, I'm glad you came.
- Yes?
- I'm very pleased.
I saw you in the Bazaar and I thought it was not possible.
But I think so. Go back to the wall!
Dear good!
Let's go further.
- Watch where you are.
- Who are you?
- Yeah, like who you got us?
- That's right. Sorry. My mistake.
Let me explain.
Wait a minute. Are you the pilot?
- Yes I am.
- And you were absorbed in the game?
- A step back and sit back.
- Why?
Very scary.
Mommy how bad.
Wait.
All right, let's take this plank.
Follow me.
Carefully. It's a terrible way to die.
So.
Come on.
I can, I can.
I deactivated the snake, give me some respect.
Good.
Hi.
Let's.
By the way, I'm Alex.
Spencer Gilpen.
Martha, Fridge and Bethany.
Bethany?
- Are you a girl?
- Woman.
In real life you probably do not touch her.
They have escaped, they seem to have been helped.
Seaplane.
They probably got rid of the channels.
I'm sorry boss.
It will not happen again.
I know.
What do you prepare?
Margarita, is one of my abilities.
That and piloting.
Though I was shot down by orangutans and fighters.
So maybe I'm not that good.
Cheers.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- I've never been drinking any more.
- Me neither.
- You know what? Damn it!
- Cheers!
- I'm done with that.
- It's good.
Can a repetir be?
Alex, what about these candles?
Lãmâiþã. One of my weaknesses is the monsters.
Which is pretty bad when you live alone in the middle of the forest.
Opa, he's alone.
Who's this?
Who's Alan Parrish?
It's the one who built this place.
Are you saying there have been others stuck here?
Yeah, I mean, it's Alan Parrish's house.
I just live in it.
Alex, how long have you been in the game?
It's hard to say. Time is weird here.
But a few months at least.
- Months?
- What the?
- Yeah, we did not cross the place of transport.
- Is that what it is?
The next level.
The first time I could not take off with the balloon.
Then with the whole plane.
And when we came to the last life...
I realized I was done.
And I will not get out of here alone.
I could not handle it myself.
You can not kill a black Mamba with a margarita.
You can.
You need a zoologist for that.
Alex, we can help each other.
You've been here for a long time, you know the game and we have a lot of power with us.
Yeah, we're working fine together.
I do not know, if I lose again, I'm done.
It really scares me when I'm thinking of going back to the plane.
I do not want to die in Jumanji.
We just have to stay together.
We do that and we can win, I know that.
Dear good!
You are the missing part.
You were the one we were supposed to find.
The clue was to go to the Bazaar to find the missing part?
He was not an elephant.
- It was me.
- Yes.
Friends...
- Let's do it.
- Yes.
Spencer, are you in your margarita?
That's a good margarita.
Here is.
Place of transport.
There are many vehicles in there.
We have to take one, cross the canyon and go to the statue of the jaguar.
Okay, I see the place of transport, I see the canyon, but I still do not see the statue.
And that's weird, because it's the most important thing
Work in Jumanji and it's immense.
That's what she says.
Are you drunk, Fridge?
- No, I'm not drunk.
- He's drunk.
I only drank 3 glasses of margarita.
You are half the real size.
Indifferent...
Okay, Alex, what are we doing here? How are we going through the guards?
Last time I waited for them to leave.
- How long did it take?
- Three weeks.
We're gonna die.
- All right, Plan B.
- There might be another door there.
But we must distract the guards first.
I know.
I'm good at distracting men.
He plays video games and I distract men.
Bethany, I'm sorry to let you know,
but you do not have the utensils for it now.
Not I.
What the?
- You have to go down and seduce yourself.
- Not.
- And distract them.
- Not!
I can not go and seduce soldiers I do not know.
I know, but now we have no better idea.
You do not understand, I can not do it.
I'm not good at talking to men.
I hope that I teach you.
No sorry. We need another plan, I will not do that.
Just distract them enough to get in.
I can not Spencer, I'm not a dead woman.
What are you talking about? You're all right.
You can do anything.
Pretty, Spencer, do not you want to put a romantic candle in your house?
Or do you want to get the hell out of here?
Okay, show me how.
Hours begin immediately. Come on, girl.
Watch and learn.
What would you like to say romantically with candles?
What are you talking about?
You said that Martha and me, drinking candles, what did you mean?
The girl was watching you, Spencer.
What the?
Well, as far as flirting is concerned, the key is to make them see you,
without telling them that you know they saw you.
And when I start talking to you, you can do three things.
You are doing the bad, interested, or bad.
Depends what men you are in front of.
It's like my nightmare dream.
I will not take it personally.
Now the hair is everything. Touch it, move it.
Play with him, move him a long way. Hypnotize him with him.
It turns that way.
Now look your eyes down.
Leave your head down and have big eyes.
- It's shining now.
- Shining?
Like animated characters.
You need practice.
Do you really think I like it?
Why are we talking about this?
- If she tries to kiss me?
- You kiss it too.
If she tries to kiss me without warning me?
What are you talking about? Have not you kissed anyone yet?
Not... Are you gonna tell this to everyone?
Boys, I found the side door.
- Guess what I found out.
- No, do not tell them!
Okay, let's start with the way you walk.
Slowly, like an elegant gazelle.
Or a high-pitched horse. One foot in front of the other.
Come on, bum, bum, do not.
And everything you can attract attention, something like that.
It takes a very long time to do this.
Okay, that's better.
Now she smiles. You look terrified.
You are so funny...
God, how funny you are.
- I think I already understand.
- That's true.
Now keep your lips light, that way.
No, not disgusting, relax.
Now he touches the tip of his mouth with his tongue.
- So?
- That's right.
So.
So?
I think you're ready.
- Good.
You as seduced as your life is at stake. Because that's right.
Okay, that's the door, we need something to pull the fence.
Fridge, have something in your backpack for something?
Yes of course.
I have some...
Iron cutters.
Is that a good tool in the given situation?
Perfect, in fact.
This is called the power of the backpack.
Hey, guys, I think this will work.
And I believe that.
It's really great and they do not like to meet new people.
Great?
Not like Cindy Crawford, but for Jumanji, it's a bomb.
- Bomb?
- Cindy Crawford?
- You think so?
- I say so.
I'd like to shoot it.
Alex.
What year do you think it is?
- What do you want to say?
- It's not possible.
It's 1996.
You're Alex Rigg, are not you?
Yes, that's right.
What do you want to say? The weird house?
What are you talking about? How do you know me?
- Alex, I do not know how to say this...
- You are in this game for 20 years.
I would not have said that.
What the?
No, you joke?
No, Alex Rigg, everyone knows about you.
You are the missing child.
20 years ago.
20 years?
20 years.
I do not even know how to say that, but Cindy Crawford's 50 years ago.
- But she's still sexy.
- Yes.
Yes...
Here I am!
Hey.
We'll take you home.
Yes.
What the fuck did she have on the bottom?
Bethany, what did you tell him to do?
- Did some ankle sprain?
- He has not flirted so far.
Hello little girl.
What are you doing here alone?
Hello boy.
Looks like I'm lost.
Can you help me?
Hello little girl.
What are you doing here alone?
You are very interesting and funny.
What's he doing?
Did insects get in the hair?
He forgot all practice.
Let's go.
Wait...
Let me tell you the book I read.
About microbiology.
It's my favorite biology.
Hello little girl.
What are you doing here alone?
You're a lightning woman.
Dansaþi?
Whichever?
I hate this place.
Her ability is the dancing fight.
Alex, what do you think? What is the plan?
- What the?
- Which one are we taking?
I do not know... I told you...
- We have to fly, do not we? Helicopter.
- I told you, I do not know.
It gives them cafes.
This is our girl.
Yeah, great!
Destroy them.
Bravo, face!
Yes!
You are my heroine.
We have to leave.
Give me a hug, face.
- God.
- You did it!
- I did it!
- Yeah, give me a hug, face.
We do not have time to dress here.
Come on motorcycles, let's wipe it out.
Look, airplane, we have to fly, man.
No, I can not do that.
I told you I'm not a good pilot.
Maybe we should take the school bus?
What the? We can not cross the school bus.
You picked the plane and the balloon, maybe the helicopter.
No, I can not do it. Good?
I do not want to die.
I'm a little scared.
All right, I do it.
How difficult it is to fly the helicopter, push the button and spin the propeller.
After that...
I pull the lever. So you go back and forth.
Once we get into the air, we'll be fine.
I just have to climb, it does not have this scale, so ..
Let me see, you know what, I think I'm gonna get in.
- No, you're drunk.
- Not.
Fridge, you are drunk. Give me the keys.
And Alex. Alex... If I can fight these guys...
And you can fly the helicopter. I know you can do it.
Come on.
Alex.
It's time we need you.
Do not forget that you are the missing piece.
Waterman McDonough, on duty.
Let's.
What happened?
- Something has gone wrong!
- What the?
Hold yourself well!
God, we're gonna die! We'll die!
Lord!
- He does not want to get up.
- What the? What do you want to say?
- The blades are damaged.
- What the?
Someone has to go up there and tilt the rotor that fixes the propeller.
That's what we're getting up and down.
Friends...
That can not be good.
They're not good news.
White rhinoes!
They are native animals from Jumanji, big, white, and eat people.
It's not possible!
- To draw near.
- It took my stomach.
- Up!
- I can not climb!
I think I used too many margaritas.
What are we going to do?
I'll fix the helicopter.
- Yes!
- Tell me what I have to do.
You must connect the flight rod to the propeller rotor.
- The rotor flight rod.
- Wait, what?
I'll be right back.
Spencer, where are you going?
Grãbeºte up!
- Take care!
- Grow up.
I'll stand on this, and I'm headed for the lethal plummet.
Here's the flight rod.
Spencer!
Grãbeºte up!
Come on, Spencer!
We do not have time.
Ready!
What the? We did, I thought we were going to die.
Goods!
What I was scared!
Oops.
What the?
It's gently washed away.
- What the?
- Did you get rid of the gem?
I leaned to believe that I was vomiting, but I did not.
And the gem fell from my backpack.
We need that gem!
I know.
That's the crazy part, because I know we need her.
Not. We are in difficulty.
Alex, come back, we have to go back and take it.
Yes, take a detour.
Let's find her, open eyes, to work as a group.
There! I see her.
What I do?
It seems to protect her.
Okay, how will we do that?
I do not know.
You will take it, are not you, man?
What do you need, boomerang, maybe scissors, iron pipes, laces ..
I'll help you, whatever you need, I can give you, okay?
You choose.
- What the?
- Sorry.
Sorry for what?
It's not possible...
Turn us!
Help!
Dear good!
Alex, get ready to go back!
What the?
When I give you the signal, turn 90 degrees to the right.
Now!
You pushed me out of a helicopter, bitch!
- You're amazing, Spencer.
- You're an excellent pilot, Alex.
And Spencer, you are wonderful.
- Thanks, but he was...
- Not. You...
you were wonderful.
Sorry Sorry. I'm the one who sacrificed.
You do not know what it's like to be inside a rhinoceros.
And you do not even want to know.
I've seen many things. I felt it too.
Things that can never be deleted from my memory.
It's funny for you. Râdeþi. Come on.
I've been trying to cross the canyon for 20 years.
Do you realize how big it is?
- Thonar.
- Not!
Not...
Alex, no...
- Alex. Not.
- Alex.
Alex, look at me.
She's dying.
We can not let him die. We are very close.
Does anyone know how to resuscitate?
Yes, start by pressing your chest 3 times and breathing mouth to mouth.
One two Three.
How do you do this?
Tighten his nose and open his mouth.
A breath, two breaths and repeats.
Come on Alex.
Bethany, stop it. Your tattoo!
Looks like you've given a life.
It's fine.
And if you need her?
I want Alex to go home.
What happened?
Alex, Bethany has given you her life.
Bethany, are you all right?
I think so.
Bethany, is that true?
Did you give me a life of yours?
Yes of course.
Thanks.
What are you looking at?
You have a problem.
God, what a crazy thing these things are!
20 years?
Yes. I think so.
I still think of my poor parents.
By what I think they passed.
And why, because I hid in my hiding place,
Being too afraid to finish the game.
Sorry.
I do not want to tell you that, just...
I'm easy to talk to you.
I understand.
Sometimes it's easy to focus on yours,
that you think other people also have problems.
You said something very deeply.
Thanks. I feel that since I lost my cellphone,
My other senses have sharpened.
Does the phone mean something different in the future?
But you, Alex, what do you like?
In the real world.
I have a rock band. I'm a drummer like my dad.
Hey.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
We're filling these up.
- Misto.
- Yes.
I'm glad you're here, I ..
I want to tell you something.
Yes?
And I want to tell you now. If we talk again next time...
I have no courage.
I like you, Martha.
I like you crazy.
I'm crazy about you.
- Yes? Absolutely.
In the seventh grade.
Really?
It has not happened to me.
What do you want to say?
I mean, nobody likes me, I can not believe I did that.
I never told anyone about my feelings.
And I like you, Spencer.
- Really?
- Yes.
Yes! You are smart, kind and sweet.
Yes. And I like you.
Wait. Are you sure it's not all this?
What the? God, no. You're not my kind.
I like nerds.
Really? I'm a nerd!
I never kissed anyone.
- That's the first time.
- And to me the same.
Good. Goods.
Do not say, okay?
Come on!
I do not want to see that. I do not want, not today.
You taught your love and I found the jaguar.
Come on.
Lord.
Here it.
We'd better go.
I think we need to follow this path.
Not.
It can not be that easy.
"Defenders."
What does it mean?
There's only one way to find out.
Fridge, give me jewelery.
Spencer.
Something's going to happen.
I hate these drums.
Hey, you can not just go there.
Not.
That's what the game wants us to do.
Let's follow the path.
It's a trap.
When you see the elephant you start climbing.
I take it through the trees.
- Trees?
- Yes.
- Do you think that means?
- Definitely.
That's right.
It's the last level of the game.
And I'm almost sure it's a Bravestone thing.
Did he talk to him in the third person?
I think at fourth.
How does that work?
Picking up is one of his abilities.
I understand.
Cake makes me explode.
- Not!
- God!
Spencer!
God, there are panthers.
Not.
They're jaguars.
Spencer!
God, are you all right?
I think so.
You got another gem, right?
- Yes.
- Thank God.
What happened?
I do not want to talk about this.
We need a new plan.
- Right.
- Yes.
- Total.
- Spencer, do you have any ideas?
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Now?
What happened?
I cant do this.
- What are you talking about?
- I cant do this.
Who are they hunting? I'm not an adventurer.
- Actually, I'm not brave.
- Spencer...
I saw you hanging on a helicopter.
It's easy to be brave when you have spare lives.
Much harder if you only have one life.
We all have one life, man.
That's all we get. That's how it works.
The question is how do we live it.
What kind of man you want to be.
Did we quote our director somehow?
God, this game is a danger, I gotta get out of here.
Look, we can do that, man.
We can do it together.
Together.
You're a good friend, Fridge.
Good.
I'm not good at video games.
But I'm good at football.
That line out there...
are defensors.
Which means we have to go through it.
Friends...
We have to leave.
Well, look how we do.
We will play what I call:
"Double chance of winning."
Bethany, you take it to the left.
I take it to the right.
Alex, you'll take it in the middle.
I'm going with Spencer.
No, you have to do something else.
Dansaþi?
Hey! Here!
Come and catch me!
- Thank you.
- With pleasure.
Go to the statue. Go!
Oh man,okay.
Stay calm and do not panic.
Turns out!
He's an elephant and a sling.
How are you? I'm Finbar Mouse.
Zoologist and the rucsac '.
Give me the jewel
or your boyfriend dies.
- Do not give it.
- Remain silent!
Turns out!
Take me in return, okay?
Give me the jewel.
I cant do this.
5...
- 4...
- I can not give you the gem.
3...
- Spencer.
- 2...
Because I do not have it.
The zoologist is coming, jerk!
No no!
Elephant.
Start climbing.
Go there and I'll bring you the gem.
- Martha.
- Believe me I'll get it.
Go!
Go, Martha!
Alex!
I get the gem.
The game is over.
I do not believe this.
Venom is my weakness.
Go, Spencer!
Not.
That's great!
Good!
Gimme his name!
Everybody call his name!
Jumanji!
- I think I did.
- I think we've won.
I think we have succeeded.
Friends, Nigel comes.
Nigel.
Bravo, adventurers.
You lifted the curse.
Everyone in Jumanji thanks you.
You've done the job here.
Unfortunately, here we are going to separate.
Seaplane McDonough.
Let me shake my hand.
Alex...
And you, Professor Oberon.
Later, friends.
- I will miss you...
- Get me out of here!
Goodbye, Ruby Roundhouse.
Wait.
If we do not come back?
I just...
I like to be so.
With you.
Well, then... let's be that.
Daily.
Come home.
Doctor Bravestone...
Nigel...
I'm ready to go home.
Pa, my dear friend.
Pa, Bravestone.
- God...
- Allright then...
I'm back, baby!
I have no longer complained of how it looks.
I missed you.
Where is Alex?
Hey, look...
The weird house?
Do you think that...
That means he can...
- Alex?
- Hey, Dad, can you come here to help me?
Yes.
Father, excuse me for a moment?
- Sure.
- Be right back.
Bethany?
Spencer?
Yes.
Ruby Roundhouse?
And you're a Fridge.
I'm surprised to see you all.
- You came back.
- Yes.
He took me from where I left...
In 1996.
And your parents and your house?
Yeah, it's all good, pal.
Now you're an adult.
Do you have a child.
Yes, that's right.
He's Andy.
And my daughter's called Bethany.
I gave her the name of the girl who saved my life.
I'm so surprised.
Salve.
Do you want to go on trips? Namely in nature?
Yes. Something amazing next summer. What do you think?
Are you all right?
Hey!
I'll see you after hours.
- Hi.
- Howdy.
- Has something interesting happened?
- No, nothing comes to mind.
- Did you even talk to Martha?
- I gave him a message on the weekend.
Did not you talk to her again?
There she is.
Go to the door, Doctor Bravestone.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- I really wanted to call you.
- I understand you.
- Sorry. I do not know why...
- A strange thing...
As if you did not know. I wondered what was happening.
What?
Impressive.
MAKOTO77
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org