Play one of the best new FPS shooters,
search Steam for PROJECT WARLOCK
Sr. Santos, so good to see you.
We saved you usual table Mr Santos
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
5 Months in Brazil.
You're a hard man to find.
You even have the accent right.
I do say so.
The principal I represent has an offer for you.
He would like three men killed.
Each death must look like an accident.
Your specialty, I believe.
Seems that reports of your demise
have been greatly exaggerated.
My principal can make that known
to certain interested parties.
Which means that your new life here
would end rather quickly.
Or you can do the job
and go back to being dead.
What's your pleasure 'Senor Otto Santos'?
Let me make a call.
What are you doing?
Tell your principal,
never pays to fuck with the dead!!
Get the fuck on the ground!!
Get the fuck down!!
Don't look at me!!
- Bishop.
- Hello, Mei.
You're different.
Older.
Hmmmmm, something more than that.
I need time to find someone
before they find me.
Then I'll be moving on.
Who else is here?
No one.
Diving season's over. Come.
Your home is waiting for you.
- How was your trip?
- It was okay.
It was a busy season.
But don't worry,
no one came near your home.
-Nothing's changed.
-Get some rest.
Hi, how can I help you?
Oh, great you speak English.
Um…I'm running low on first aid.
I'm staying on the boat.
Sure.
This is all I have.
Thanks.
If I don't have what you need,
I can call our supply boat.
They can take you back to Phuket to get it.
No, this is great.
Thanks so much.
Any time.
Bishop!
They're fighting. It's bad.
I've met her. She has a backbone.
Women like that get killed in these situations.
Domestic squabble, Mei.
Not my business.
You helped me once.
Help her!
Or I will do it.
Hold this.
Frank, get the fuck away from me!!
Frank!!
Not worth it.
Bitch.
- Let her go.
- Who the fuck are you?
Please help me.
I said let her go.
Last chance.
Let go of me Frank.
You don't wanna do that.
Fuck you!!
Is he dead?
Bishop?
Oh, shit!
Take her ashore.
I'll deal with the boat.
Okay.
- Bishop.
- Where is she?
Sleeping. In your bungalow.
What's going on?
Gina Thorn. American.
- That's you, right?
- Yeah.
You're the second woman who
has my picture in her phone.
The first was working for a guy called Crain.
Name ring a bell?
The only thing you got right was my name.
The first woman was a messenger.
Is that what you are?
So what's the message?
- I already told you...
- Tell me about Craine!
What are you supposed to do for him?
Where is he?
Fine. I'll talk!
Look, I don't work for Crain.
That's the truth! But he did send me.
Where is he?
- I don't know
- Why are you here?
He has something on me.
- I had no choice.
- Right.
- Any of his men nearby?
- He didn't say, I didn't ask.
What about Frank?
- Part of the setup.
- Explain.
He was supposed to get mean.
I'd escape to this island.
It wasn't meant to be real.
But then Frank got drunk and attacked me.
Crain wanted me to look like a victim.
- And get next to me?
- Yeah.
But Frank took his part too far...
So we meet. What's next?
I use that cell. And called the
preprogrammed number. Let it ring once.
After that, I don't know.
My 'new girl' gets kidnapped is what.
- What?
- The thought didn't cross your mind?
Okay so you fall for me and
Crain thinks he has leverage on you. Why?
Well to force me to do something I don't want to do.
What is it that you do?
I'll make the call not you.
I'll choose when they come.
Then I'll take Crain out.
No I'm not going to help you kill anyone!
Do you really believe that Crain lets
people he blackmails into helping him live?
I've spent my whole life setting people up to die.
I can set you up to live.
Subtitled created by Freaky.
My father was a doctor of Eastern medicine.
He was a healer.
Bishop used to study with him.
To learn how to heal?
Men like him?
I thought so too,
but my father understood...
that those who have been hurt the most
often have the greatest ability to heal.
18 months ago special military operative
Gina Thorn left a warzone in Afghanistan...
to offer humanitarian assistance in Cambodia.
After my last deployment I just needed a change.
Too many innocent people have
been caught in the line of fire.
Rules of engagement made it impossible to prevent.
And then, you know when I came to Phnom Penh, I uh…
I don't know it just felt right here.
And, felt like I can maybe do
something good with my life.
I can't afford surprises.
Need to know what Crain has on you.
I run a shelter for victims of trafficking in Cambodia.
There's always been an issue or two, but…
I've managed to handle it.
A few weeks ago,
one of my staff members was kidnapped.
Two days later, she was thrown off
a truck at my front door.
Beaten. Died within an hour.
Crain sent this asshole Jeremy...
who said that was just a taste
of what he would do to everyone at the shelter…
including children.
They are my weakness.
All the leverage Crain needed.
So you see I didn't have a choice.
I had to do what Crain wanted me to.
- What are you doing?
- Hold my hand.
It's for Crain's people.
They're watching.
Where?
Two men in a Zodiac.
Out in the ocean.
Subtitled created by Freaky.
There you are. Come on you two.
You're gonna miss the best part.
Give me your hands.
Hold this please.
We can just get a drink and…
No you will not. You will stay right there…
Thank you very much.
What are you doing?
All couples have to be tied together.
But we're not a couple.
You sure looked like it on the beach.
So um…do you go to weddings a lot?
Not my idea of a good time.
Me neither.
Here.
We supposed to drink this?
No. Put your fingertips in it and place 3 dots on
each others forehead for good luck.
- Enjoy.
- I could use some luck.
Enjoy?
Okay, my turn.
Come on lets just get a drink.
Leave that.
All right one second.
This is a great look for you.
You missed a spot.
It's kind of stuck.
Okay, okay.
Next time you use your shoe.
I love this song.
This is a Thai song?
Yeah.
It's so good.
Wanna dance?
No don't worry.
I don't want to dance with you.
What do you think I'm a bad dancer?
You look like you're a terrible dancer.
Hey.
I uh…I just wanted to thank you…for everything.
Everything?
And I wanted to apologize
for getting you into this mess.
Those kids are everything to me.
If they get trafficked or…
or killed, I couldn't bare it.
I understand.
I was an orphan too.
I was sold to an east end gangster
who specialized in training child soldiers.
Crain was there too.
What happened?
I escaped, he didn't.
No doubt they blamed him.
Took it out in blood.
So now he blames you.
Yeah this is his payback.
Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
What are we gonna do?
I worked it out.
Supply boat from the backside
of the island out of view.
And tomorrow night you'll be out of danger.
Your kids too.
It's all arranged.
And what about Crain?
I'm not doing his three kills.
Once your safe there's
only going to be one…him.
But they'll never let you near him.
They'll never know I was there.
I want you to hold onto something for me.
Until I come back.
My father gave this to me.
It's the only memory I have of him.
I'll keep it safe.
That's Crain's guy.
Look at me.
You remember, make sure
I get you home. Trust me.
Bishop!!
Mr. Crain I have him right here.
Tell me how to find you face to face.
Are we done?
Follow me.
Sit down.
Please, don't move.
I'd listen to her if I were you, Arthur.
No need for guards or guns when the man
you want's sitting on a pound of syntax.
How did you find me, right?
What? No, 'Hello. Nice to see
you after all these years'?
But then you always were
one for getting down to business.
How did I find you?
You should know better than anyone, Arthur.
There's no privacy anymore.
Not with wonderful things like
facial recognition and…
satellite tracking.
I'm going to give you
something I never give anyone:
The chance to walk way.
Give me the girl... and walk away.
I see you've developed a
sense of humor over the years.
But if it's all the same, no,
I need you. You're the best.
Open it.
I need you
to eliminate three people.
And this is the first.
His name is Krill.
Mass murder and warlord.
He's also the highest profile arms dealer in Africa.
He's imprisoned on Penjara Kaedah in Malaysia.
His imprisonment is what keeps him secure.
It's impossible for his
enemies to get to him.
And this?
It's important that you
swallow it only after the kill.
Or the fuel cell will degrade
and we'll never find you.
Where is Gina?
Do the three kills, Arthur.
Get the girl back.
Even if you don't love
her you at least owe her, no?
I mean she's in this shit because of you.
How do I know you'll keep her alive?
Finish your kill,
get a video call.
After the last one you'll receive
instructions where to find her.
And your word's good is it?
Good heavens, absolutely not.
But I do have a very keen
sense of self-preservation.
I know that cheating you
will only make me your target.
And since that concludes
our business for the moment,
I wish you 'bon chance'.
Subtitled created by Freaky.
Let's get moving sweetheart, come on.
The prison is seventy miles out to sea.
Set off cliffs more than a hundred meters high.
And surrounded by shark infested waters.
So basically impossible to get in.
And nobody has ever gotten out.
It will be even harder
to get your man.
He's surrounded at all times by
his team of loyal soldiers.
Getting in alone will be your main challenge.
It's powerful stuff.
Hope you know what you're doing.
Hey!! What? What?
What do you want.
Hey, stop.
Stop it.
Fuck you.
You're under arrest!
Line up!
Go.
Keep going!
Bishop, remember,
it has to look like an accident.
If he dies with a knife in his
back no one will be there to pick you up.
Good luck.
- Who the hell is that?
- Krill.
He was an executioner for
people like Charles Taylor…
and the Sudanese militia.
People say he ate
the hearts of his victims.
Some have relatives who want revenge.
Like that guy over there.
He used to be Krill's best assassin.
Now all he wants to do is kill him.
But he has his bodyguards
constantly protecting him.
You're a good man.
Why don't you join us for dinner?
I'm not sure I like the company.
Then they are not invited.
Hey. Come, come.
Come in my friend.
There are six murders and twenty-three
stabbings every week in this shit hole.
Most of them pointed at me.
That guy you stopped.
He used to work for me.
Oh maybe he is still
upset that I killed his brother
Loyalty is a scarce commodity
in my line of business.
Oh yes! How did you know that
he would want to kill me?
I hear things.
My ju-ju tells me everything
that I need to hear.
Maybe you weren't
listening hard enough.
Do you know who I am?
Krill. You run this place.
Exactly. And when I get of this place,
I'm going to run all of Africa!
There could be a
job for a man like you.
I already have a job.
- What job?
- You.
Let the man pray.
Here he comes.
He's right below us.
Bring up the net.
Nothing in the net, sir.
What the fuck'?
Looking for someone?
I want my call.
Bishop survived.
- Hello, Arthur.
- Happy now?
Nice work on Krill.
Prison food'll kill you.
Put Gina on.
Here's your boyfriend.
Hi.
- How are you holding up?
- I'm okay.
Crain wanted me to let you  know that um…
you have 36 hours to eliminate the
next target or they will eliminate me.
That won't happen.
Okay, this is all very sweet, Arthur.
But you heard what she said.
You need to pick up the pace.
This is your next kill. Adrian Cook.
Did Bishop tell you where he got this?
It belonged to his father.
I never saw him take it off. Never.
You know, I wasn't sure there was a thing
in the world that could break Arthur.
Until I saw you wearing this watch.
Now I know he'll do anything for you.
In the heart of downtown
Sydney at top of 58th story high rise,
is a penthouse suite
owned by Adrian Cook.
The mining and minerals millionaire.
Few people know that he originally
made his fortune in human trafficking.
Specializing in underage sex workers.
He has plenty of manpower
protecting him of course.
But that's the least of it.
There you go. The Sydney Opera house
and the Harbor Bridge.
Cook's paranoia is only trumped by his ego.
Exhibit A. His cantilevered pool.
The walls and floors are all concrete.
3-feet thick.
Every door is made of
6-inch nickel chromium steel.
That's like 12 armor plates.
And the biometric sensors and retinal readers
at the access points are impossible to hack.
It's a fortress in the sky.
Mr. Clark. Good to meet you.
Shall we?
So each apartment has only 300 square
meters of premium living space.
But this one gets the Sydney sunset.
The specifications are all in the brochure.
Let me show you the detail floorplan.
You've got Italian tiles
running completely across here.
- Oh, excuse me.
- Sure.
Hello? Samantha Burns.
Hello?
Sorry about that.
So where were we?
- You were about to tell me about the floorplans.
- Oh, yes.
But we're not dumping on the reef.
Near is not on.
Yeah. That's right.
Now I've gotta go.  Now I've gotta go.
Billionaire Adrian Cook plunged from
the 56th floor to his death
this morning when the glass pool of his Sydney
penthouse collapsed. Although authorities--
- Give him his call.
- Okay.
…death as a tragic accident
effectively ruling out foul play.
- Ready.
- Go ahead.
Bishop.
Your watch has stopped.
I think it's a sign.
Maybe it just needs cleaning.
No, closer.
Son of a bitch!
- Hello?
- It's the harbor master's office?
Yes, how may I assist you?
My name is uh, Tom Silva.
Some bastard in a bloody grave
yard just screwed my vessel.
Uh, I have the hull number, but my insurance
needs the owner's details.
- Alright. Go ahead.
- WRX-489-674-2239.
Okay. Give me one moment.
The vessel's berth is in Sydney
Harbor on Pier 7. That's about it.
The boat you're looking
for is gone, mate.
It's a big one, too.
Head out of the harbor.
It couldn't have gone far.
It's your money, boss.
There. East.
Come out of the sun so he can't see you.
Drop it down to 60 feet.
Hold it steady.
Bishop.
You know your problem, Bishop?
You just can't help yourself.
That's how I knew you'd come back for her.
That's your weakness.
Now do the third kill, or the girl's dead.
Take him down below.
And give him a proper sendoff.
Bishop, if you pull another
stunt like that, our deal is off.
And you'll never see
your little girlfriend again.
Now, playtime is over .
Go to the port town of Varna.
On the Black Sea.
That's where you'll find your third kill.
His name is Max Adams.
A wealthy American arms dealer.
On the north side of Varna, you'll find a
truly vulgar memorial to Bulgarian communism.
Adams spent a fortune restoring it.
They're putting in the most
comprehensive security system.
But the interesting part
is what you don't see.
Hidden in the mountainside below is the subpen.
Adams stocks his U boats with
intercontinental ballistic missiles.
Nobody gets in or out.
Many have died trying.
So needless to say, this will be
the hardest sub to penetrate by far.
On top of all that, Krill and Cook's deaths
may have Adams on the defense.
You have 24 hours.
You're using me to take out the competition.
We will dispatch the helicopter.
Once you reach the compound, you'll have
to deal with several waves of security.
The building has its own power system,
oxygen supply and a state of the art panic room.
Good luck, brother.
Open the goddamn door.
Please.
Call me when you know something.
No sign of the intruder, Mr. Adams.
That's because he's sitting right in
front of me here in the safe room, jackoff.
Magnificent.
Even if you have all stolen and looted.
(inaudible) features totalitarianism.
Of course it's magnificent.
- Like uh, dinosaur bones.
- It's ugly.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm here to talk.
Lose your cell phone?
I should've hired
those guys in Houston.
Alright, what is it you want to talk about?
I want to help you avoid an accident.
Krill, Cook, that was you.
I warned those guys that one day
Crain would come after all of us.
Cappuccino? Espresso?
Espresso. No sugar.
Krill was a warlord but also the
number one arms dealer in Africa.
Cook used his mining empire as a cover
to control the Asian franchise. You...
have got Europe and most of South America.
North America too,
if you count Mexicans.
That didn't leave much for Crain.
So I have a deal for you.
Hmm. Well, I'm a dealer.
We can talk about it.
I have been called a lot of
ugly names over the years.
Communist, socialist, racist, fascist.
None of which is true of course.
Well, I'm certainly not a communist.
- You just admire their architecture.
- I believe in fair play.
I saw the David and Goliath story play
out on the frontlines of Vietnam.
Soviets in Afghanistan. Ethnic cleansing in Bosnia.
Chemical weapons on the Kurds.
The little guy is always gonna need a slingshot,
and somebody's always gonna pay for it.
An arms dealer with a moral clause.
Uh-hmm.
Let's talk about Crain.
We both need him gone.
The question is how do we accomplish that.
He's got an army around him.
We need something tempting enough so
that Crain uses his men to go after it.
What do you have in mind?
Your submarine pen.
Have them search for weapons,
treasure... your corpse.
What?
You'll have to die.
Well, that's easy. Although it will cost
a tremendous amount of money.
You can afford it.
Are the boats all secured?
Yes, sir.
- Batteries charged?
- Yes, sir.
- Fully provisioned?
You got those Russian girls
in here last night for the crew?
Yes, sir.
Well, looks like we're ready to go.
Stay here.
There was an explosion and
Mr. Adams slipped into the water.
His security, they tried to reach him.
But the rocks came down and he
was buried under the water.
Gone.
I never imagined dying would be
so goddamned invigorating.
Stay out of sight for two days. After that,
you can invigorate all you want.
You calling for the driver?
Making dinner reservations?
Checking in with mom?
I'm calling Crain to make
sure he takes the bait.
You do know how to put on a show.
There's a pier a few miles north of
Varna. Be there tomorrow with the girl.
Not until I see Adams' body.
You'll find him with his most prized possessions.
In his submarine pen.
Get over there.
Find Adams' body.
Secure everything inside the pen.
And uh, what about Bishop?
Kill him.
Jeremy, point the camera
forward so I can see.
All right. Let's go.
Fan out.
Where the hell is Bishop?
Clear.
2,1 clear.
Contact right rear.
Take cover.
Motherfucker!
- Anything?
- No sign of him, Mr. Crain.
Stay sharp. Bishop's coming.
You can count on it.
- What is going on?
- Your boyfriend is coming to die.
And you're the bait. Move.
Come on, Bishop.
I know you're not gonna let her die.
Bring her to the bridge.
Let's move.
Let's go. We got three
minutes before it blows.
Gina. You okay?
I'll be fine.
Let me see. Ah, shit.
I saw Crain doing
something on the console.
- What is going on?
- Crain is trying to kill us.
Let's go.
- Get this shit on the boat now.
- Yes, sir.
What is this?
Just get in.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Making sure you'll live.
No. Come with me! Bishop!
- Here he is!
- Bishop!
Find him…now!
Got him. Move!
Fletcher!
Let's get going.
- You never asked why ?
- I know why.
'Cause I got out, and you didn't.
And here we are again.
You deserted me.
It's time you paid for that.
No chance.
You're gonna get your third kill
This one won't look like an accident.
You're a dead man, Bishop.
You might get off the boat, but you'll never
swim far enough away before she blows.
Who said I was swimming?
Bishop!
Hey!
Were there any survivors?
No.
That's the anchor compartment.
Nothing more out there.
Bishop never made it.
Even legends die.
Dear…Mei. I'm back in
Cambodia with the kids.
The water filter's working.
Thank you so much
for your generous gift.
You have to come here some day.
I think you'd like it a lot.
Bishop would have loved it.
See you soon. I hope.
Lots of love. Gina.
Self-contained reinforced chamber
to house the anchor chain of any ship.
Steel chamber containing trapped air, allowing
divers to breath normally while submerged underwater.
Clever son of a bitch!
Sneaky bastard!
Bang, you're dead.
Subtitled created by Freaky.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org