♪Subtitles by ♪  XQ2☻♥
Play one of the best new FPS shooters,
search Steam for PROJECT WARLOCK
[FLYING DUTCHMAN]
- Father.
- Henry. What have you done?
- I said I'd find you.
- Look at me, son.
- I don't care!
- There's no place for you on the Dutchman.
They know you're here.
Get home to your mother.
No!
- Leave now, before it's too late.
- I won't!
I'll never stop.
And if you throw me over,
I'll come straight back!
Don't you see,
I'm cursed to this ship?
That's why I'm here. I think I know
a way to break your curse.
To free you from the Dutchman.
- Henry, no.☻
- I've read about a treasure.
A treasure that holds
all the power of the sea.
The Trident of Poseidon
can break your curse.
Henry.
The Trident can never be found.
I found you.
It's just a tale.
Like the tales of you
and Captain Jack Sparrow?
- He will help me find the Trident.
- You stay away from Jack!
Leave the sea forever.
You have to stop acting like a...
A pirate? I won't stop.
I want you to come home.
Henry.
I'm sorry.
My curse will never be broken.
This is my fate.
You must let me go.
I love you son.
Captain Jack Sparrow.
[Nine years later]
Faster you pathetic bilge rats!
Pump the bilge and fill the scuppers.
We're chasing down pirates!
Henry get back here. You don't wanna
get kicked off another ship.
It's a Dutch bark.
Probably stolen by the Pirate Bonnet.
My God.
I warned you of leaving your post, boy.
I need to speak with the captain.
- What did you say?
- Move!
She's going in, sir.
Chase her down.
No, don't do it!
Don't do it
You will not address a Captain, boy.
Sir, look at your charts, I believe
you're sailing us into the Devil's Triangle.
Do you hear this man?
This landsman, believes an old sailor's myth.
Sir, with all due respect
I have spent my life studying,
the myths of the sea.
I know every legend and every curse.
And I know, ships that sail into the
triangle do not necessarily sail out.
I'm sorry sir.
- This one is clearly disturbed.
- Sir, trust in what I say. Change your course.
You dare to give me orders, boy?
Arrest him!
Turner!
I'll not let you kill us all.
Come on.
This is treason.
- Lock him up. - No.
- We're going in!
This was your last chance, Turner.
If it were up to me,
I'd string you from the yardarm.
On deck!
Jack Sparrow.
He's dead.
Buried in an unmarked grave
on the Isle of St. Martin.
[UNCHARTED WATERS]
Sir, there's something in the water.
Ship to starboard!
That's no ship, sir,
it's a shipwreck.
No...
She's sailing straight toward us.
Open fire!
What are you?
Death.
Jack Sparrow.
Do you know this pirate?
- Only by name.
- You're looking for him?
- Is that a yes?
- Yes.
For too many years
the Triangle has cursed us.
Condemned us
to this Hell on Earth.
The key to our escape
Is Jack Sparrow and the compass,
which he holds.
No, no. No need to fear me boy.
I always leave one man alive,
to tell the tale.
Find Sparrow for me and relay
a message from Capitán Salazar.
Salazar.
Tell him I will behold
the daylight again.
And on that day...
...death!
Death comes straight for him.
Would you say that to him?
Please? - Yes.
I wish I could do it myself, but...
dead men tell no tales.
[SAN MARTIN, THE CARIBBEAN.]
- Carina Smyth.
You're an orphan,
born of the devil.
Accused of practicing witchcraft.
Before you die.,
do you have anything to confess?
I confess that I am not a witch,
that I'm a woman of science.
I confess that I have survived on my own,
with nothing but a diary
from a father I never knew,
and a quest for the truth
of who I am.
I confess that I will die
before I give up this search.
And I confess,
that while we've been talking,
I pinched this lock.
Today we dedicate
The Royal Bank of St. Martin...
the most secure banking institution
in the Caribbean!
Our new vault is 5 inches thick,
and weighs an imperial ton.
I've got her! I've got her!
Get her!
Don't let her get away.
Stop that witch!
With this bank,
the town of St. Martin,
enters the modern world.
I'm so sorry, sir, the witch
escaped her chains.
Find that wicked lass,
or you swing in her place.
- Sir.
No man, nor army,
can ever rob the gold from St. Martin.
Open the vault!
Pirates!
Pirates?
This may seem a peculiar request,
but, could someone explain to me
as to why I'm here?
How long?
No, no, wait, it's coming to me.
Need just a moment to clear me head.
Make ready!
Hold your fire!
There's a woman with him in the vault.
Never mind about that trollop!
Sir, I believe that's your wife.
Frances?
Oh, I've got it!
I've got it.
I'm robbing the bank!
Shoot him!
That was not part of the plan.
Stop him, don't let him get away!
No woman's ever handled my Herschel!
Clear a path!
No, no, no!
Stop, stop, stop!
Hard a-starboard!
There, your celestial fix was off.
I've adjusted it two degrees north.
Your map will no longer be imprecise.
Though you will have to
start again with it.
- You're a witch!
- No, I'm not.
Am I a witch for having
catalogued over 200 stars? - Witch!
There's a Bloodmoon coming.
I simply need to purchase
a chronometer.
I pay you double for
selling to a woman.
Help!
Help, there's a witch in my shop!
And a pirate!
There's a witch and a pirate in my shop!
Well it's your lucky day!
Have either of the four of you
seen my bank?
Found it.
- Were you part of the plan?
- I'm not looking for trouble.
What a horrible way to live.
- Stop that Witch! Get her!
- We're trapped.
What do we do?
You need to scream.
Over there! Secure that woman!
- You filthy pirate!
- No need for name-calling!
Jack!
Bridge?
It's empty!
Where is the dosh?
Do you think that
robbing a bank is easy?
You gaggle of gutless eels,
are the ones guilty of
putting me in this dreadful
pickle in the first place.
Now line up
and offer me a tribute.
You want us to pay YOU?!
Am I not the captain of this ship?
You call this a ship?
- Where's the treasure?
- All of us are starving.
We'll no longer follow a captain
without a ship.
I have a ship.
Black Pearl has never left me side.
The pirate Barbossa
rules these seas now.
Has 10 ships. Guns full.
Not to mention his canon balls.
18 pounds each they say.
One legged man with 18 pound balls?
That's why he walks funny.
Oh, come, come mates!
Did we not find the
treasure of Macedonia together?
It was a trawl of rotten wood.
- Gold of King Midas.
- Pile of donkey dung.
Face it Jack, bad luck dogs you,
day and night.
Now that is a blatant fabrication!
- You've lost your luck.
- You've lost your ship.
Now, you've lost your crew.
Jack Sparrow is no longer
our captain.
I'm sorry Jack. But we've
reached the end of the horizon.
Right, then!
You're all dismissed!
Eh?
All of ya, dismissed!
Never sail with Captain
Jack Sparrow again. Tell you that!
The whole town speaks of you.
The only survivor of the Moray.
A boy who peaddled all the way to St Martin,
against the tide, on a piece of driftwood.
Now, jabbering about pirates.
And tridents.
Please sir, let me go off these chains.
My job is to protect this island
and these waters.
And your sleeves have been ripped;
the mark of treason.
- We were attacked by the dead.
- You're a coward who ran from battle.
And that is how you die.
- I don't believe you're a coward.
- Please leave me, Sister.
I've risked my life to come here,
to see if the rumors are true.
- You speak of the Trident?
- Who are you?
- Tell me why you seek the Trident?
- The Trident can break any curse at sea.
My father is trapped by such a curse.
You're aware that curses
are not supported by science.
- Neither are ghosts.
- So you have gone mad?
- I should never have come here.
- Then why did you come here?
Because I need to get off
this island, to solve the map...
...no man can read,
left by Poseidon himself.
- You've read the ancient texts?
- In each language they were written.
But this map has never been seen
nor read, by any man.
Luckily, I'm a woman.
This is the diary of Galileo Galilei.
He spent his life
searching for the Trident,
It's why he invented the spyglass.
Why astronomers have spent
their lives staring into the sky.
So you're saying,
the map no man can read,
is hidden in the stars?
It was left to me by my father.
He believed I could find
what no man has ever found.
I will not let him down.
Soon, there will be a Bloodmoon.
Only then can the map be read
and the Trident found. - Who are you?
Carina Smyth!
If you wish to save your father,
you'll have to save me.
Find us a ship
and the Trident will be ours.
Answer me Witch!
Oh!
He's gone!
He's gone, sir.
Find that coward.
He'll hang with the witch.
Think Cap'n Jack's washed up, eh?
I've not had a wash in years.
Check the alley down there.
You two, check the church.
The rest of you, with me!
Bugger!
- May I please have a drink, please?
- Show me your silver.
Silver?
How about a trade?
Give me the bottle.
Capitán!
What's happening?
Jack Sparrow, Jack Sparrow
has given away the compass.
Daylight! Daylight!
We are free!
Now, now, it's time,
to hunt a pirate.
Pirate's life.
Come to Daddy.
- Just the man we've been looking for.
- Why? Why am I looked for?
Let it be known that the pirate
Jack Sparrow will be executed at dawn.
Executed?
I will never set foot in this town
again, sir. Ye mark my word!
I do mean it.
I shall never be back here again!
To release the power of the sea.
One must divide.
It's an island.
The stars lead to an island.
- I'm looking for a pirate, Jack Sparrow.
- Bugger off!
I need to speak with you.
- Hand me your sword.
- I don't have a sword.
- What kind of soldier has no weapon?
- I'm currently wanted for treason.
So, not a very good kind.
I'm looking for a pirate,
Captain Jack Sparrow?
Today is your lucky day.
Because I just happen to be
Captain Jack Sparrow.
No, it can't be.
I've spent years searching for this?
The great Jack Sparrow is not some
drunk in a cell.
Do you even have a ship?
A crew?
Pants?
A great pirate does not require
such intricacies.
Do you know how long I've
been waiting for this moment?
The risks I've taken to be here?
- Are you sure you're the Jack Sparrow?
- The real question is, who are you?
My name is Henry Turner.
Son of Will Turner and Elisabeth Swann.
You're the evil spawn of them two?
- Does mommy ever ask about me?
- No.
Go on! Does she calls my name
in her sleep?
She never spoke of you.
Are you sure we're talking
about the same people?
He's a chaste eunuch.
She's a golden haired, stubborn,
pouty lips, neck like a giraffe,
- and two of the most wonderful...
- Yes, yes, it's her!
I need you to listen Jack, because
at the moment you're all I've got.
I found a way to save my father.
There is one thing that can break his curse
and free him from the Dutchman.
The Trident of Poseidon.
The treasure that can be found with
the map that no man can read.
Never heard of it.
There is a girl inside this prison,
Jack, who holds that map.
The moon has turned to blood,
the Trident will be found.
And you could be the one
who holds the sea,
and with it become all
that you once were.
The great...
Jack!
Oh, I'm so sorry, were you still talking?
I believe I nodded off, there.
One more thing.
A message from someone you know,
named Captain Salazar.
I once knew a Spaniard named...
...something in Spanish.
El Matador Del Mar,
The Butcher of the Sea.
Him? No, no. Quite happily, he's dead.
Very, very, dead. Ship went down!
Inside the triangle.
He's coming for you Jack, to seek revenge,
as the dead man's tale is told.
I don't believe you.
What did he say?
He said your compass was
the key to his escape.
An army of dead are coming
straight for you, Jack.
The Trident of Poseidon
is your only hope.
Do we have an accord?
I'm not going in there to tell him.
It was your idea.
No, it was my idea for you
to tell him.
- He likes you more than me.
- He doesn't like anybody.
Sorry, sir, we know you said
never to disturb you,
or to come in without good cause.
Or to speak without first...
asking ourselves whether our
thoughts were absolutely necessary.
Like the time the ship was on fire.
That being an example
of necessary thought.
So, again, we do apologize
for starting that fire.
Speak!
It's the ships, sir, they're being attacked
by an enemy that takes their Riches.
Kills without provocation.
My ships?! Not possible.
Three have already been sunk, Sir.
They've been sunk by a captain
called Salamander.
Samovar.
Salazar!
That's it, your Sirness!
He leaves one man from each vessel
to tell the tale.
The entire fleet is being sunk,
and will soon be dead.
And quite possibly out of business.
I'll be needing some time
with your witch.
I've been expecting you Captain.
Perhaps you'd like some tea.
I shall pass, thank you kindly.
The price of crossing my door
is blood, Captain.
That explains why you're not so busy.
Everyone pays, eventually.
Shansa, you and I made a bond long ago.
I saved you from the gallows,
remember?
And I cursed your enemies.
But now you come to me in fear,
as the dead are taking
command of the sea.
And what would the dead
be wanting with me?
Not you, Captain.
- They're searching for a Sparrow.
- Jack?
Jack who sails for the Trident
with a girl and a Pearl.
The Trident can never be found.
The Trident is Jack's only hope.
The dead are conquering the sea,
unable to step on dry land.
Maybe you should retire
to the countryside.
Do you mean grass?
On a farm?
Milking a cow? Making cheese?
- While they sink me treasure?
- Ask yourself this, Captain.
- Is this treasure worth dying for?
- I'm a pirate.
Always will be.
So how do I save, what be mine?
Jack held a compass, which points
you to the thing you desire most.
But, betray the compass,
and it releases your greatest fear.
And a pirate's greatest
fear'd be Salazar, is it?
- How did you get this?
- I have my ways.
Lead them to Jack
before he finds the Trident.
And all your treasure
will come back to you.
Time to make a deal
with the dead.
Come on, pirate.
Hold on, stop.
- Uncle Jack!
- Jackie boy, how's it goin'?
Can't complain, really. You?
I've been waiting all morning in here,
for a beating.
- But the service is terrible.
- Shameful.
Jack.
The oceans have turned to blood.
Best stay on dry land,
where it's safe.
- I'm about to be executed on dry land.
- Good point.
Did I ever tell you the one
about the skeleton?
Yes you have, many times.
Skeleton goes into a bar,
orders a beer and a mop.
Funny as ever.
Come on, let's go!
If they disembowel you, ask for Victor.
He's got the softest hands.
Thank you.
And mention my name,
they won't cut your feet off.
Come on, you're first!
How would you like to die, pirate?
Hanging, firing squad or
a new invention,
- the guillotine.
- Guillotine?
Sounds french. I love the French.
Did you know that they
invented mayonnaise?
How bad could it be?
It's French, right?
Oh, my bad, I changed me mind!
No please have mercy upon me.
I, I'm a bed-wetter.
Oh, come on! I mean I have to
walk upstairs as well for this?
- Bring the basket.
- Basket, why?
Strap him down!
Here's an idea.
Why don't we try good old fashioned stoning, eh?
I'd kill to be stoned right now.
Gets the crowd involved, doesn't it?
I should like to speak to Victor,
in disembowelment.
I should like to speak to Vic...
I, I'm not one to complain, normally,
but this basket's full of heads.
Final words of Carina Smyth. QUIET!
The final words of Carina Smyth,
who says, I'm not a witch.
But I forgive your common dim
wittedness and feeble brains.
In short,
most of you have the mind of a goat.
Pardon me sir, is it not common practice,
for those about to be executed,
to be granted a last,
I don't know, something or other?
I believe I was making a point.
If you could just be patient.
No!
My head's about to be lopped off,
hence the urgency.
And my neck is to be broken.
Did you know that on occasion,
the neck doesn't actually break.
- It just hurts.
- What? - Oh Yes.
I have seen men swing for hours.
Eyes bulging, tongues swelling.
- Revolting gurgling sound.
- May I finish?
No! You're lucky. Wish I was hung.
- Kill the filthy pirate, I'll wait.
- The witch is first.
I'm not a witch.
Did not you listen?
Quite hard to listen
when you have the mind of a goat.
Enough! Kill them both.
Yes!
Get another noose.
Did you think you could defeat us, boy?
No sir, I'm just a diversion.
FIRE!
Still rather be stoned!
Reload!
Thank you.
C'mere, you pirate scum!
Hey!
What you doin'?
No, no, no, no!
Horses?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome Milady.
Got you!
Knew you'd come crawling back, traitor!
The Turner boy gave us
10 silver pieces to save your neck.
From this moment on,
we are to be allies.
Considering where your left hand is,
I'd say we're more than that.
We'll find the Trident together.
Do I have your word?
You're holding everything but my word.
Then I bestow upon you the honor
of saving me, for a small donation.
You expect us to pay you,
to save you?
Yes!
For a mere 10 pieces.
Madness!
- We won't pay more than 5!
- Well, then, 8 it is.
Perhaps we could discuss this later,
as I'm having trouble hoisting your port.
- You're far from port, that is my stern.
- Are you sure? - Positive.
Well, look at this!
If I kill the coward, the witch hangs.
- Two for the price of one.
- Please don't let go of me.
Might be difficult once he kills me.
Gentlemen, these two prisoners
will lead us to the Trident.
- Captain. - Hm? - Do you really
think we can find the Trident?
Master Gibbs, you old worrywart,
there's nothing to be concerned about, at all.
What could possibly go wrong, eh?
So this was your plan?
To be tortured and killed by pirates?
- You said you needed a ship.
- You call this a ship?
Cut the shaft!
Prepare the crows.
My dear beloved crew, finally, today is...
Something's gone wrong.
She floats!
Ship, dead ahead!
Sir. We would never
question your reason as a captain.
But, uh,
is there a reason, as captain,
you've chosen to sail in this
unreasonable direction?
Tell the men to prepare to be boarded,
to stand their ground and show no fear.
Capitán! A ship sails toward us.
Capitán Salazar, I hear you've
been looking for Jack Sparrow.
Hold point!
And await orders.
My name's Captain Barbossa
I stand before you,
- with cordial intent.
- I don't need any cordial intent.
Do you hear that?
The pirate wishes to be cordial.
So let me show you
what my cordiality is, hombre.
Every time I tap my sword.
One of your men will die,
so I suggest you speak quickly.
Oye ahí!
Might want to go a bit faster Capitán.
- Where is Jack Sparrow?
- Jack be sailing for the Trident.
- No, the sea belongs to the dead.
- The Trident controls the seas.
No, no! There's no treasure.
There's no treasure
that can save him.
He will die, as will you.
I be the only one
that can lead you to him.
I declare you shall have
Jack's life by sunrise on the morrow,
or you can take me own then.
Do we have an accord?
Take me to him and you will live
to tell the tale.
You have my word.
I thank you on behalf of me crew.
Olé! You can take what's left them.
The living, come aboard!
Carina, we haven't got much time,
the dead are sailing straight for us.
- Is that so?
- Yes, I've spoken to them.
You spoken to them?
Have you spoken to the Krakens
and the mermaids as well?
Krakens don't speak, everyone knows that.
- Of course.
I never should have saved you.
Last night there was a Bloodmoon,
just as you described.
- Tell me what it revealed.
- Why should I trust you?
You trusted me to hold your port,
remember? - It was my stern.
Clearly you need to spend
more time at sea.
Tell me what you found
and I promise to help you.
- I don't need any help.
- Then why did come to me Carina?
Why are we tied together in the middle
of the sea, chasing the same treasure?
The moon revealed a clue.
To release the power of the sea,
one must divide.
Divide?
- What does it mean?
- I'm not sure yet.
Then we'll find out.
- There is no map in this map.
- Give me my diary.
Give me the map no man can read.
If you could read it, then it wouldn't
be called 'the map no man can read'.
I beg you please,
don't argue with her.
Most of the men on this ship can't read.
Which makes all maps,
'maps that no man can read'.
Well if you can't read it,
then you have no use for it, or me.
Let me start again.
Show me the map.
I can't. It doesn't yet exist.
- She's a witch!
- I'm an astronomer.
- She breeds donkeys.
- What? No.
- An astronomer contemplates the sky.
- Yeah, on a donkey!
- No, there's no donkey!
- Well then how do you breed then?
Allows me to simplify this equation.
Give me the map...
or I will kill him.
I'll kill him.
Go on then. You're bluffing.
And you're blushing.
Throw him over.
We call this keelhauling.
Young Henry will be tossed over,
and he will be dragged under the ship.
Alright.
- What're you waiting for?
- He doesn't appear to be bluffing.
No. Not bluffing, me.
He's trying to say something.
No, no, we don't have any
food aboard. Sorry.
If he's lucky, he'll drown before
the barnacles shred him to ribbons.
- Barnacles?
- Like a thousand knives across your back.
'Course, the blood attracts sharks.
- Sharks?
- Shark off the bow!
- Where?
I would say that swimming
is no longer his primary concern.
The map is there.
- Where?
- On the tip of your finger?
No. In the heavens.
That diary will lead me to a map,
hidden in the stars.
Let him up, I'll find it tonight.
Sorry, can't bring him up.
Look for yourself.
As I said: blushing!
Filthy pirate!
The sea has turned to blood.
A sailor washed ashore
talking about the Trident.
He was looking for Jack Sparrow.
The same pirate who saved a witch
from the gallows.
- She's no witch.
- But you are.
- And you're going to help us.
- You're afraid, Lieutenant.
As ships burn in the night, you want
to know if you can save your own.
If the Trident is real.
You're going to read that
wall for me, or you will die.
The British Empire will have
the Trident and rule the sea.
I want to know where that
pirate is going with that witch.
Your destiny is in these stars.
I will set your course.
Oh! Spaghetti balls!
Why did I bother coming to you?
The dead are hunting us down
and you do nothing.
- Nothing? You call this nothing?
- You're drunk and you're sleeping!
My point exactly,
I'm doing two things at once.
You can't save the unsaveable mate.
Like it or not, Jack,
you're going to help me.
I will break my father's curse.
Next time you raise a sword, boy...
be the last to die.
Might I suggest you entice her
with a bit of flattery.
I am here for my father, nothing more.
I knew it, absolutely
smitten with'er.
Now, a bit of discretion
when courting a brunette.
Never pursue her sister.
But, if you cannot avoid
the charming sister,
kill the brother, savvy?
No, I do not savvy.
Who hurt you?
By the way that little sliver
of knowledge, cost you five pieces.
- I'm not paying you for that!
- Never say that to a woman.
Just because you can't see something
doesn't mean it's not there.
Like the map?
We have to find it.
It's the only link to who I am.
Who my father was.
So we've both spent our lives,
searching for our fathers.
Perhaps you and I
are closer than you think.
The sun is up and so is your time.
Not to disagree, but, the precision
of our accord ends at sunrise.
This be the first light,
far from a fully rising sun.
- And I know you to be a man of honor.
- Honor. You know nothing of me.
I know what it's like to be
bested by Jack Sparrow.
- He's an enemy to us both.
- You don't know who I am.
I've heard stories of a mighty
Spanish captain. El Matador Del Mar.
A man who scourged the sea,
hunted and killed thousands of men.
No-no-no. Men, no. No!
Pirates! Eh?
Pirates.
Pirates had infected the seas
for generations,
taking the life of my father
and his father before.
So I vowed to end this plague
once and for all.
And that's what I did.
I destroyed dozens of ships.
The last ones joined together
to try and defeat ME.
But they soon realized
it was hopeless.
Nothing could stop the Silent Mary.
Hit them below the water line.
Vamo, vamo!
Hang on boys!
The sea was finally pure.
Their wretched flags
would no longer stain the sea.
They are begging for mercy.
Mercy? Mercy?
There's no mercy.
Make ready...
Adios!
FIRE!
It's up to you now Jack.
This compass points towards
what you want most.
Never betray it.
The Devil's Triangle.
The last of their ships were
burning before my eyes.
And in that moment of victory,
it's when I heard it.
Hey!
Hold on, Capitán!
One ship was trying to escape
through the smoke.
It's a lovely day for a sail, innit?
And there, in the crow's nest,
there was this young pirate boy.
The way I see it,
it's just the two of us left.
You surrender to me now,
and I'll let you live. Simple.
He stood there, looking like
a little bird.
And from that day he earned himself
a name that would haunt me
for the rest of my days:
Jack the Sparrow.
Right then, you surrender to me
now and I'll let you live.
I shall let you live.
This boy...
This boy was mocking my power.
So I chased him, knowing that
I would run my knife along his neck
and when he was dead, I would finish,
finally, with the pirates's life.
Follow him in!
To the gallows!
Grab some lines!
Prepare the bootleg!
Port side.
Throw it now!
Bootleg curve!
What's all this?
Tribute, Sir.
He took everything from me,
and filled me with rage...
and pain.
And here's where the tale ends.
Not yet, Capitán.
There! Found, as promised.
So she's saying she's got the map,
but she's the only one who can follow it?
- So, we should shoot her?
- Leave her be.
- She will take us to the Trident.
- You've been saying that for hours.
Two things we know are true,
the stars don't shine by day.
And she forgot a donkey.
How can we go to a spot,
where no land exists on any map?
This chronometer
keeps the exact time in London.
I'm using it to make an altitude
measurement to determine longitude.
Only then will we find
our exact spot at sea.
So you expect to find the Trident
with a timepiece?
Yes.
My calculations are precise and true.
I'm not only an Astronomer,
I'm also a horologist.
No shame in that, dear.
I mean, we all have to earn a living, eh?
No, I'm a horologist.
So was my mum, but, she didn't
cry about it as loud as you.
Are you saying, your mother
was academically inclined?
More like a horizontally, reclined.
Horology is the study of time.
And she was always looking at her watch.
I can vouch for that.
- So, no one can find the X,
but you, right? - No.
- And the donkey?
- Ship to the aft!
Salazar.
Jack, the dead will not rest
until they get their revenge.
Dead?!
No, no, the dead were never
part of this deal.
We should'a never follow a
luckless pirate and a witch to sea.
Right, that's it. Kill them all.
Kill me and, and I'll be dead.
And then the other dead won't
be able to have their revenge.
- Against me... Being dead.
- What?
- Which will anger them even more.
- He's right.
That's right.
Are all pirates this stupid?
- Yes.
What are we going to do?
As Captain, might I suggest...
Mutiny?!
You had to suggest mutiny?
Carina, the dead are coming.
Well, I choose not to believe in
supernatural nonsense.
Do you not see what's behind us?
- Drop them!
- Si.
Drop them!
What're you doing?
Men on that ship are looking for Jack.
And Jack is on this boat.
I'm going to swim for it.
How dare you do exactly
what I would do, if I were you?
- Carina, stop.
- No-no-no, don't stop.
- This has gone far enough.
- No, it has not!
Listen not to him,
carry on, carry on!
- Why, she was almost finished.
- I saw her ankles.
You'd have seen a lot more,
if you'd kept yer cakehole shut.
Kill the Sparrow.
That's not good, is it?
Keep rowing man. Faster, faster!
No, that's it!
I'm going with her.
You would leave me for some
horologist in her knickers?
Yes.
You men are all alike.
Shark.
Henry!
- Doesn't seem to be working.
- No, we'll be fine, we'll be fine!
Vamo!
- How do they do that?
- We have to swim for it.
I'll distract them.
Now!
Shoo!
Henry!
Hey, Jack Sparrow.
Jack 'Esparrow'.
Spanish?
No, no... Ghosts!
Ohh...
They're unable to step on land.
I knew that, though.
Ghosts! Aahh!
Carina!
You will soon pay for what you did to me.
No-no-no. There's no
need to bother, really.
Carina!
I have no time to chat,
because me map just ran away.
I will be waiting for you.
Why would he be waiting for me?
Pirates!
- Scrum.
- Captain?
Jack always told me that
if anything should ever happen
to him, he wanted you to be captain.
Yeah, but the men voted for you, yes?
Well, you've got a captain's hat!
Be that as it may, them were his wishes.
So be a good lad and take the wheel.
And you, take the captain's hat.
Oh, it's the proudest moment of my l...
We will beat your captain to death,
until he reveals where they're heading.
- Carina!
- I know what's ailing you boy.
You've got the unscratchable itch.
Carina is the only one
who can help us find the Trident.
- And I'm not in love with her.
- Love?
Who said anything about love,
what are you talking about?
The unscratchable itch?
Scabies, I'm talking about scabies.
Small mites that burrow under the skin.
Certainly annoying me,
has done, for years.
Oh, no!
Help!
- Help me! Help!
- Carina!
- Henry, help me.
- Help her!
By rule of the King,
I sentence you all to death.
I think we should tell each other
where our treasures are buried,
just in case one of us survives.
Oh, good idea.
- You go first.
- My treasure is buried
between two crossed palm trees
in an unmarked grave in Aruba.
What about yours?
I haven't got any.
- You promised me Jack's blood.
- But Jack be trapped!
- He can never escape that island.
- HE'S ON LAND!
Hello.
I upheld our deal.
Me men and meself will go ashore.
The scurvy traitor
will be yours, on me honor.
Honor?!
What honor, hombre? What honor?
You don't know what honor is.
Spare me my life
and I'll fetch you the Sparrow.
First we must swear, though, an accord.
Wake up Sparrow.
Wake up, Sparrow.
It's time to pay your debt.
Pig?... Pig Kelly?
- Me old mate.
- Mate?!
D'you hear that boys?
This lyin' pirate owes me
a blunder of silver.
And luck has brought him to
Hangman's Bay,
where he can settle his debt,
here and now.
And I will, I will, Pig.
Name your price.
Her name is Beatrice.
And she's my poor widowed sister.
W-what is that?
She's been looking for
a respectable man.
- But you'll have to do.
- Right, let's get on with this.
- No! Why? Why?
- To make an honest woman of her, Jack.
Congratulations, it's your weddin' day.
Let us begin?
We'll honeymoon in the barn.
No-no-no. Now, Pig,
how could I honestly make
an honest woman out of it?
That. Her. I mean, her.
- What are those things?
- Our children.
Best not look them in the eye.
Bring the best man
and the bridesmaid.
I looked it in the eye.
Place your hand on the Bible.
- I have got scabies.
- So do I.
Place your hand on the Bible.
I'm a bed-wetter!
Say, I do.
- Or I'll put a bullet in your skull.
- Jack, they're going to kill us.
- I don't care!
- Just say, I do.
- Last chance, Jack.
- Wait. Surely, this is not legal.
This is not legal.
He's right.
Does any man here
object to these nuptials?
- I do.
- Congratulations.
You may kiss the bride.
Y-y-you...
You like seafood, do you?
Jack, we meet again!
Hector!
This is me bestest mate
in the whole world.
I always knew you'd settle down,
eventually.
Did you bring me a gift?
That'll do.
You look marvelous.
Got quite a spring in your step.
Has your leg grown back?
Captain, shouldn't we be getting
back to Salazar.
Trade Mr. Sparrow's life in
for our own?
Aye, that we could.
But I've come for the Trident of Poseidon.
You're gonna double cross the dead?
You, did, promise.
And with it I'll gut the dead
that stole my command of the sea.
As much as I love this plan.
No vessel can outrun that
wretched hull of a ship.
But there be one, Jack.
The fastest ship I know.
The pearl, trapped in that bottle
by Blackbeard, 5 winters ago.
By the power of that
blackguard's sovereign blade
I hereby release the Black Pearl,
to her former and rightful glory.
Get ready!
It's coming.
It's coming! It's coming!
Stand aside! Stand aside!
It's coming!
It's shrunken.
Why doesn't it unshrink?
Maybe it's cold.
She needs the sea!
She was a fine ship.
Let's...
There be room for only one captain.
- Oo, filthy beast.
- Time to raise the dead.
The only safe place is the land.
Why are we going away from the land?
Does anybody know?
Captain, your map is incomplete.
I can take us to the Trident,
if you'd only trust me.
Did you not hear anything I just said?
So you be saying, that,
that star is pretending to be a map?
Sir, there is no island on any map
to support what the woman says.
Captain, you don't have
to understand her.
Just believe her.
Anyone?
If we had something sharp,
I could pick that lock.
You're not gonna find
anything sharp in here.
Keep still you bilge rat!
Please, I don't wanna
be captain anymore!
Release them!
Sir, you wouldn't allow a woman
to steer your ship?!
She will follow her star,
or we'll all die together.
The Black Pearl!
She sails again!
Yeah!
This ship, those ghosts...
there can be no logical explanation.
The myths of the sea
are real, Carina.
I'm glad you can finally
see you were wrong.
Wrong?
Perhaps I had some doubts.
This is the worst apology
I've ever heard.
Apology? Why would I apologize?
Because we've been chased
by the dead, sailing on a ship,
raised from a bottle.
Where is your science in that?
Fine, I will apologize.
Go on, then.
Well then, one could argue that
you owe me an apology.
As my life has been threatened by
pirates and dead men.
Which you now believe in,
sorry to say.
Apology accepted.
I'm going to the lookout.
I'm glad you see it my way.
12 degrees to port!
- Ready the guns.
- Aye. Ready the guns!
These pirates are going
for the Trident.
Where did you get that from, Missy?
I know this book, stolen from
an Italian ship, many years ago.
Stolen?
No, you're mistaken.
There was a Ruby on the cover,
I would not soon forget.
This was given to me by my father.
He was clearly a man of science.
He was clearly a common thief.
The memory of my father will not be
befouled by the tongue of a pirate!
This diary is my birthright.
Left to me on the steps
of a children's home.
Along with a name and nothing else.
Oh, so you're an orphan?
What be you called?
The brightest star in the North
gave me my name.
- That would be Carina.
- Carina Smyth.
- So, you do know your stars?
- I'm a captain...
I know which stars to follow home.
Smyth?
Smyth is quite an unusual name.
Did we not, once, know someone
called Smyth?
- Shut your trap!
- What was her name?
It's right on the tip of me tongue.
- Do you wanna lose that tongue?
- Margaret Smyth!
Aye, so we make an accord then?
Or, shall I tell you know who,
what we both know is the truth.
- We both take this secret to our graves.
- You mean, it is true?
- I was bluffing.
- I'm not!
You kill me, you got nothing
to bargain the dead with.
So you need me.
I'll have to frank Hector.
You are very, very, ugly,
so how could you produce
a fetching creature, such as that?
Margaret died.
I summoned as much honor as a
worthless blackguard ever could.
I placed the infant in an orphanage,
never to see her again.
I thought the ruby might afford her
some ease in life.
But I never imagined
she'd take those scribblings
and make a life of her own.
A life that's led her back to me.
I'd say this puts me in a
rather favorable position, Daddy.
- Tell me what you want.
- I want me compass.
216 barrels of rum.
And the monkey.
- You want Jack?
- Dinner!
I want to eat him.
I want to eat that monk...
No deal Jack.
A clever young woman such as that,
would never believe that a swine
like me could ever be her blood.
And the Trident will be mine.
Redcoats!
- Prepare to fire!
She comes starboard!
We shall fight to the last.
The Pearl will not be
taken from me again!
Sir.
Only the British Empire
will hold the power of the sea.
What ever happens,
stay your course.
Jack Sparrow? Jack Sparrow?
I've come with the butcher's bill.
Where is he?
Defend yourselves, men, to the death!
Hurry up man!
What, did you sharpen it with butter?
There's nowhere to hide.
Let's be brave, save the Pearl!
This has to be it.
It has to be here.
Find that land, or we'll all die!
We're nearly there.
It's here, somewhere.
Have you found what
you're looking for yet, miss?
I'm trying!
The stars will soon be gone.
Carina!
Henry, look, the island is there!
You found it!
The island.
Land!
Get to the Mary!
Carina!
Henry!
They took Henry!
The Trident be all that can
save him, now.
Then we have to find it.
Where is it?
It has to be here.
Look at it Jack.
It's the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen.
This is what my father
wanted me to find.
- Rocks?
- No, not rocks, stars.
This is the map no man can read.
This island is a perfect reflection
of the heavens.
One star's missing.
Quickly!
We have to find the
Trident to save Henry.
Hector, I think you should know
she's a horologist.
Why isn't it glowing?
Finish it, Carina.
The missing star.
For my father.
Aye, do it for him.
There.
Poseidon's tomb!
This way.
Capitán, you know the danger.
Don't do it!
He has no choice.
Jack is on land going for the Trident.
Capitán, there must be another way.
Once you possess the living,
there's no coming back.
You will be trapped in his body, forever.
The Trident will set me free.
- Time to kill a sparrow.
- No!
- Look Jack, there it is.
- The Trident!
Jack!
You cut me, you cut the boy, Jack.
- Henry!
- No.
Hola, Sparrow?
No.
I hate the Sparrow. Die Sparrow.
No!
Henry, he's walking on land!
Please! Henry wake up!
Oh, piss off!
Henry wake up, he's killing Jack!
Henry!
- Power of the sea.
- What?
The power of the sea.
"To release the power of the sea
all must divide".
If the Trident holds
all the power, then...
Then every curse is held inside.
As I told you before,
surrender to me now
and I will let you...
...live.
- Do you want me to surrender?
- Maybe.
This is where the tale ends!
No!
Die!
Divide.
Henry!
Divide. Break.
Break the Trident and you'll
break every curse of the sea.
Adios, Sparrow.
All curses have broken.
Yeah!
We're flesh and blood!
- The Pearl! My Pearl!
- Climb.
Move, fast!
Hold it steady boys,
don't let it slip.
Jack!
Faster!
Hoist, anchor!
Get the anchor up, quick!
Stop, stop.
Bring it up, bring it up!
Capitán, Capitán!
Oh, crap!
I've got ya.
Who am I to you?
Treasure.
Hold on!
Hector!
Go to starboard!
Pirate's life, Hector...
You were right.
I don't know.
For a moment I had everything, Henry.
Now, it's all gone, again.
It's not all gone, Miss Smyth.
Barbossa. My name is Barbossa.
- Maybe Jack was right.
- About what?
The unscratchable itch.
Why did you do that for?
Just checking it's truly you.
You're not still cursed.
- It's me.
- Then I was...
- Wrong!
- Slightly in error.
Although, one...
Apology accepted.
The Dutchman.
- Henry.
- Yes, father.
Let me look at you son.
How did you do it?
- How did you break the curse?
- Let me tell you a tale.
A tale of the greatest
treasure known to man.
That's a tale I wanna hear.
What a truly revolting sight!
Make way!
Captain Jack Sparrow on deck.♥
Indeed!
Welcome back, Captain.
I thank you very much.
Coming through.
- Captain!
- Thank you, I remember you.
- Cheers, thank you.
- Oh good!
- Master Gibbs.
- The ship is yours Captain.
I thank you!
Monkey.
Thank you.
What be our headin' Cap'n?
We should follow the stars,
Master Gibbs.
Aye aye, Cap'n!
I have a rendezvous beyond my
beloved horizon.
♪Subtitles by ♪  XQ2☻♥
Craving big poker? Feast your eyes on Venom.
$5 million GTD. AmericasCardroom.com