Subtitle created by - Aorion -
"The Huntsman: Winter's War (2016)" ^ (Run time 01:52:51)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
What does the Mirror show you?
What do you see?
An oft-told tale,
that of Snow White.
How she vanquished the evil Queen Ravenna,
and took her rightful place on the throne.
But there is another story,
one you have not yet seen.
One that comes long before
"happily ever after".
THE HUNTSMAN
WINTER'S WAR
A mere pawn?
A humble pawn can bring down kingdoms.
Stop distracting me.
Poor little pawn.
Mean old king.
So sad.
But the final say...
Well.
Queen, will have that.
Queen takes king.
And you thought
this was just a game.
With the Mirror at her command,
Ravenna was invincible.
She took her kingdom
as she had taken others before it.
and as she would take
others again,
with her sister, Freya, at her side
Is it love?
Truly?
It is love, truly.
Your move.
Why should I bother?
You always win.
You always let me win.
I suppose you are my weakness.
Very well.
Queen to Rook five.
Checkmate in three.
Learn from lost, Freya,
and your day will come.
Your possibilities will be endless
once the magic awakens in your heart.
It won't.
We both know it won't.
I'm not like you.
All the women of our blood are gifted, Freya.
And in time...
you will find the source of your power,
as I've found mine.
We'll see.
What?
You're carrying his child.
Oh.
You didn't know.
Well.
- He's promised to another.
- He does not love her.
Their engagement is sealed
and cannot be broken.
He will deny you.
And he will deny your daughter.
He will not.
Freya.
I'm not being cruel.
I simply wish to protect you.
You may be surprised
how things turn out.
You know much, Ravenna.
But you do not know all.
I'm afraid I do.
Freya did not believe her sister.
For love blinds even the clearest eye.
And when her daughter
was but a few weeks old,
Freya's trusting heart was rewarded at last.
Her lover had sent word.
He would defile his family and marry
Freya in secret in the royal garden.
They would gather their child
and flee the kingdom
to begin a life of their own.
Freya, don't.
I had no choice.
I had no choice, Freya.
NOOOOO...OOO !
Consumed by grief and anger,
Freya left his sister to seek a kingdom
of her own in the land far to the north.
There, the people would come
to fear her very name.
Burn it!
Kill them all!
For if she could not raise a child,
then in it's place
she would raise an army.
Come on, boy!
- No!
Eric!
Run!
Come on, you runt.
Freya turned the once
green farm lands of the North
into a frozen wasteland.
There she built her fortress,
and rule as the Ice Queen.
Charrets!
How lucky you are.
You're with me now.
And you will never know
this suffering again.
You are scared?
No.
Is it your father that you missed?
Your mother?
- Yes.
Tell me your name.
Tull.
Love is a lie.
It is a trick played by the cruel
on the foolish and the weak.
Cast it from your mind.
Never let it render you
frail of mind, or of will.
Because in my kingdom
there is but one law:
"Do not love."
It's a sin,
and I'll not forgive it.
Now, let's hear no more
of family and love.
Those illusions are beneath you.
I have freed you from them.
And in exchange for this precious gift,
I ask only one thing.
Your loyalty.
You will train.
You will harden.
You will become my elite,
my Huntsmen.
And nothing will ever, ever
destroy you.
Take it!
One. Two. Three.
Strike!
And so, children grew to be soldiers.
Becoming one with blade and arrow.
Prepare your bows!
Draw!
Release!
Guard.
The boy and the girl.
Who are they?
What are their names?
- Which?
- The best ones.
Eric and Sara, my queen.
Did I scare you?
Do you not know?
I never miss.
More Charrets!
The new children, sir.
It's about time.
Come on, kids. Come on,
hurry up, get out. Come on.
Come on.
Don't worry.
Out!
Come on.
Move, faster.
Pssst.
What are you doing in there?
I know who lives here.
She scares me.
Uh, you're right.
She can be wee bit grumpy
from time to time.
Do you know what I do? I just never
let her know what I am thinking.
How do you do that?
Well, can you make a mean face?
That's not bad.
What about like this.
That's better.
Now, that's your war face.
If you wear that always
when the Queen is near,
she'll never know what
you're thinking either.
You do that and you'll be fine.
Come on.
The Queen sent her army to wage war
against the great kings of the North.
Battle after battle,
they returned victorious.
Those who were left alive.
You've done well, my children.
Very well.
You forget to walk in shadow.
And you forget your balance.
What are you doing?
Well, can't you tell, you daft boy?
I'm marrying you.
It was my mother's.
My only treasure.
I lived for her.
Now...
I live for you.
How do we live for each other
in this place here?
Freya will take one look at us
and she'll know, what then?
It's almost day.
Gather your things.
Meet me in the courtyard.
She'll catch us,
or she won't.
But either way...
we shall be free.
You do love me, don't you?
Aye, I do.
I give you my life and my death.
Stand or fall, I'll never leave your side,
I swear it to you.
I know this story.
The girl goes in secret
to meet her one true love.
I wonder how it ends this time.
I gave you both everything.
And in return,
you betray me.
For love.
We fought your wars.
We've done enough.
Please, my Queen,
let us go.
Do not beg me.
It is weak.
You are weak.
You want to leave?
Very well, go to each other.
If you can,
and I'll let you go.
Shouldn't be too hard.
Love conquers all.
So I've heard.
Take him out of my sight.
Once upon a time,
a man and a woman fell in love.
But such things cannot last.
For the heart is a treacherous thing.
And love...
Love is nothing more
than a fairy tale.
Days turn to years.
Freya's empire continue to rise.
While her sister, Ravenna's fell at the hands
of the Huntsman and Snow White.
But some evil...
cannot truly be vanquished.
Seven Years Later...
In The Kingdom Of Snow White.
Fan out!
Align the flanks !
See you later, love.
- Your Majesty.
- Please, my friend.
How did you find me?
It wasn't easy.
Oh, Nion.
- You sworn.
- Well, he...
He friends put me in a big...
big pot.
What nonsense.
We paid him 3 gold.
3?
Is that all?
3 each.
- Who are you?
- Gryff.
At your service.
Bonds, rewards, debt collection.
- I'm his brother.
- He, half brother.
- Same mom.
Walk with me.
I have come on a matter
of grave importance.
Well, you should find some
gravely important people then.
The Mirror is gone.
We believed it's dark magic
died with Ravenna.
We were wrong.
There is an evil within the Mirror
that has only grown in power.
The Queen Snow White has vowed
to rid her kingdom of it
before it's darkness cannot be stopped.
2 weeks ago, the Queen ordered
a detachment of soldiers
to take the Mirror to Sanctuary,
they never returned.
Wait, wait,
I'm not your man.
You're the best tracker
we have in the Kingdom.
As you say, the Mirror is evil,
it mustn't fallen into the hands
of the wrong person.
And Snow White thinks
I'm the one to find it?
She commands you
to find it.
And deliver it to Sanctuary where
it's wickedness can forever be contained.
Do you accept or not?
Yes, yes, yes.
He accepts.
Provided, there's a reward.
I don't want no reward.
Eric.
Snow White is unwell.
The Mirror...
She said she couldn't stop looking at it.
She can hear
it's voice calling for her.
That's why she sent it away.
What was that thing?
Move all your forces
to the northern border.
Why?
What do you know?
Freya, Queen of the North.
That owl was her spy.
Now, she knows about the Mirror.
And if she finds it, everything you
hold dear will be covered in ice.
Move your men to the north.
What are you two still doing here?
We are your partners.
No, you are not.
I am Snow White's men as well.
I mean-I mean dwarf.
If she's in trouble, I want to help!
My Queen.
Vardhelm has fallen.
It was the last stronghold.
The entire White Lands
are yours.
You've won.
Have I?
The game is not finished.
Is this where the world ends?
Or is there more?
My Queen,
the South cannot be conquered.
Snow White's lands are too vast,
her armies are...
Did you know that Eric was alive?
Did you?
I...
How?
- I swear to you I threw his body...
- That's alright.
I prefer it this way.
There's something that he seeks.
I want it.
My sister's mirror.
It holds great power.
And with it in my command,
I can do great things.
I will free every child.
I'll save them all,
as I've saved you.
And my army of Huntsman will grow
until nothing will stand in it's path.
So, you see,
the game is not finished.
Prepare the Huntsmen.
- They came through here.
- Obviously.
It's to access to the Northern road.
Leads directly to Sanctuary.
No need to be a Huntsman to know that.
Hey, Nion,
who am I?
I'm talking to the dirt.
I hear it speak to me.
He's actually quite good at this, Gryff.
He's stuff.
He's a buffoon.
We ride north.
Actually, they headed west.
The Northern road cuts through a plain
No where to take cover.
The Western road
runs next to a forest.
That's where they would have make camp.
That's where we're going to find them.
- Obviously...
- Shhh, shhh, shhhh.
- The dirt is talking to me again.
- What's it saying?
It's saying the mouthy one is an idiot.
He wouldn't last a day on his own
and should go home.
I agree.
I'm not going home
till I get my reward.
You want gold, but all you're going
to find out here is death.
A bit dramatic.
Dramatic, yeah, unless it's true.
We should consider it
an extra warning.
I know I'm not afraid
of Freya of the Frost.
Hey, not so loud.
Keep your voice down.
You're even more stupid than I thought.
Bloody hell.
Who would have attack them
out here in the open?
Keep your eyes peel.
They could still be around.
We'll look for tracks, blood trails,
anything.
Get off!
These are their own arrows.
Their own blades.
They killed each other.
But why?
These are all the Queen's men.
The Mirror was here.
This is definitely not one of theirs.
I grew up in the mines.
It's worth half the world.
Whoever it belongs to has the Mirror.
We need to find it
before Freya does.
What's this?
We have to get off the road.
I'm looking for... information.
You'll not get much for that.
Well, then.
There was a wee massacre
on the road not far from here.
The Queen soldiers.
You know anything about that?
Yeah, they passed through here
a few days ago.
- They did?
- They didn't stop. They weren't thirsty.
Was anyone...
anyone following them or...?
Oh, a pint as well.
I take that as a "No".
Good day.
A bit choosy for what she's offering.
Or perhaps you would have
better luck with your own kind.
Have you ever seen a female dwarf?
- No, I can't say I have.
- Horrifying.
Horrifying is the best of them.
Repulsive things.
So, assuming this is a
commonly held opinion.
How exactly are new dwarfs made?
Uh, generally by accident.
Too little light.
- Too much of this.
- Yeah.
Come on, keep up.
Chilly with that door.
Pass me that.
- What?
- I'll have some of my own.
That.
You 3 looked like
you're far from home.
Aye, aye.
Just seeking shelter and moving on.
Are these your children?
Your missus must be
quite a looker.
- That's a good one.
- What?
- What did he say?
- Leave it aside.
No, no, no.
I'm not having it.
You want to hold your tongue mate,
before you loose it.
Is that so?
Yeah, If it were just me own,
I wouldn't be worried.
If it's me and him,
I would be a tiny bit worried.
- Because he's a bit of a waster.
- Not true.
But none of that matters.
Because we are with him.
And he will gut you like a deer,
quicker than you can blink.
'Cos this man here...
This man is the Huntsman.
Is this true?
Are you the Huntsman?
That's me.
Well.
The thing is...
We are all Huntsman.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- It's alright.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait...
Can we not talk about this?
You call yourself a Huntsman?
I expected more from a man who had
the courage to betray his queen.
And for what?
For the love of some spineless woman.
Maybe you were something
in your day, brother.
But that day is long gone.
Have you made your peace?
I'll be, soon enough.
Tell Freya I died a free man.
Freya doesn't care how you die.
No one cares.
You're already forgotten.
Fall back!
Fall back now!
You have aged.
Sara.
Sara?
I tied you up.
Is she his wife or something?
No, it can't be.
His wife's dead.
Dead?
Is that what you told everyone?
You poor heartbroken widower.
That story must have wet
the eyes of many young lass.
Maybe more than their eyes.
No, no, no.
You're dead.
I saw you die.
This is not real.
It's not happening.
You're a ghost.
Or you're some...
Or some...
I'm dead.
Am I not alive?
You're alive.
Although you should be dead.
You got hit on the head like six...
- What do you say, six or seven?
- Seven.
Seven times is a lot.
- So, this is...
- Real.
Very!
Did you think I would forget?
Did you think I would forgive?
"Stand or fall", you said.
You'll never leave my side, you said.
You swore it.
And then you fled.
I see you fight
and I see you run.
No, no, no, Sara.
That's not what happened.
I saw Tull killed you.
I saw him killed you with my own eyes.
I would never leave you.
But I saw you leave me
with my own eyes.
And you of all people should know.
Tull could never kill me.
Sara.
I...
- Don't.
- I swear to you.
She put me in her dungeon
for 7 years.
And when I finally escape,
I swore I would find you.
It's taken me a long time.
But here we are.
Husband...
and wife.
You honestly believe that?
That I abandon you?
Aye.
You still forget your balance.
She's got another knife.
Yeah, yeah.
I probably should have said so.
She's got 2 more little ones
in her left boot.
That's no longer important.
If your face is the last thing
that I'm meant to see,
then I'm grateful.
It should be the last thing you see.
- I don't like her.
- No.
I don't like her one little bit.
My Queen.
No fire.
NO FIRE!
It's alright.
So.
What happens if Freya
gets this Mirror?
Don't you think that you and me,
have other things to discuss.
- Like us.
- No.
What happens?
She'll be unstoppable.
- Where's my horse?
- I sent if off.
- Why would you do that for?
- Them horses make tracks.
We keep off the road,
we'll be safe.
So, you're coming with me then?
No, you're coming with me.
Whatever you need to tell yourself,
that's fine.
From what I can see, your wee band
won't do too well without me.
Huh?
Whatever power this Mirror contains,
I'll not let Freya yield it.
We'll find it and we'll bring it
to the Sanctuary.
And then you and I...
will part forever.
Now.
Tell me about this.
We'll hit Callan Crossing by nightfall.
There's a market there,
they might have sold the Mirror.
If an enemy uses diamonds for arrows
I doubt if he'll sell
the Mirror for money.
Well, if you don't like my plan,
you can piss off.
Oh.
That is charming.
And you can piss off too,
you so elegantly put it.
But that's not going to
get rid of me.
You're still my wife.
We...we were deceived.
The ice wall that Freya
put between us,
she showed us
what she wanted us to see.
Wait.
And what if I'm right?
Do we not deserve that chance?
It wouldn't have matter.
You would leave again.
We blind ourselves to the truth
because we are weak,
because we hope.
But there's no hope for love.
Love ends in betrayal.
Aye, and always.
Well, I don't believe you.
Don't move.
That looks familiar.
A dwarf made trap.
That's where I would have put it.
Yes.
It will take more than that,
to catch the like of US !!!
Oh, no!
Curse the bugger.
What?
It was unexpected.
Oh. Oh what?
The hidden dwarf trap was unexpected?
You're not the tracker
you think you are.
I've been a little distracted.
Hey, Doreena,
we've got some of...
Catch of the day.
God, no.
Careful, sweetheart.
I wouldn't want to ruin that
pretty little face of yours.
Okay.
- Oh, boggle me.
- Oh, it's like that, is it?
See, you don't even know us.
What do I need to know,
you squawk face little he-dwarfs?
The sight of you clods
make me sick.
Shut your mouth, you monkey slag.
Shut yours, you grunty wanker.
Kiss my ass, you filthy minger.
Kiss mine, you wobbly shed box.
- Sorry.
- Madam Dwarf,
we have no quarrel with you.
We seek a mirror.
I don't got no mirror.
Ho, ho, that's clear.
Right.
Oh, you are getting...
No, no, no!
Enough, enough, enough.
Well, just tell us what you want.
Well, personally I like you to take
your shirt off and prance around me.
But since you're so modest,
I'll settle for every penny you got.
Aye, so it's money you're after.
My-My apologies.
All I have is this.
You know what this is?
It's a great big bullion diamond.
I'm not blind.
- Where did you get that?
- You let us down and I'll tell you.
Doreena!
Coming, Mrs. Bromwyn!
Keep an eye on this lot.
Shoot the he-dwarfs
if they get mouthy.
Oh.
Or you just feel like it.
- Hey, don't just cut it.
- Hey!
Whoooa!
You... you thirsty?
I could get you some water
if you like.
Oh. Yes, thank you,
I like that a lot.
Aw.
I mean, no.
I don't want nothing
from the lots of you.
Alright, my little fishes.
I have got a little proposition for you.
- Truce?
When I get my hands
around your lice bitten neck...
Aye...
Yes. Truce.
Your diamond.
You got it from a golden spear, right?
Aye, I did.
Goblins.
Goblins?
That old fishwives tale.
You expect us to believe that?
I expect you to stand there,
and look ugly and stupid,
and say nothing else.
Goblins real.
Finest thieves in the world.
And greedy as the day is long.
- We're just trying to catch one.
- Yeah.
You know, they say their armor
is made of gold.
- Where can we find them?
- Not far.
There's a hidden forest
just up the Dorian river.
On the Northwest side of the Sanctuary.
They say they keep all their treasure
there in that wood.
Gold, silver, jewels,
as far as the eye can see.
If your Mirror's shiny,
it would be in there somewhere.
Could we access the Sanctuary from there?
Don't know.
Maybe.
Will you show us a way?
Well, you see, that's where
the proposition comes in.
You see, no one's ever
come out of them woods alive.
You two big one,
you look like Huntsman.
And Huntsmen are pretty handy
with the blade, yeah?
We all go in together.
You get your Mirror.
Me and Doreena fill our pockets
with as much loot as we can carry.
Deal?
Aye, deal.
Right after I kill those two.
What? No.
- What?
- Wait.
Why?
I don't know. I like them,
I guess.
Like the dwarf, do you?
So, Mrs. Bromwyn.
Where is Mr. Bromwyn?
Dead, thank God.
How did he die?
Engorging his own eyes out?
Keep flapping and gobble
and you'll find out.
I'm sorry about before.
I would have drunk your water.
You seemed thirsty.
Yeah, yeah I was.
I get thirsty sometimes.
If it's hot or if I'm running.
- Me too!
- Ha.
Or sometimes if I eat
something really salty.
- Like roast chicken.
- Chicken.
I know why you're not talking.
Do you?
You noticed the sparks between
me and Ms. Bromwyn.
I don't know what to say,
she's my type.
Loud and angry.
Well, that's what I'm used to, isn't it?
And I'm awfully sure
you'll have a good life together.
Aye yeah, we would.
But there's a problem.
Another woman.
A bit taller,
not as pretty mind you.
She sounds far too clever
to waste her time with you.
I remember...
That one time we were
caught up in a net together.
That was a long long time ago.
Are you the only hero
of every story you tell?
Aye, that's because I'm very brave.
Which is why I'm going to
save you from drowning.
And how do you expect...
That's some unpredictable waters around here.
It's not me.
You're a real brute.
So are you.
We're here.
Oh.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Come on.
What did you find?
Flint and steel.
Their blood smells like tar.
You see.
It is gold.
Yeah, it is.
Goblins ain't real, aye?
Look.
Do your best to stay dry.
This is bonkers.
Praise the bridge that carries you over.
More.
Death.
They killed each other.
Just like the Queen's army.
What now?
Now we take what we came for.
Keep it covered.
Do not look into it.
Bollocks.
The Mirror.
Move!
- This is heavy.
- I can't see anything.
Ow, you're pushing me!
Come on.
I can't see.
What do you need to see?
I can see, I'm in the front.
Aw, watch your feet.
Move to the side.
Lift up.
Oh, this bridge is wobbly.
It's obviously wobbly,
will you just shut up?
See that?
I've never taken it off.
It's time to go, love.
Come on.
Go, go, go!
Take the Mirror to the Sanctuary.
Come on.
No.
I need fire!
Come on.
Don't you miss.
I never miss.
He saved us.
Eric.
Are you crying?
I can't rid ourselves
soon enough of that thing.
The heart of the Sanctuary
is only 2 hours away.
I say we move tonight.
Aye, there will be a strong moon.
Plenty of light.
No.
Who knows what's lurking in the dark.
I agree.
Kid's stuff. There's nothing
out there that can take us.
Yeah, that's right.
I took you, in a tavern.
I took you here as well.
In the morning then.
Good night.
And after the Sanctuary.
On to the Dwarf mining town.
Jewel and gold merchants
are looking to buy.
Me and Doreena are going to make
an absolute killing.
Where is she?
- Where is Doreena?
- And Nion?
Well.
Would you look at that.
Harpy.
This one, is called Delphinium.
It's good for piles and toothache.
What's this one call?
That's just a flower.
I think it's beautiful.
I think you are beautiful.
- Me?
- Yeah.
No.
If you're looking for gratitude,
you have it.
Nothing more.
What exactly am I suppose to do?
You think it's about you.
- No.
- What you should choose.
What you should do.
And I'm just waiting here
for the man to pass a test.
And you did,
so now I have to love you.
But I don't.
I choose for me.
Not you.
So let me go.
I can't.
Stand or fall, I'll never leave.
Let me go!
Let me go.
Sara, stop it.
The one you loved is dead.
I don't even remember
what it feels like to be her.
We did not ask for our sins.
We did not ask for this life.
Eric, I've done...
terrible things.
Unforgivable things.
I know.
So have I.
Maybe you and me are not
worthy of forgiveness.
That's for someone else to judge.
But we are worthy of each other.
Eric...
Come...
closer...
Kill...
Yes...
Kill for me.
What are you doing?
Have you been true?
Eric.
My heart is yours,
it always has been.
But if this is a game...
End it now.
Have you been true?
Huntsman, what is this?
Stand tall, brother.
Eric.
My Eric.
Your Queen has missed you.
You're not my Queen, Freya.
I'm forever your Queen.
Isn't that right, Sara?
You see...
You abandon her, Eric.
But, not I.
I raised her from despair.
Make her the point of my spear,
my tempered steel.
She's laid waste to kingdoms
and brought men such as you
to their knees.
She's everything
that you're not.
All I had to do is
sent her to you
and you lead her
straight to the Mirror.
It's pathetic.
Oh, what are these?
Dwarfs.
They are just like children.
We're mighty far from children,
bitch Queen.
Adorable.
Bring me the Mirror.
You'll have to kill me first!
No...
I won't.
Doreena, no!
You knew. didn't you?
You knew she would betray you.
And you spared her still.
Have you learned my lesson at last?
Harden your heart, Queen of winter.
Bury the world in a tomb of ice.
It matters not.
Love will endure.
Perhaps you're right.
Shall we find out?
Kill him.
Is he dead?
I think so.
What do we do?
Pull it out.
Go on!
One. Two.
Quickly!
Bloody hell, that hurt.
I can't believe that she missed!
She never misses.
Have you lost your mind?
She betrayed us!
Eric, she's not Cupid.
I doubt that an arrow to the chest
is an expression of her love.
Oh, no, no.
There is a grand design
at work here, friends,
that grows even louder.
Head injury.
Number eight.
She never misses.
Look, I'm twice as angry as you are.
Doreena was the only friend
I had in this world.
But you need to face facts.
Sara is not on your side.
I don't need you
to believe what I believe.
What are these for exactly?
I'll give you a hint.
We're not going to
carry them on our backs.
So what are you gonna do?
Trek all the way to the frozen north?
Face down an evil sorceress
and her entire army?
Aye.
All right, I'm in!
Tull, take the dwarfs to the gallery
and bring the Mirror to my sanctum.
Welcome home, Sara.
Freya...
Come to me...
Say the words...
Speak the words...
"The age can be wicked
to those who walk alone.
When I look into the mirror,
I see myself as I might to become."
Yes...
Mirror, Mirror on the wall,
who is the fairest of them all.
Do not back away from me.
You asked a question.
The Mirror has answered.
Ravenna, how?
Are you not dead?
Yes.
No.
Something in between.
You've become quite literal, Freya.
Of all people, you should know.
That, is but a vessel.
I left my body.
I went into the Mirror.
And there I stayed.
I became part of it.
Trapped.
Until you release me.
We have much to do, little sister.
With you and your army
by my side.
I will regain my kingdom once more.
Snow White...
shall kneel before me.
She will beg for mercy.
And then I'll tear her heart out.
Ho.
That's...
That's a bit bigger than I imagined.
So what's the plan?
You have got a plan?
Aye.
Is it any good?
No.
But it's simple.
Freya will be in her Sanctum,
below the steeple.
I'll make my way down from the top,
find her, and kill her.
What about Nion and Doreena?
I have got someone on the inside
who is going to help me find them.
- Uh, who?
- You.
You have given my Huntsmen new orders.
Better orders.
We will attack tomorrow
in 2 waves.
Flanking maneuver.
I presumed you would agree.
It's a far superior tactic.
This is my kingdom.
Did you say something?
This is my kingdom!
Of course it is.
And it always will be.
I would never question my sister's rule.
But beyond these walls,
is my kingdom.
My dominion.
Do not forget what you owe me.
I made you what you are.
Come on.
Move along.
Hurry and follow.
Move along, hurry now.
You, keep up.
Quickly.
Shut it.
Keep walking.
Just keep walking.
It's not my sister's fault, my lord.
She was hit in the face as a baby,
with a rock.
You two, come with me.
- Did you have to hit him so hard?
- Shut up.
It's very heavy.
Right.
We stuff him in here.
We cover our tracks.
That's very sloppy work, that is.
This is the worst plan ever.
My children.
This is the day for which...
For which you were born.
You'll face an army of men
who have never lost a war.
Men who have...
Who have forgotten...
for what it means to be afraid.
We will bring fear...
once again... to Snow White's army.
And their lands will be mine,
and their children...
Their children...
For I am Queen.
I am the Queen.
This is what I trained you for.
This is why I raised you.
This is why I made you
what you are.
Hello, Eric.
I've missed you.
Guard!
Why?
They're in love.
They reek of it.
Is this not your kingdom?
It is.
Do you not have laws?
I do.
And what...
... is your judgment?
Death.
Traitors!
Traitors to who?
Your old queen?
Your new queen?
- You broke the law.
- The law?
You've forgotten the ones
who loved you?
Your mothers, your fathers.
What law did they break?
Love does not make you weak.
It's all that ever give me strength.
Have we not fought side by side?
We were children!
Brothers and sisters,
do we not love each other?
Fight with me.
If you die,
die for something that's yours.
Why did you turn away, Freya?
You deceived us,
and now you deceive yourself.
- Silence.
- Why didn't you kill us back then?
Instead you break my heart
and turn her against me.
Pretty.
You see, Huntsman.
Love doesn't save your life.
I should know.
I've been dead before.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Stand or fall.
Together.
- I stand with you.
- Aye.
Don't.
Stand back!
Nothing can save you, Huntsman.
All that's left is PAIN !
Ravenna, stop.
Stop!
ENOUGH !
We can't leave the Mirror.
Then we climb.
I thought I've driven
the weakness out of you.
I thought I made you strong.
But you're as pathetic
as you ever were.
Have you lost your mind?
How did you make me strong?
How did you draw the weakness out?
What did you do?
What did you DO?
I don't have to tell you anything.
Oh.
Oh, but you do.
You see, you said it yourself.
You're something between
this world and the Mirror.
I summoned you out.
Now, you are bound to me!
Tell me the truth.
Mirror, Mirror on the wall,
Who is the fairest of them all?
You are, my queen.
But not for long.
Your sister holds a baby
to her breast.
A daughter.
She will grow to be more beautiful
than even you.
You cannot ask such a thing of me.
I ask nothing.
I am but a reflection.
And you...
you have already decided.
Kill...
Kill for me...
Oh.
I loved her.
I loved you.
That's why I'm stronger than you!
Leave my children alone!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I killed your daughter.
And released the greatest power
within you.
A power you have wasted
on nothing but cheap sentiment!
Did you not think
I wanted a child?
I wanted love?
But these things...
... were not meant for me.
I have a higher calling!
Do you still believe...
... that love conquers all?
Maybe not all.
Just you.
Are you ready, Huntsman?
Aye.
NOOOOOOO !!!
How lucky you are.
Come on.
Breathe.
Oh, breathe.
I'm alright.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
Look, the sun!
Once upon a time,
there lived a beautiful queen,
who's heart was broken in two.
But even buried under ice and snow...
Love survives.
- Not on your life.
- Fine. Fine. Fine.
You're going to give up that easily?
God, you're stupid.
The lands of the North were free.
And Snow White's kingdom
was safe from harm.
And so,
some fairy tales do come true.
But none ever truly end.
Subtitle created by - Aorion -
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org